<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Gaming (new threads)</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/c-31957/gaming</link>
		<description>Threads in the forum category &quot;Gaming&quot; - Discuss gaming other than BvS.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:18:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12960786</guid>
				<title>Other newbies at online casinos?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12960786/other-newbies-at-online-casinos</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 10:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jenny_Jenny</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6048319</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi! Are there others who have just entered the world of online casinos? Felt like I needed something new and this has been my latest hobby. Any suggestions on how to hit the jackpots? What are the best new Finnish casinos for this? Thanks.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12534787</guid>
				<title>Ever tried slots and card games online?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12534787/ever-tried-slots-and-card-games-online</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 17:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jacob89</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5666170</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Looking for other options other than RPG games, but not as exhausting as RPG.</p> <p>Was recommended online card games and slots. Been on it for a month now. Any other BVvS players who're into this as well?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-369200</guid>
				<title>goal to get item in League of Legends named after Billy Vs. Snakeman</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-369200/goal-to-get-item-in-league-of-legends-named-after-billy-vs-s</link>
				<description>In League of Legends the reward for getting 1000 referrals is naming an in-game content item. I want to name an item in honor of BvS.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 19:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>zebulen</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>First off here is the link for my referral page.</p> <p><a href="http://signup.leagueoflegends.com/?ref=4db02e22c11a4251158774">http://signup.leagueoflegends.com/?ref=4db02e22c11a4251158774</a></p> <p>Its a free to play game that is fun whether or not you want to help with the item naming, all you have to do for the referral to count is reach lvl 5, which is not very hard.</p> <p>When I reach 1000 referrals I will name an item after whatever the most voted BvS item is that appears in this thread.</p> <p>I want to do this as a thank you to McMasters for making BvS, and as a way to further promote his game. I love playing this as much as LoL and hope that others will be able to enjoy both games as much as I do.</p> <p>I will also update everyone periodically on the progress of this endeavor.</p> <p>Thank you, and wish me luck.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243743</guid>
				<title>join Omerta village they are doing impossible mission</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243743/join-omerta-village-they-are-doing-impossible-mission</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Murakami</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>486671</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>name says it all</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-171327</guid>
				<title>Dungeons and Dragons Campaign</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-171327/dungeons-and-dragons-campaign</link>
				<description>You wanna play a campaign online, but prefer the text-based type to DnD Online? Character-generating madness ensue</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Novaix</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>333449</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I wanted to play online, but I preferred the text-based type to the online game, so I figured it would be quite logical for such a game to be played on a forum. Therefore…</p> <p>I only have the 3.5 rules, and would prefer to use them, but if you want to use other rules feel free to make your own thread ;)<br /> Of those, I only have the 3 core rules (DM guide, PC handbook, Monster Manual)</p> <p>Oh, and although I'm organising it, I'm fine being a PC. Either way is fine with me, it's just me being a PC might be easier what with not having all the rules.<br /> I have a few links to sites with DnD information, and could probably convert them from 4e to 3.5</p> <p>So… yeah, post if you're interested.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-151315</guid>
				<title>Yoshirou needs AV rivals</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-151315/yoshirou-needs-av-rivals</link>
				<description>Ok im back playin AV as im workin on another character and playin Yoshirou again too.......until i get this other character to 100</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 12:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok im back in AV, Yoshirou needs 19 AV rivals, post here if you add me and i'll add you back</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114700</guid>
				<title>Byond. The ultimate in gaming!!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114700/byond-the-ultimate-in-gaming</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 04:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ninjajohn100</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>115224</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Try this site for awesomness in gaming!! My personal favorite is Bleach by VcentG. Check it out!!</p> <p><a href="http://www.byond.com/games/VcentG/Bleach">http://www.byond.com/games/VcentG/Bleach</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77745</guid>
				<title>AdventureQuest</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77745/adventurequest</link>
				<description>The name is cheesy.
The game is fun.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 16:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wartooth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>174414</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So…does anyone here play AdventureQuest?</p> <p>Oh, if you're wondering, the URL is <a href="http://www.battleon.com">http://www.battleon.com</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74031</guid>
				<title>Animeversus - Need a rival?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74031/animeversus-need-a-rival</link>
				<description>BvS&#039;s unloved step-sibling</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 04:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well, there's another game by animecubed that came before BvS called animeversus. It's not quite as deep as BvS and not as much fun (in my opinion) but it's not all that bad either. It's main drawing point for people who already play BvS us that after reaching a particular point in animeversus you get a special permanent item (See here:<a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:pika-bike">http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:pika-bike</a>).</p> <p>I was just wondering if anyone else played and more specifically if anyone that did play would be interested in adding me as a rival?</p> <p>And if anyone's interested (and feeling generous) I'd appreciate it if you'd sign up (and give me a referral bonus after you reach lvl 10) by clicking here: <a href="http://www.animecubed.com/animeversus/av/create.html?friend=moodragonx">http://www.animecubed.com/animeversus/av/create.html?friend=moodragonx</a></p> <p>The referral bonus isn't all that great so I don't mind if you don't sign up under me, but I'm just looking to get some rivals.<br /> The rival system in that game works a lot like the sparring system in Billy vs Snakeman but with more perks. The only problem is there's no in-game way of messaging someone so all the rival negotion has to be done somewhere outside of the game (which is why I'm here).</p> <p>A lot of information about the game mechanics, and questions you may have about the game (as you start playing) can be answered here: <a href="http://www.animecubed.com/animeversus/howtoplay.shtml">http://www.animecubed.com/animeversus/howtoplay.shtml</a></p> <p>Overall the game resembles BvS a lot (BvS is supposed to be a sequel) and isn't hard to pick up at all. It does parodies on manga and anime in general and their crazed fans (there's a fangirls stat).</p> <p>So, if anyone's interested just post here we can exchange user names and start pummeling each other.<br /> Thanks in advance.</p> <p>P.S. Wrong Forum by any chance? I was debating between this and off-topic since this thread's purpose isn't necessarily to "discuss the game" but discussion isn't discouraged here so… don't shoot?</p> <p>P.S.S. It takes quite a while to get the item in animeversus unless you get A LOT of rivals in the game and fight them daily. But the rival feature speeds things up when taken advantage of.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61389</guid>
				<title>Bleach fan game, lots of fun</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61389/bleach-fan-game-lots-of-fun</link>
				<description>its similar to his game, be dedicated and you will be strong and this site came out not too long ago =D join now and you can be one of the few strongest people in the game.</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 00:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://www.example.com">Click Here</a><br /> Its similar to his game, be dedicated and you will be strong and this site came out not too long ago =D join now and you can be one of the few strongest people in the game. I do have to say, if you join and want to really play the game, message Jim and ill give you a friendly starter kit =) which is a lot of money to start with =D Hope I can see you guys soon</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-47404</guid>
				<title>Kingdom of Loathing</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-47404/kingdom-of-loathing</link>
				<description>Anyone else play?</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 18:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Schon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>88446</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Anyone else play KoL here? That was my first web based game ever. It is a lot more tongue in cheek than BVS, and very different, but I love it. If you haven't seen it you should check it out.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-45536</guid>
				<title>Naruto Fan Game</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-45536/naruto-fan-game</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DesertJ</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>92816</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>NFG is a text based Naruto game, where you are a ninja in one of the villages.</p> <p>Basically you, level up, train in skills, learn jutsus, rank up. You can become a missing ninja or even if you work hard enough a Kage!</p> <p>It's a really fun and addicting game ^^ so here's the link :D</p> <p><a href="http://www.narutofangame.net/new_user.php?uv=10074">Naruto Fan Game!</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>