<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Suggestions / Feedback (new threads)</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/c-31955/suggestions-feedback</link>
		<description>Threads in the forum category &quot;Suggestions / Feedback&quot; - Post suggestions and feedback on how to improve the Wiki!</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 02:35:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12223400</guid>
				<title>シャネル 偽物</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12223400/</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>シャネル 偽物</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>お札入れもカードスロットを添えたシャネル財布コピーは、実用性が印象的。ブランド 通販 店 そんなシャネルの魅力ともいえるデザインを描いたシャネルの三折り長財布コピーが発売した。シャネル 偽物 ジェットブラックの人気財布の内側はもちろん上質。</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12206990</guid>
				<title>ブランドスーパーコピー代引き後払い時計</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-12206990/</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 08:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ブランドスーパーコピー代引き後払い時計/財布/服佐川国内発送</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>弊社は業界の唯一N品の佐川国内発送pwiki.jpブランドスーパーコピー代引き後払可能対応安全口コミ専門店です！<br /> ルイヴィトン,ロレックス,エルメス,グッチ,ウブロ等ブランドコピー代引き財布/バッグ/時計/服好評OnlineShop！</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-11405488</guid>
				<title>ブランドコピー代引き日本国内発送スーパーコピー品安全必ず届</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-11405488/</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ブランドコピー代引き国内発送</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>ブランドコピー代引き日本国内発送スーパーコピー品安全必ず届く後払い信頼店!最高級スーパーコピー品,ブランドコピー靴,ブランドコピー財布激安,コピーブランド時計, スーパーコピーバッグ通販txy.jp専門店!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-8183262</guid>
				<title>we-fashion.co スーパーコピー 代引き可能</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-8183262/we-fashion-co</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 02:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>スーパーコピー 代引き</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>スーパーコピーブランド代引き対応日本国内発送後払い口コミ安全必ず届く専門店!スーパーコピー信用新品店,ブランドコピー代引き可能国内発送後払いは業界最高N品質に挑戦!品質信用第一なので ご安心ください</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-7313236</guid>
				<title>Wiki Forum Clean Up</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-7313236/wiki-forum-clean-up</link>
				<description>Need to clean out old posts</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 11:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Trapper</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Many old posts asking for Note Page Bingos etc could be cleaned up to make the place less cluttered.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-2196288</guid>
				<title>スーパーコピー</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-2196288/</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 07:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ブランドスーパーコピー</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>チップの表面からいくつかの重要なチップの部品を見て、表面、添え板を並べている上で比較的見やすいのたとえば：アンチ・ショック器。異なる商店があって、等級も異なって、低級でよくあったのは三角形の物のアンチ・ショック器を使って、うそが会ったのを表すのは比較的多いです。良いのはINCBLOCのを使って、高級な腕時計は普通はKIFアンチ・ショック器を使って、たとえばロレックスROLEX、バセロン・コンスタンチン、パテック・フィリップは、彼らが好きで、注意深くあなたを観察して発見して、たとえおなじなチップを使うのですとしても、アンチ・ショック器の規格も行くのが異なりました.たとえばオメガOMEGAと帝陀TUDORはすべてETA2892チップを使って、しかしTUDORはKIFを使って、はINCBLOCを使って、高級な腕時計は高級な伝統の方法があって、通常KIFアンチ・ショック器はウォーム式の精度と構造(“オーストリアが特にこれを垂れる”)を調整して組み合わせて、高級な腕時計のチップの標識、最も最低限度はえこひいきのルーマニア打つ微調整する機関を使うのです。</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-1033495</guid>
				<title>Anti-Spoiler Measures?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-1033495/anti-spoiler-measures</link>
				<description>A suggestion regarding Quest pages.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 00:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Aldraia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>628021</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Just as a thought, perhaps on Quest pages we could list everything needed to complete the Quest at the top of the page? I know for me it is a pain trying to scroll through and check the requirements without reading all the text and turning the actual Quest into tedium.<br /> (I would, of course, be willing to do much of the work in adding such a thing to extant pages.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-384020</guid>
				<title>Welcome to the Jungle!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-384020/welcome-to-the-jungle</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 19:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ignifer</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>390206</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Jungle Missions are now added to the game (and the wiki), but they still need to be spaded out completely. Got the basics added in, but I don't know whether or not any of the missions are rare, or if any of those ones without hidden content actually do have something. It's possible, if unlikely, that they give content at a higher crank, or are RedEye only, or something else I'm not testing. And, of course, we need all the mission texts, difficulties, and results. Will put in what I have already.</p> <p>Also, we need to add in the Workshop, and add Jungle to the top bar.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370320</guid>
				<title>Glowslinging Allies unlisted</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370320/glowslinging-allies-unlisted</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 19:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As far as I can see, none of the glowslinging allies are listed in the allies untabbed page- nor are the Flower Wars allies.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-363809</guid>
				<title>No page for El Diablo Supreme</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-363809/no-page-for-el-diablo-supreme</link>
				<description>Village perk</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 00:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>LittleGruz</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>775033</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've recently discovered there was a link to El Diablo Supreme in a very highly upgraded village and I found there wasn't a page on it. So I though it might be good for one to be made. This area first appeared when I had -2 stamina.<br /> The page had the following text:</p> <p>El Diablo Supreme</p> <p>You walk into the roaring lucha arena, and see a huge crowd cheering at some weirdo in the center ring, with a silly mask and a microphone (he looks a lot like the guy who stands on the Crank, now that you think of it)..</p> <p>&quot;Does anyone have the courage to face..&quot;<br /> the crowd joins in, saying the rest together with the man..<br /> El Diablo Supreme?&quot;</p> <p>You survey your surroundings..</p> <p>(If you have 1 to 9 Stamina remaining, you may spend it here once a day, in the Lucha Ring, readying yourself to fight El Diablo Supreme. If he points you out, you get a chance to use all your training to wrestle El Diablo Supreme - if you win, you get 100 Stamina. If you lose, however, all your training goes to waste. The people who've beaten El Diablo Supreme within the past 24 hours are listed in the Desfile de los Técnicos below)</p> <p>Current Training Level: 3<br /> Last Win: Never!<br /> Days until next lucha: 9<br /> Stamina: 0</p> <p>&#8212; Training &#8212;<br /> Already Trained today!</p> <p>&#8212; Lucha &#8212;<br /> Now is not the time, luchador..</p> <p>&#8212; Desfile de los Técnicos &#8212;</p> <p>Edit: Just realised that this was a recent addition</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561</guid>
				<title>Big Shammy Lvl 2</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561/big-shammy-lvl-2</link>
				<description>Something missing from his page.</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 04:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nytol</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>919249</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I apologize if this is in the wrong spot. I must say that this wiki has been very helpful in using BvS and possibly kept my interest in the game.</p> <p>The reason I'm making this post is that I notice much of the content for Flower Wars has been added, but I noticed something that seems missing. I accidentally left Big Shammy Lvl 2 in my party over night when I first got him and I noticed I had an extra free game for Flower Wars at day roll. On my main screen listing my bonuses it was listed as he played games with me through the night. I'm without the exact phrase at the moment, but I've used the extra free game lots of times.</p> <p>I Noticed Cato Lvl 2's over night bonus was listed and wanted to point out that I think all of the Flower Wars characters possible have an overnight bonus. I am not a very high level in Flower Wars so I can not check this for every one.</p> <p>Anyway I just wanted to point this out in case no one else noticed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-361587</guid>
				<title>Pigeons lacks a page</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-361587/pigeons-lacks-a-page</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 00:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Luc</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Pigeons needs a wiki page.</p> <p>If odds calculating is a problem, just hit up Google for a Keno calculator, and set Jackpot to 0.</p> <p>Thanks<br /> Luc &quot;Obvious post&quot; French</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-349734</guid>
				<title>Allies pages revamp?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-349734/allies-pages-revamp</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 03:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The allies page has the icons of each ally load after the framework and any specific ally type links are done (for example, the &quot;wasteland&quot; section) and as such shunts the entire page down as they load. Can we either get the cells resized to proper hold the icons without resizing as they load, or the icons resized so that when they are loaded they don't force the cells to resize? Or if a third option that still deals with the issue can be found, whatever the case.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-349732</guid>
				<title>Teams Link Streamlining,</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-349732/teams-link-streamlining</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 02:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While editing the page for Ninja Art: Hottie Regeneration, while adding the teams that specifically give a chakra discount, that a lot of them are counter-intuitive to most other links, requiring the addition of &quot;-bonus&quot; at the end of the team name even if it doesn't have it. Would be nice to get it sorted out so that all such pages have the &quot;-bonus&quot; removed if not applicable, and all links tidied up appropriately.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296055</guid>
				<title>Crank page needs update</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296055/crank-page-needs-update</link>
				<description>noticed an error on some of the requirements of crank for some of the keys.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 07:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Trevor</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>on the Crank page, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/the-crank">http://bvs.wikidot.com/the-crank</a><br /> there are two errors in the Crank Requirement list,<br /> another wiki page, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:r00t">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:r00t</a> confirms these corrections.<br /> As for actual experience, I just acquired Filthy and Noodle Shop with only a crank of +2.<br /> Corrections are in brackets:</p> <p>Find Errant Bit on Syntax Error Item Crank 1+<br /> Find Dance Floor on Mind The Gap Key Crank 2+ (recommended, not required)<br /> Find Delicious on Eat The Tasty Key Crank 2+ (recommended, not required)<br /> Find Chosen on Flaw in the World (Nin) Key Crank 6+<br /> Find Filthy on Flaw in the World (Tai Nin) Key Crank 6+ (+2 recommended, not required)<br /> Find Hopeless on Flaw in the World (Gen) Key Crank 6+<br /> Find Noodle Shop on Flaw in the World (Gen Tai) Key Crank 4+ (+2 recommended, not required)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-247819</guid>
				<title>Parent Pages</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-247819/parent-pages</link>
				<description>want to link Parent Pages</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 11:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nait</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>329508</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi guys, I just wondered if it's allowed to set the Parent Page for each site. I guess that would improve the navigation through the wiki.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-247796</guid>
				<title>I want a holiday page.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-247796/i-want-a-holiday-page</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2010 06:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Darkuwa</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>495369</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Or like a holiday tab under other and a page for each holiday.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-241853</guid>
				<title>Suggestion: Basic Bloodline Comparison</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-241853/suggestion:basic-bloodline-comparison</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 08:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Basically, a page where you can see the comparison between different bloodlines.<br /> +AP/XP , +Stamina, +Event find, +Appetite, Wkai bonuses, r00t bonuses, PW bonuses, and so on.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-240830</guid>
				<title>Power of Greass mistake?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-240830/power-of-greass-mistake</link>
				<description>Either Wiki has a typo, or I found a bug. I&#039;d like to get clarification before reporting.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 03:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Liminality</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>On the Pizzawitch Mission, Add Some Toppings!, you can get an Unknown Pizza as a drop. Since my level and range are too low to complete this normally, I used Flying Thunder God Technique along with Power of Greass since I only had 11 stamina left. This is the result…</p> <p><a href="http://img441.imageshack.us/i/82302511.png/">http://img441.imageshack.us/i/82302511.png/</a></p> <p>Is this a typo on BVS Wiki, or is it a bug?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-227239</guid>
				<title>add yuki-chan to allies list?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-227239/add-yuki-chan-to-allies-list</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 23:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>itachi92</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>can someone add yuki-chan to the allies list? she's already in the wiki and you can get to her by looking at her team with tsukasa, but its not on the main allies bit (not under party house allies anyway)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>