<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>General (new threads)</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/c-31954/general</link>
		<description>Threads in the forum category &quot;General&quot; - General Discussion on the BvS Wiki</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:18:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-1792794</guid>
				<title>Would someone bingo me?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-1792794/would-someone-bingo-me</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 18:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nishimoto</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Where on the forum can I find players to soft bingo with the note page in order to get Anonymous? Find me as Nishimoto at Neo Konoha Village.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-891710</guid>
				<title>Start processing memberships again</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-891710/start-processing-memberships-again</link>
				<description>Non-members are not allowed to edit any page anymore because of wikidot policies.</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 09:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>tn5421</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>378091</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Non-members are not allowed to edit any page anymore because of wikidot policies. Please start processing membership applications again.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-867629</guid>
				<title>Retail</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-867629/retail</link>
				<description>Needs a header section</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 14:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The upcoming new content that's already got two pages, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/retail:truck-loading">Truck Loading</a> and <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/retail:perfect-poker">Perfect Poker</a>, should be slotted into the header somehow. I tried looking for a Shop page, since Retail seems to be all about the Shop, but there's only the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/store">Store</a> which looks incredibly out of date.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-624059</guid>
				<title>Email Notifications</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-624059/email-notifications</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 14:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I want to change daily notifications, so that instead of getting emails from EACH AND EVERY CHANGE, i get one a day instead. Anyone know how to change the settings? there's a checkbox in wikidot settings to disable instant notification, but i'm afraid unchecking it will stop me from receiving ANY email messages</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-459157</guid>
				<title>Can&#039;t see market graph for items</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-459157/can-t-see-market-graph-for-items</link>
				<description>Can&#039;t see market graph for items</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 10:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>nothing</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It seems to have been replaced by this 'pastehtml' thing. Please rectify.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-398277</guid>
				<title>Ninja Kitty&#039;s special ability</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-398277/ninja-kitty-s-special-ability</link>
				<description>extra ability when at max lvl 100</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 15:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Knightman</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I leveled Ninja Kitty to lvl100 yesterday, but didn't see the extra &quot;100lvl max&quot; ability until after dayroll today.<br /> The 100 max lvl ability for Ninja Kitty is</p> <p>+5 Stamina per Kaiju Attack</p> <p>So when looking on your main page, and you mouse over Ninja Kitty in your Current Bonuses, it will say<br /> +20% Kaiju Damage, +5 Stamina per Kaiju Attack</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-396202</guid>
				<title>Rare Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-396202/rare-missions</link>
				<description>Catch a Legendary Spy and Time to Kill really not rare?</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 18:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Basically I'm asking about Catch a Legendary Spy (listed as A-Rank Genjutsu) and Time to Kill (listed as Monochrome Genjustu). I spent over a hundred smokebombs on the relevant Genjusu mission stacks, trying to get these missions to show up, with no success, but was able to get both within 10 smokebombs each after switching to general.</p> <p>I realize this is a very small sample size, so has anyone managed to get these missions to show up without using General missions? And if so, was it pre-recode?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-384699</guid>
				<title>How do we handle the post-Look change?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-384699/how-do-we-handle-the-post-look-change</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 23:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ignifer</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>390206</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Add in a new category of missions, the way we did for Inner Wasteland? Add the missions to the appropriate categories and put &quot;Have not completed The Look&quot; and &quot;Have completed The Look&quot; in the content? Even ignoring casually spoiling the content (I don't care what happens if you click on it, but if you're just looking at the Missions page, you shouldn't have your game experience spoiled), it's kind of a complex little situation to handle.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-376922</guid>
				<title>How does the Worldcracker work?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-376922/how-does-the-worldcracker-work</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 02:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fertfreak</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1074057</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>From what I can tell from the wiki, You Unleash on day 1 and it activates on day 2. Worldkai that hit Crippled on day 2 would then give emblems for every rank to everyone in your village on day 3, regardless of whether they fought or how high a rank a person got. Am I wrong?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-306268</guid>
				<title>Item display suggestion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-306268/item-display-suggestion</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 05:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>taltamir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>663175</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Originally this was a suggestion (really more of a request for someone to do the work). But I spent the last 5 and a half hours learning and then doing it (instead of my homework T.T) So here is my work for all to see.<br /> I went ahead and created overhauled include pages (I did not modify the current include:item, but instead created include:item-black, include:item-red, include:item-blue)<br /> Those show the exact details and near exact appearance of hovering over an item, and of left clicking an item.</p> <p>I have applied each new template to one (matching) item as a "demo":<br /> For a black item (non perm, non consumable):<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:billy-bucket">billy-bucket</a><br /> For perm item:<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:regalia">regalia</a><br /> For consumable item:<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:super-potion">super-potion</a></p> <p>I think it looks AMAZING and definitely worth it to switch all pages to be this way. The neatest thing is that its only done via simple code and no images so it should be super light.<br /> If someone knows how to make the table appear on the top right (Where the image used to be), please modify the include pages to do so.</p> <p>Note that these are exactly as they are in the game, the red items show their mouseover data in their leftclick, the blue do not, the black do not even have mouseoever.<br /> The quickest way to update all the pages with the needed info would be to change the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/include:item">item</a> page to say:<br /> This page is using an obsolete item include, please replace with the current include from <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/template:items">Item Template</a></p> <p>However, I think I think for such a far reaching change (it will retroactively affect all item pages) a moderator's permission should be sought.</p> <p>Here is (most of) the info I collected to do it:</p> <p>Perm's mouseover:<br /> Pink background: F8D5E7<br /> White background: FEFCFA<br /> Outline: E9A6CC<br /> Text on white: 6C244D<br /> Text on Pink: 9C527B<br /> Width (is always): 306 pixels</p> <p>Non-perm mouseover:<br /> same as perm, except colors are different, I inputted the data directly into the include:item-blue page</p> <p>Item left-click description:<br /> Blue Background: 0E0C5F<br /> Brown background: E0C69A<br /> Text on brown: 000000<br /> Tradeable background: 660000<br /> Loopable background: 006600<br /> Permanent background: 666600<br /> Sellable background: 000066<br /> White text: FFFFFF<br /> Dotted border: A75928<br /> Image Wideth= 100px +3 on each side<br /> width of rest= 192px<br /> pixels after the 106 of picture to reach tradeable/sellable box: 17px<br /> pixels between tradeable and loopable: 2px<br /> Tradeable text: Tradable / Untradable<br /> Sellabele text: Is Sellable / Not Sellable<br /> Loopable text: Is Loopable / Not Loopable<br /> Permanent text: Permanent / Non-Permanent<br /> Image border: black aka 000000</p> <p>The current models are available at:<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/include:item">item</a><br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/include:item-red">item-red</a><br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/include:item-blue">item-blue</a></p> <p>problems:<br /> Issue 1: putting 306 pixels in the table style gives me a 300px wide cells. Putting 306px in the cell style gives me 314px wide cells. Rendered moot by issue 2.<br /> Issue 2: The text on the wiki is different (larger, wider spaced) then the one used for the mouseover &amp; leftclick boxes. So if someone wants to tweak them to match go right ahead. As it is, the boxes are similar but not exact to what is found in BvS.</p> <p>I realized, the pink popup is only for items colored red in your bucket. Blue colored ones have a light blue popup, and black colored ones have no popup. I created seperate colored ones.<br /> AFAIK the reds are pemanent items, and blue are consumables, while black items are neither.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303936</guid>
				<title>Superfail</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303936/superfail</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 20:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>WingedCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>57091</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/partyhouse:superfail">http://bvs.wikidot.com/partyhouse:superfail</a></p> <p>Draft posted. WARNING: McM may still be adjusting the game, depending on how it goes over its first week.</p> <p>I don't suppose anyone who's better at dice games than I, could update the page with better strategies?</p> <p>Also, could someone clean it up to the wiki's standard and get it linked off the Party House nav menu, please?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012</guid>
				<title>Tags</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 00:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The use of tags around the wiki is inconsistent at the moment, but I think it's safe to say that if a given tag is being used for only one page, the tag shouldn't be used at all. (e.g., there is no reason why "Sharktooth Necklace" would be tagged "sharktooth" or "necklace")</p> <p>In general, I'd be inclined to stick with making the use of existing tags more consistent, rather than adding new ones wholesale. (e.g., if you notice that most trophies have the "trophy" tag, and one is missing it, go ahead and add it)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393</guid>
				<title>Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy</link>
				<description>FairyGuy has a trophy named Om Nom on his forum signature on the official forums... Is it real?</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 10:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As the summary says, FairyGuy has the trophy shot on his Forum Signature on the official forums saying he earned it 12/11/10. It states "You Bargletronned before you Nommed". Is this a real trophy, and if so, is it obtained by simply using the Bargletron before you eat anything that day?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-280440</guid>
				<title>Psycho Mask</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-280440/psycho-mask</link>
				<description>New item</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2010 06:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>msliver</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>546523</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Psycho Mask<br /> Ew, this got pulled off of such a creepy guy..<br /> (Base Bingo Track Difficulty set to 0, Item disappears at Dayroll (does not count for Perm Count))</p> <p>Untradable Is Loopable<br /> Not Sellable Permanent</p> <p>You can get it for beating a psycho house (choose right in the minigame after finding a psycho house) in candyween.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-266021</guid>
				<title>Billy con wanderings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-266021/billy-con-wanderings</link>
				<description>help expand the wander page for billy con by posting your wander results</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 12:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Vinccent</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>446142</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>so i figured that bi;;con might need a bit more info, and would like to help</p> <p>Wandering Encounter<br /> Modifiers: 9+ Cool, Full Cosplay, &lt;2 Sleep, With The Flow<br /> You are given a Cosplay Cupcake by a friend!<br /> +4 Nom</p> <p>I got a few other wanders that aren't on the page but i didn't think of this till now, I'll be posting here all the different wanders i get that aren't on the wiki page or this post.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-257124</guid>
				<title>11DBHK new Gear</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-257124/11dbhk-new-gear</link>
				<description>Just beat him in Arena might as well update his page...</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 02:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rayning</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>534534</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Coolness Badge<br /> Soul Glove<br /> Codec<br /> Ninja Puppet<br /> Giant Fan<br /> K-Dog's Headband<br /> Desert Robes</p> <p>Add those to his profile.</p> <p>Have a nice day</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243733</guid>
				<title>join Omerta village they are doing impossible mission</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243733/join-omerta-village-they-are-doing-impossible-mission</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Murakami</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>486671</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>name says it all</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-237057</guid>
				<title>Permissions Problem</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-237057/permissions-problem</link>
				<description>I can&#039;t make a village page, but i&#039;m the leader!</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 20:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm the leader of the Pain village. I tried to make a page for my village, since i'm the leader. However, the site only lets mod/admin do such a thing. Problem?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314</guid>
				<title>Speedloop guide to slow</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314/speedloop-guide-to-slow</link>
				<description>I have started speed looping and have found the guide to be slow. It says that you need to be done most of the starting things, but it tells you to do things that slow you down: bingos, reaper.</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 22:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Hokorippoi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>448532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have started speed looping and have found the guide to be slow. It says that you need to be done most starting things, but it tells you to do things that slow you down: bingos, reaper.</p> <p>Here is the time table of what I 1st loop has been like so far.<br /> Day 0, loop day: Loop, Chunin, Special Jonin.<br /> Day 1, 1st full day: Jonin.<br /> Day 2, 1st Jonin only day: Taijutsu lvl 23.</p> <p>Looking at the ap I get, I should be able to loop in 2-3 days max.<br /> Bingos and reaper would have added a few days.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-214000</guid>
				<title>Pinky Lvl 3</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-214000/pinky-lvl-3</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2010 08:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Spl4sh3r</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>432434</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>There is one mistake written on the Pinky Lvl 3 page. It say you have to complete the synch in one try to get her to level up. This is incorrect, the real number is 6 or less. Mostly since I got it in 4 tries and because it say something about mastery in 6 tries or less on the synch.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>