<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Roleplaying (new threads)</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/c-32975/roleplaying</link>
		<description>Threads in the forum category &quot;Roleplaying&quot; - Want to add stories to your BvS character?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 02:36:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-251784</guid>
				<title>new hero coming to town</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-251784/new-hero-coming-to-town</link>
				<description>you are a new comer that helps peple with day to day things (what harm could it do)...............</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 03:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>zach caldwell</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>513359</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>One day you were walking around your village and you saw some one in need of help so you head over to him to see what was up. He say he had put up some flyers to join his gulid but he has not hade any luck with any one joining. You ask him what it is about and he reply's: we look around the world for people who need help and we well help them to the best of our abilty you don't have to do jobs you don't wont to but to the pluse side every time you come back with a job done and with the person's name and what you did in one of thes note books (he shows you one) you get a free muffen of your chose" you look at him and think for awhile …… then you say that you will join his gulid and that you might be able to get some of your friends to join to. Then you run off looking for your friends.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243739</guid>
				<title>join Omerta village they are doing impossible mission</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243739/join-omerta-village-they-are-doing-impossible-mission</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Murakami</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>486671</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>name says it all</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-151734</guid>
				<title>Sikcools path</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-151734/sikcools-path</link>
				<description>To become sannin</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 16:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sikcool</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>317334</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sikcool is a stupid guy wich isnt so powerful.<br /> He only has one kaiju drop.<br /> He just achived sannin in SEASON 3 dammit.<br /> His way was the redeye. With training from anomynus and many petals from shorty i made 7 elexirs.<br /> With more help from the party expert j-diddy i managed to bllow up my ryo on parties… The rest i did with anomynouses secret training.<br /> Sannin they call me now. Im a legend XD (not really, i suck)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115365</guid>
				<title>Chasing</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115365/chasing</link>
				<description>Choose whether you are a ninja chasing another ninja for some reason or you are being chased by another ninja.
Or of course both!!!</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 17:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Shady Neo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>258030</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Shady Neo made a wrong turn somewhere in life, as a result over 20 countries wanted him dead for criminal experimentation. On top of that the ninja he created in a test tube was seeking out SNAKEMAN. Shady had to find him first or surrender all the secrets in the body.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271</guid>
				<title>Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures</link>
				<description>K-Dog travels back to Cana&#039;s Wolf Pack to tell of Cana&#039;s  adventures in the Ninja world and other world these are the tales he will tell.</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Back when Cana was just a young puppyish cub a ninja would always travel by her pack bringing gifts, knowledge and always entertained the young cubs like Cana with tales of his adventures and the exploits of his ninja and reaper companions.</p> <p>This ninja was very excentric had a metal plate over 1 eye and constantly had his nose in a book. When he arrived after Cana's generation were born he caused quite a stirr. He had always senced potential in the Wolves of this pack and had taken some back to train long ago. Some like nico and risa had returned to the pack and tought the cubs of the ways of the ninja.</p> <p>This life had intrigued Cana from the moment she had first heard the word ninja, when K-Dog arrived she hung on his every word and every time he returned she questioned him more. Until 1 visit he asked the pack leader could he take Cana to Narutofan to assess her ability.</p> <p>The elders allowed it and Cana travelled with K-dog to the Ninja world. As they travelled K-Dog asked her</p> <p>"Why do you have bandages over your eyes Cana? Last I saw you you had perfect albit vivid colbalt crimson slitted eyes?"</p> <p><strong>"Well"</strong> Cana began</p> <p>"Hold on let me guess you poked your eyes with a kunai?"</p> <p><strong>"Nope I'm recovering after having had an eye infection"</strong></p> <p>"oh..ok…<em>hmm she is gonna have a white eye limit now…</em>well whats the matter….?"</p> <p><strong>"Who goes there show you self"</strong></p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"woah your good K-Dog didnt sence me yet"</span></p> <p>"Ah… there you are t-Pad"</p> <p><strong>"huh?? Who is he K-Dog-sensei?"</strong></p> <p>"Your new sensei Cana this is where I leave you"</p> <p><strong>"oh.. ok.. I'll see you again wont I"</strong></p> <p>"Yeah when you are chunin"</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Alright till then K-Dog she's safe with me"</span></p> <hr /> <p>After a months training with t-Pad (and still sparing). Cana Joined White Wing's Village (the nightmare) And made Chunin</p> <hr /> <p><strong>"Yay I did it"</strong></p> <p>"Yeah you did Cana I knew you would"</p> <p>Cana swirled around</p> <p><strong>"K-DOG!!!"</strong></p> <p>"Woah dont slobber over me would ya…….Um Cana would you get off me"</p> <p><strong>"oops ok"</strong></p> <p>A couple of seconds later ater wipins some wolf slobber and dust K-dog turned to Cana</p> <p>"Cana I'll be travelling back soon so we gotta make stories for me to tell or have you got some for me?"</p> <p><strong>"Oh I've got some to tell Sensei!!!"</strong></p> <p><strong><span style="text-decoration: line-through;">-</span>-</strong></p> <p>Cana Entered the forest of death to remove traps and any ninja that were lurking around</p> <p>As she removed yet another trip wire</p> <p><strong>"<em>whats with these nin and trip wires have they no imagination….</em>huh whos there behind that tree with the scorch marks"</strong></p> <p>A shadow emerged……..</p> <hr /> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174</guid>
				<title>Wild and Untamed</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed</link>
				<description>Animist Life simple as that</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 21:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Naruto Namikaze</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Animist was a man of many words…nope not many…but when he did talk your learned to shut up or get the hell out of dodge either way you learned never to talk bad of him or his friends or do stupid shit with him around. But some people are just to dumb for there own good.</p> <p>Animist sighed as he caught the fist coming his way…this people just didn't stop did they break the arm in his grip he smirked when he heard it shatter before sending the last of the masked people flinging into a tree. He smirked and picked up all the bags and used clones to pick pocket all of them before taking all their useful stuff and sealing it away.</p> <p>Making his way down the road he made sure to mask his power and smiled in a wolfish kind of way before making his way to a stand and ordering some ramen…ahhh he loved food.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-44114</guid>
				<title>SNAKEMAN&#039;s Cantina</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-44114/snakeman-s-cantina</link>
				<description>Hidden deep within the Country of Sandwiches...</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 19:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>A fragment of a newspaper tumbles across the path. It bears a headline, "Mysterious Tavern Discovered!" Looking closer, the following story can be discovered…</p> <blockquote> <p>Deep within the forest of the Country of Sandwiches, an old run down bar has been found. It appears that a large number of shinobi participating in the Ninja World War have been congregating here for quite some time. The sign outside the door reads "SNAKEMAN's Cantina," suggesting that this may be the establishment of the notorious Sannin level criminal. Shinobi are advised to take extreme caution before approaching this establishment.</p> </blockquote> <p>(<em>Note</em>: Feel free to use this thread to roleplay amongst yourselves. It's a standard "bar" style environment, so knock yourselves out!)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-44112</guid>
				<title>Rules of the Forum</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-44112/rules-of-the-forum</link>
				<description>Follow these!</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 19:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Greetings!</p> <p>This forum is intended to provide BvS players a place where they can add some depth to their character that would not ordinarily be provided in the game. Here, you can submit stories, background information, and setup "Bar" style places where players can hang out and interact "in character."</p> <p>However, the following rules are in effect.</p> <ol> <li><strong>All Roleplaying in this forum is to be about <em>Billy Vs. SNAKEMAN</em></strong>. This is not a Naruto/Bleach/Death Note Roleplaying Forum.</li> <li><strong>An attempt should be made to have your roleplay stick close to your actual abilities in <em>BvS</em></strong>. For example, you should not roleplay using <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/jutsu:attack-on-the-nervous-system">Attack on the Nervous System</a> unless your character actually knows that jutsu.</li> <li><strong>The power of your character should be reasonable</strong>. A Genin should lose to a Jonin in most circumstances. Your ninja is not an under appreciated genius who's a low rank now, despite the fact that you think he's all powerful.</li> <li><strong>Play your Bloodline appropriately</strong>. RedEyes poked themselves in the eye and their eyes stayed red. It is not the Sharingan. WhiteEyes got something in their eye, and it stayed white, they don't have the Byakkugan. Similarly, Legacy characters poked their eye out, they don't have the nine-tailed fox sealed within them. You can take some liberties with this, to some degree. For example, a legacy character might claim that a spirit has been sealed in their missing eye-socket. Just be reasonable, don't just rip stuff off from Naruto wholesale, at least make a joke about it.</li> <li><strong>You are not Naruto's long lost brother</strong>. You're not even Billy's long lost brother. Your character should have its own distinct history, not just be some leech latching onto major characters to fill in backstory you don't want to write. However, you can claim a prominent ally has trained you (i.e., "Student of K-Dog" or "Received special training from Shorty".)</li> <li><strong>The only one who can kill your character is you</strong>. Do not attempt (or claim) to kill someone else's character without their express permission in writing.</li> <li><strong>Have fun with it!</strong> <em>Billy Vs. SNAKEMAN</em> shouldn't be taken too seriously. If you're not having fun, something's wrong.</li> </ol> <p>More rules may be added as is appropriate.</p> <p>If this forum goes well, I'm thinking we might add an "rp" category to the main site to preserve some of the more interesting takes that get posted here. But I thought this would add to a greater sense of community, and for some, increase the depth of their BvS experience.</p> <p>Enjoy!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>