<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Off Topic (new threads)</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/c-31960/off-topic</link>
		<description>Threads in the forum category &quot;Off Topic&quot; - Topics that otherwise don&#039;t fit in any of the existing topics.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:19:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243744</guid>
				<title>join Omerta village they are doing impossible mission</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243744/join-omerta-village-they-are-doing-impossible-mission</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2010 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Murakami</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>486671</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>name says it all</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-151377</guid>
				<title>Guru</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-151377/guru</link>
				<description>Thank you all</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2009 18:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I would just like to say that my wiki status has now moved up to guru ^_^ I thank you all to those who asked questions and gave suggestions for the wiki. This means a lot =D Let us continue making this wiki great</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-117174</guid>
				<title>add</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-117174/add</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 17:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>spontaneousadds </wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>261818</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <h2><span>database of Star Wars Battlefront, Socom, and Combat Arms. Also home to the [MAC] clan:</span></h2> <a href="http://battlefu.wikidot.com"><img src="http://battlefu.wdfiles.com/local--files/logos/battle%20logo.png" width="500" alt="battle%20logo.png" class="image" /></a> <hr /> <p><span style="font-size:70%;">add provided by <a href="http://spontaneousadvertiser.wikidot.com">http://spontaneousadvertiser.wikidot.com</a></span></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115565</guid>
				<title>Requesting</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115565/requesting</link>
				<description>I want to get bingo&#039;d by a note page</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 07:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>skieth13</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Can someone bingo me with a note page? Thanks</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115447</guid>
				<title>Merry Ninja Xmas</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115447/merry-ninja-xmas</link>
				<description>This is just a topic for everybody to wish a merry christmas and for those who like to share how they spent their christmas or what they got for christmas.</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2008 07:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Merry Christmas and post away!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-87538</guid>
				<title>Need something...from someone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-87538/need-something-from-someone</link>
				<description>Need help with getting emosuke lvl 3.</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 01:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DemonPupp</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>198091</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Can someone send me a Billy Bucket?<br /> my village hasn't contacted me back and i need one to lvl up emosuke.<br /> PLEASE!<br /> my account name is<br /> DemonPupp<br /> i only need one.<br /> am willing to trade an ultra elixer or reversing hourglass.<br /> or if you need something then i can see what i can do.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-70221</guid>
				<title>Router Broke</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-70221/router-broke</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2008 15:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>My wireless router broke a few days ago and I'm not sure when we're getting a new one.<br /> So I may be inactive.</p> <p>Sincerely,<br /> Chidon</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-69382</guid>
				<title>BvS Player/Village look up.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-69382/bvs-player-village-look-up</link>
				<description>Got bored decided to do this lol</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 03:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Harry Dresden</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>100189</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://mycroft.mozdev.org/developer/devlist.html?email=spychase13%40yahoo.com">http://mycroft.mozdev.org/developer/devlist.html?email=spychase13%40yahoo.com</a></p> <p>Search engine things for BvS so you can look up a village or player.</p> <p>Added a banner look up. (So it looks up the signature banner u use on forums and such.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-65682</guid>
				<title>I looped</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-65682/i-looped</link>
				<description>YAY</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 19:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Arkantos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98147</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Lol I just wanted to brag about my awsomeness ^_^ so here you are in the Off Topic section &lt;_&lt; Yes I am very kind ^_^</p> <p>Hey, Hey, We're the Ninja!<br /> You See Right Through Me<br /> Stand By Your Ninja<br /> Teacher's Pet<br /> Warstruck<br /> Drunken Fist<br /> Flip Out<br /> Money for Nothing<br /> All Together Now<br /> Good Night, Ninja<br /> Seasons Don't Fear<br /> Floating on Air</p> <p>Those are the themes gotten in Season 1 :) YAY for me!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61805</guid>
				<title>Smashing Your Own Ivory Towers.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61805/smashing-your-own-ivory-towers</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 23:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Harry Dresden</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>100189</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><em>The key that locks the prison, unlocks the prison. But you have to turn it the other way. — Arthur M. Young.</em></p> <p>This is a fair complex observation to discuss, but I wanted to give it a try. It's generally accepted that the highest position is the best place to be. High upon the tree, shouting orders to the so called herd. For me, that is the most dangerous place to be in. The higher upon the ladder or tree you stand, the more pain you will feel when you fall down. When did we start to think that we were better than others, and put on our eye shutters for other people with a voice too? what's wrong with a little self-integrity and plea guilty to ignorance? You can argue that this hasn't anything to do with hacking, but I like to believe otherwise.</p> <p>I think it's primordial behavior to get to the top of the tree, it's animal like. It is far from being a truly evolved human being. Some rant about "survival of the fittest" and "hierarchy" without understand the concepts that lie beneath them. Survival of being the fittest, is the one who can adapt. Bacteria can adapt better than we can, and so they will eventually win it -if there is something to win, which is wrong also- from all of us. So they are really the winners aren't they? but they sit at the lowest place possible.</p> <p>Next up is Hierarchy. Hierarchy is really only useful in nature because it is a form of order that could not be obtained otherwise. In better terms: Wolves have hierarchy because they lack the intelligence to communicate properly and comprehend their situation and solve problems. We humans do, but somehow we think it's better to have a group to control and think that hierarchy is the way to go about. We make a mistake, a group can only exist if there are individuals which in term organize the group according to group interaction and discussion upon their individualism. There is no expert, there is no-one better in the group. In fact they are equal and contribute to the overalls group knowledge and understanding. So individuals can organize themselves better and form a true group. Problems arise when some individual thinks he is better than the rest, and want to control the group or want control over other groups. In fact he is the dumbest of the group and only relies on his primordial instincts, because he cannot overlook the whole group other then impose hierarchy, it is too complicated so he substitute his comprehension of reality for what he only knows. This is how our world functions it is how companies function, it is how religion functions and how all groups function in this world.</p> <p>And it is wrong, because we ought to think for ourselves because we are individuals. The cerebral cortex of the human brain gave us the power to escape the lower intelligence and animal instincts, in this regard you could reason that we aren't yet who we ought to be. We escaped the group thousands of years ago to become individuals who can operate in a group because of that very same reason. To organize a group by better communication instead of relying on instincts. My fair guess is that many are not willing or capable to understand or comprehend this thought. So beware the voices who talk too loud, look for the person who doesn't show off. The ones who understand this are people who aren't on top. They don't sit in ivory towers, or claiming to be mister so and so, of company x and y doing z and that and driving the most expensive cars and living it up. Those people sit in their circle watching the world go by and shake their heads while trying to improve it. Those people work behind the scenes, rarely you'll see them. Even more rarely you'll see them boast, because the stand above that. They don't have too, because there is no need to prove yourself by talking everywhere if you are certain anyway. Only actions really counts. I think some of you reading this are individuals like I portray here. I don't know you, but I know that you are there, sitting in silence and grasping what I say without the need to let it be confirmed. I always think that there are people far more intelligent than you think you are, you'll have to take that into consideration every single day and in every discussion.</p> <p>The greatest discovery one can make in my opinion, is to discover that every human being has talent waiting to be unleashed. Every kind of group always suppresses the individuals because their instinct tells them that they could possible take over the group. Which again is animal instinct, and the lesser intelligence. So, you get clashes of cultures, of countries, of companies or clashes of groups and the individuals in them. Some individuals manage to slip out and revolutionize the whole group. See it as a circle that starts small and expands when the individuals are walking towards the edges and returning back to explain the edges for the rest, so that the group can expand towards that edge, and so on until the circle gets bigger and bigger. This is a sad idea, but closer to reality than I like to think otherwise.</p> <p>One revelation from the old Chinese masters was very simple: the lowest place is the place where everything originates from. It is the place that people despise and that yet nourishes everything, a place where no-one bothers to look. The place where a solution awaits in all it's splendor.</p> <p>That place is most certainly you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-53101</guid>
				<title>jounin accesment</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-53101/jounin-accesment</link>
				<description>where is the mission to unlock jounin accesment</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 18:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>where is the mission to unlock jounin accesment</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50769</guid>
				<title>Video downloads?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50769/video-downloads</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 01:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hey I have a regular MP3 player and I was wondering where was a site I could download a music video of "Remember the name" by Fort Minor</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49942</guid>
				<title>What songs do you have on youre mp3 player =D</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49942/what-songs-do-you-have-on-youre-mp3-player-d</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 16:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Teh Kaz</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>101519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have a ton XD =o<br /> Night Drive<br /> venom<br /> boulvard of broken dreams<br /> amercan idiot- i can't get rid of it -<br /> Shawn michael theme song<br /> John Cena- you can't see me<br /> Tazz's theme song<br /> Sabu's theme song<br /> A bunch of digimo songs<br /> Sonic Fly high.<br /> Move along<br /> Dirty littlesecret<br /> Numa numa<br /> Soulja boy- XD-<br /> Jack sparrow song<br /> I am a real american<br /> Ben ten theme song<br /> DX theme song<br /> Naruto GO!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-44599</guid>
				<title>Nine Inch Nails released it&#039;s new album for free...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-44599/nine-inch-nails-released-it-s-new-album-for-free</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well, the first 1/4th at least! They expect you'll be able to find the rest of it on the Pirate Bay as well. I bought a copy for $16.99, but the main site got hammered with 3x's the traffic they expected, so I haven't been able to download it yet. Probably tomorrow.</p> <p>Anyone heard it yet?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>