<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Aether Village</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Aether Village&quot; - yea, its awesome</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:56:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-323030</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-323030</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 04:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yea I'm not even going to dignify a response. Stop trying to fan the fire</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-322226</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-322226</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 06:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Racthoh</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Racthoh here ~ Sorry for the late responses to a conversation I had no idea was taking place. I hadn't expected it to take place because as Genji said, this isn't the where we should be discussing this. Nonetheless, I feel the need to defend myself from false accusation.</p> <hr /> <p>Genji, you said: "I like how you sound like you're giving us a deal, but the fact of the matter is: I'm not stupid.<br /> You could simply scam us, and laugh in our face 2 minutes later. and I'm even less likely to trust you considering you threatened me in-game that you'll attack me."</p> <p>The first part, I completely understand.<br /> Scamming anybody hadn't even occurred to me though, since naming the village was pretty important to me. I was completely willing to spend 5 or 6 days in your village, farming ryo and invading for resources on your behalf.</p> <p>To be clear, my threatening you was in response to your threat. I told you in as little threatening tone as I could possibly give text: that you've lost an ally. (In case you you still don't understand, allowing us to use the name would have made us very grateful allies.) And your response to losing an ally? You were ready to contact McMasters and report us for harassing you if I, or any other Dark Villager, "touched your village"… -_- Even after that, I still held back. I simply linked you to the "Major Bingo Change" topic on Random.</p> <p>Implying that I'm going to bingo you.. some threat, yeah? I'm sure that was the first time someone's ever told you they're going to bingo you.. I mean, it's not like this game is about warring with other players.</p> <hr /> <p>Kagir, you said: "I can understand why you'd be upset that after planning someone else got to the village name first, but it isn't like we've had any contact with Dark Village or any way of knowing what you planned to name your IR village."</p> <p>I know it's extremely far fetched, but there is no denying the possibility of Genji having known about Darks plans for the IM. You could be lying. Of course, without any evidence, it's best to let that go.</p> <p>Though after the village agreed on a new name, then seeing a few days later that that name was taken too, by a genin with only 1 mission completed, I'm finding it hard to simply let go.</p> <hr /> <p>Genji, you also said: "you both came in here attacking me, and claiming it was unfair that I don't give up the name"</p> <p>I don't think I've attacked you. I've asked you to allow us to purchase your Village's name, which was a long shot, but it was still only a question. As for considering the entire situation to be 'unfair,' no I don't. Hence my offer to buy the name.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-322076</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-322076</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You're welcome. Hopefully that SWORDFISH!! part makes you cackle atleast half as hard as we did<br /> see you around</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-321977</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-321977</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 22:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fujikage</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I must say, you sound a lot more mature now. I only wanted to correct what I felt was inaccurate, a now, I find nothing that is. Thank you for your time.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-321966</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-321966</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2008 21:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok I only skimmed through the last reply. I'm done arguing with you, the outcome was decided when Racthoh messaged me. He just decided to be indignant about it, I have better things to do before I start my day. FYI</p> <p>I don't care what people think about me, and simply put, I throw out pretty harsh words to make the little people go away (usually when people become a thorn). I'm only understanding, and willing to listen when people treat me with respect. That flew out the window when you guys posted about being upset here. A separate thread would've been fine, and if you want to convince me that you're a mature and a good ruler, talk to me on civil ground where it is appropriate. Though it seems a little too late for that now.</p> <p>In a sense im similar to Orochimaru when he rules the village of Sound. If im gaining ground, and my buddies are there with me. Awesome. Otherwise, I probably won't take you seriously. Most of the stuff to begin with was pointed at Racthoh for being obnoxious and accusing me of stealing a name, in my recruitment page no less.</p> <p>No, you're right, it doesnt have anything to do with Aether. Like I said the village started as a group of friends, and we had just seen that movie. The swordfish part made me laugh until tears, and had Kagir, and Squiggy yelling AWESOME. So its really just an inside joke among most of us. And seeing how we all started the game together, the joke came at the perfect time, and it just stuck.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-321442</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-321442</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 22:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fujikage</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I believe you need to grow up, yes. One of your most prominent immature traits is that you accuse me of things, which I have not done. Just to name one thing, you accuse me of claiming it was unfair that you don't give up the name. I'm not sure how you read my message, but if you read it again, you should find that no matter how you look at it, I make no claim of it being unfair that you do not give up the name. And speaking about "rediculous", that accusation is ridiculous. Please don't insult me with words you cannot spell. Atleast not if you're just doing it baselessly.</p> <p>If anything…I might make Aether village look more popular? <strong>I</strong> would be the foolish looking one? Don't joke around.</p> <p>I'm not asking you to be clones, it would be enough if you grew up and talked like a reasonable being. Although, I must admit, you are funny.</p> <p>Not being a pushover is good, you should try that, and you probably should avoid getting robbed as well. No, there is no Kage-standard list, nor should their be, since this is only a game, and indeed no one starts off perfect, but notwithstanding if you're a Kage or not, you usually earn on being reasonable, and preferably humble to some degree. Maybe Buffy89 wasn't great, but that is no excuse for you, or me, to follow Buffy89's example. I'm not comparing you to me, or anyone else, so I don't want you to be anyone beside who you are, but I would like you to be less offensive, for every ones sake, decisions and chances can still be taken. It's not that Kagir is nice that makes him benign, it's the fact that he listens, instead of judging whatever he doesn't like as 'random things'.</p> <p>Obviously you do have the village name, and clearly you have no intention of giving it up, however, that doesn't take away anyones right to speak. You can't simply ask someone to move on if they do not wish to. It would be dictatorship to force someone to move on, when they are still troubled by a matter. You could ask them to try and accept how things are, but you should in no way be forced upon any. They fact that you are telling people to, as well as the fact that you have very little patience, are two of the things unsuitable for anyone in a leader position. If you deal with those characteristics, you would surely make an excellent Kage.</p> <p>It's in FE as well as in SSBM, and also a certain colourless sweet-smelling liquid.</p> <p>Get Smart. Will do. But it doesn't sound like it has anything to do with Aether.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-321339</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-321339</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 20:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well Fujikage that first statement was at pointed at Racthoh. I considered you the more mature one at first, and not replying to much other than "Aether is from here" considering it was more Racthoh who attacked me head-on.</p> <p>*laughs* I need to grow up? Nice try Fujikage. you both came in here attacking me, and claiming it was unfair that I don't give up the name…lets not even bring up details on the rediculous comment of "we'll get over it when we feel like it". If anything you might make Aether village look more popular AND making yourself look foolish. Thanks xD</p> <p>Kage-like…..are you implying that theyre all supposed to be clones of you? Where's the fun in being like everyone else?</p> <p>Sorry, my kage approach is to not be a pushover, nor get robbed blind. I don't recall their ever being a Kage-standard list, and no one starts off perfect. Our old village leader in Obvious was Buffy89 and he sucked at first too. By the time he blew it up, I respected him for dealing with half the idiots in our village, and as a leader. Sorry if we can't be like you, but some people like to make their own decisions and take chances. Kagir may be nice to people who spew out random things when the outcome is clear: We have the village name, and have no intention of giving it up. Move On, and stop bugging us. I however have little patience when dealing with people who publically cry when they dont get their way.</p> <p>Aether was also supposedly the 5th element, too. It's not solely on Fire Emblem</p> <p>Swordfish - Watch the movie: Get Smart, or a clip of the swordfish scene on Youtube.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-320806</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-320806</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 04:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I never said you did it to inconvenience me, Genji. So judging by your conclusion, I'd rather see you 'grow up'.</p> <p>Regardless of how much you like how I sound like I'm giving you a deal, the fact of the matter is: I haven't. As for scamming you, I don't get why we would do that. Myself, I wouldn't call the offer Racthoh gave a harassment, but, well… However, it pains me to hear you accusing others of immaturity.</p> <p>Kagir, thank you for understanding. In my case, I'm not as much upset as I am uneasy about the extreme misfortune(on my part), and possibly somewhat jealous. I know you got the name first, but due to the circumstances, the fact does appear in an unfair manner(and it does remotely vex me that you hid the village in, The Swordfish. Why?) I only wish it was for a better reason than FE because I myself put much thought into the name. I took it from the myth of Aether, and then to hear it copied from FE. The fact that it was taken from FE only happened to make it seem more unfair, from the point of view which I am at.</p> <p>At first, the coincidence seemed so unlikely, that it did feel like you stole the name, but when I got around to consider the other possibilities, I chose to believe you didn't.</p> <p>I'm dealing with the fact that you got it fair, but I really rather wish Genji could act more, Kage-like. (Not that many Kages do.)</p> <p>- Fujikage</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-320779</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-320779</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 03:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Kagir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167291</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Fujikage,</p> <p>I can understand why you'd be upset that after planning someone else got to the village name first, but it isn't like we've had any contact with Dark Village or any way of knowing what you planned to name your IR village. We just happened to get to the name first (and in response to "I wish it was for a better reason than FE", thats your opinion, if you don't like Fire Emblem, fine, some of us do.).</p> <p>If we had intentionally planned to undermind your village and steal your name, that would be understandable, but I think getting upset over a village name we happened to get to first isn't exactly noteworthy.</p> <p>Sorry you're irritated with our village name, but we did make it first.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-320778</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-320778</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 03:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes, I create village names just to inconvenience you. Are you kidding me? Grow Up</p> <p>I like how you sound like you're giving us a deal, but the fact of the matter is: I'm not stupid.<br /> You could simply scam us, and laugh in our face 2 minutes later. and I'm even less likely to trust you considering you threatened me in-game that you'll attack me. Seriously, come up with something else and quit harassing me. Deleting announcements is annoying enough, I don't need immature people spamming me.</p> <p>Uzuki, just delete this topic if people are going to cry over a village name. They act like I owe them something for making the village first.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-320749</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-320749</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 01:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>- Fujikage (Just so you don't mix me up with Racthoh.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-320745</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-320745</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 01:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The name will be gotten over when we feel like it.</p> <p>I get that you like the name, too(although I wish it was for a better reason than FE), but the fact that it was decided 15 days ago is nothing compared to the time since we had made that decision. And fairly unrealistic? How come? Surely it can't be more unrealistic than you having just 'happened' to take our name.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-320724</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-320724</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 00:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Kagir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167291</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This isn't really my place to post, but I'm Kagir from Aether Village, and it's a village name, get over it.</p> <p>We simply picked the name (based off of a list of names we generated, Aether named after the mastery move of Ike from FE) because we liked it. How would we have possibly known what you were attempting to name your village?</p> <p>And I don't know if you noticed, but my friend Genji here posted this page 15 days ago, I don't know how long you've been planning to name your village Aether, but that seems fairly unrealistic.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-319632</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-319632</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 18:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Forgot to leave my in game name, Racthoh.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-319628</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-319628</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 18:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The fact that you had to state that you aren't an Immortal Village leads me to believe that you KNEW Dark Village was going to name their Immortal Realm, Aether. I've sent you an in game message, asking you to restart your village, and that we'll reimburse you for your losses.</p> <p>How about I join your village, and leave when you have 500k Village Ryo, 5-10 of each basic resource, and 5-10 village upgrades? That seems like a fair reimbursement for abandoning a village with 4 upgrades, and 9 members.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-316092</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-316092</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 01:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>2 of my friends are off on sannin/the trade run's seeing how my village cannot give them just Yet.</p> <p>we now have several upgrades, and low tax rates. come join, and check us out =D</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-308912</guid>
				<title>Re: Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-308912</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 22:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Update:</p> <p>only a few days after creation and we're almost up to the War Council upgrade. lucky with recruits i suppose</p> <p>i strongly encourage many to join, we already have our sweet headband, and party house to satisfy your gambling needs. our growth is rapid, plus we're all gamers and anime fans. no requirement needed to join, just apply</p> <p>in your village app put in "Genji sent me" for a little care package upon joining</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299#post-306323</guid>
				<title>Aether Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104299/aether-village#post-306323</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 03:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I finally broke down and made a village at the request of friends</p> <p>If you would like to join, it is NOT an IR village. and it will be a casual approach rather than an enemy-maker.</p> <p>currently a handful of members, soon to be epic</p> <p>Kagir, a friend of mine who also plays says: "Join NAO"</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>