<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Openings for Sannin Hopefuls?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216/openings-for-sannin-hopefuls</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Openings for Sannin Hopefuls?&quot; - Any spots in the Wiki or allied Villages for would-be Sannin?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:13:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216#post-308617</guid>
				<title>Re: Openings for Sannin Hopefuls?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216/openings-for-sannin-hopefuls#post-308617</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 15:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Felina</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>236466</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Do you know of any preferred way of contacting the leaders of those villages, or do they just take blind applications usually?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216#post-306155</guid>
				<title>Re: Openings for Sannin Hopefuls?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216/openings-for-sannin-hopefuls#post-306155</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 23:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This particular sub-forum is actually for Wiki Redux villagers (and related stuff), and unfortunately we can't help too much. Because we're an immortal realm village, the game won't let an S1 join our village unless they have Survived the Impossible.</p> <p>I think Underworld, Eulers, Anansi and Threat down all have Epic Monuments and aren't immortal realms, so they can take S1s.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216#post-306071</guid>
				<title>Openings for Sannin Hopefuls?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-104216/openings-for-sannin-hopefuls#post-306071</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 21:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Felina</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>236466</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm coming up on the end of Season 1, and I'd like to take a stab at making a Sannin run before my time runs out. Are there any villages within the alliance that have an open spot and an Epic Monument? I'd be more than willing to stay on and assist the village, or if the spot is needed I could bow out afterwards, whichever works best.</p> <p>My plan is to make my run on the 17th of November. I have everything arranged except Snakeman (who I'd pick up in transition), with the exception of needing to be Note Page bingo'd to grab Anonymous for Obsessive Insight. Thank you in advance for taking the time to read my request.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>