<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Devil Village</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176/devil-village</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Devil Village&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:56:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176#post-349725</guid>
				<title>Re: Devil Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176/devil-village#post-349725</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 23:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DevilSF</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>217602</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>im sure alot of people knows me from here now &gt;.&lt;"</p> <p>tell you the truth my village isnt very good and we need more strong people to join…..</p> <p>after a few weeks then days i will reward you if i think you helped me alot =]</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176#post-334895</guid>
				<title>Re: Devil Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176/devil-village#post-334895</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2008 03:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DevilSF</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>217602</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>now with 26 members</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176#post-318590</guid>
				<title>Devil Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108176/devil-village#post-318590</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 18:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DevilSF</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>217602</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Oh we are just one of those regular villages looking for some really good members to…i dunno….rule bvs? =P<br /> lol…anyway…..if you need a village but cant decide then just come to us….Are we any good? umm… we are just like another normal villages that the village leader cares for there members and uses a vote method to decide on decisions so we can all be happy. soo if we are any good i guess ill say yes<br /> Any spectacular reason why you should join? Well we are still growing so once we grow we will grow faster, and we are half way till reaching the highest level we can grow….with 22 members and still counting and the members all love it here. Loyal friendly nice…..active<br /> Requirements? none at all…..like i said were just here to have more members and to have fun</p> <p>Any other questions? well come ask me cuase i got all day……</p> <p>if you want to know upgrades and such im sorry but i wont tell you….i like members who like it where they are under certain circumstances. therefore more loyal members…other than that you have to join to find out….but ill tell you that i treat my members with respect and i give them whatever they deserve they should get. Like the other day when someone help me pick a head band…i gave them 7 powerful potions… head band wasnt that great but we were still growing and we needed one….so yea…just a example how i treat my members</p> <p>Join? well i dont see why not</p> <p>personal rate? i cant say 5/5 cuase ill be bragging and i also know its not that great (but i try my hardest) so ill say 4/5 as my rate….</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>