<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Hikari Village is looking to go epic.</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254/hikari-village-is-looking-to-go-epic</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Hikari Village is looking to go epic.&quot; - Hikari is looking for members who will be active and follow us to the immortal realm.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:56:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254#post-297859</guid>
				<title>Re: Hikari Village is looking to go epic.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254/hikari-village-is-looking-to-go-epic#post-297859</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 05:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Pluveus</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>86000</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>We're a little low only eighteen, most of the time we get genin wanderers who go inactive. But we do have Burgerninja, I've got TPoG myself, we're going for tools of the trade next. what we need is people who are willing to be active and stick with us so that we can get an epic monument. That'll be the first upgrade at 40.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254#post-297545</guid>
				<title>Re: Hikari Village is looking to go epic.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254/hikari-village-is-looking-to-go-epic#post-297545</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 19:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>How many active members do you have right now? Do you have a BurgerNinja?</p> <p>These are important questions, as I am also looking to go Epic; I need the Power of Greass bloodline and an Epic Monument, though, of course, so I'm looking for a village that has at least the former and a fighting chance at working toward the latter. If this sounds like you, then perhaps we have something to discuss! I will be leaving my current village to snag Snakeman soon, so a prompt response is necessary.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254#post-293014</guid>
				<title>Hikari Village is looking to go epic.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-100254/hikari-village-is-looking-to-go-epic#post-293014</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 22:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Pluveus</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>86000</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hikari is a village that is going to seek the Immortal Realm, but we need more members, our next upgrade is tools of the trade so our members con go monochrome, but we need more members, and members who will stay with us. I'll post as new upgrades are acquired, plus you can always check the Hikari wiki once I post it.</p> <p>Also if you put in your intro that you joined after reading this, you'll start with better standing in the village.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>