<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Sharpening Stone</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Sharpening Stone&quot; - ash covered gem</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:31:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-422968</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-422968</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 07:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sasorichan</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Perfect explanation, thank you very much Seb. For note pages I'll start the Trade than.</p> <p>To the sharpening stone issue: first day after this bitching of mine, my alt found it togeather with two lenses and cobalt pole. 720 outskirts missions on the mission counter.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-422405</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-422405</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sebmagic</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>271527</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Larry and Haro are useful once you are in the Wasteland (2nd portion) and you have access to the Kaiju Monuments, which can drop ash-covered runes that can result in valuable runes. Those missions are 10 difficulty/10 success, so not hard to accomplish.</p> <p>Your best team to get drops if you have an adequate range is to use Haus, Good Boy, and Bones lvl 2, with the I Need This Jutsu taught by Good Boy.</p> <p>As for the odds of getting Sharpening stones, I have three extras laying around, after doing two scythes in S1, and prepare 2 Sharp Crystal for the scythe I will do in S3. I would say it's all a matter of luck. Pray the RNG that he will be merciful with you in the future, and good luck.</p> <p>For Note Page, your doing it wrong. To get them, you either use the Prize Wheel and hope for that drop there, while running the mission you are going for… Or, you use the note page you currently have, Bingo people with them (use Spot jutsu, Epic Dog Urination Technique for extra points), get 200 style points and unlock Hyuk. Do about 50 missions with Hyuk and you should have your 10 Note Pages. Good luck again.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-422384</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-422384</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 17:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sasorichan</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ive just checked it. With one of my 3 alts I am still without any find of sharpening stone. Other two are in inner wasteland already, but this one did 668 outskirts missions up to today, (most of it with ichi ramen) and still has no scythe to procede further. (but found 3 sham rocks. hurray :)</p> <p>So am I stupid or what? Did I omited some basic trick?!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-422369</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-422369</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 17:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sasorichan</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So what good are Larry and Haro for? You must to have them in the team when droping ash covered items?</p> <p>If yes I doubt their worth a bit.. or at least in Season 1. I, for one, would have a lot of difficulties to even succeed in outskirts missions without two or three ouskirts lev 2 allies in a team.</p> <hr /> <p>My drop score for sharpening stone is … a bit of suspence… 4 pieces per 1300+ ouskirts missions :) (I keep notes on monitor.. )</p> <p>Which seems to be the worst of all outskirts items. Its like one half or one third of drop chance of steel tile or cobalt pole. Ive found 7 pieces of first, 11 pieces of second during these missions. (most them i have run with ichi ramen, a lot of them with House on top of it. )</p> <p>but it gets worst after outskirts. To get Paper in later stage of wasteland storyline proved to be the and of a line for me - I planed to drop necessary note pages from "write a ninja essej" mission.. but after first week and two urinated drop I had to give it up. I felt like a moron :) I will either do the trade, or wait till wining it on the wheel.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-323192</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-323192</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 10:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>D0NC35</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>:((<br /> HOW MANY GEMS U NEED<br /> :((<br /> MY APPRAISAL TODAY :<br /> Appraise All Unlocked Items (10750 Ryo) &lt;== CHECKED<br /> Ash-Covered Shaft: 19 (Appraisal cost: 100 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Tile: 21 (Appraisal cost: 250 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Gem: 16 (Appraisal cost: 50 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Rare Shaft: 4 (Appraisal cost: 250 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Rare Ring: 11 (Appraisal cost: 100 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Coin: 8 (Appraisal cost: 25 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Ring: 7 (Appraisal cost: 50 Ryo)<br /> Ash-Covered Rare Coin: 3 (Appraisal cost: 50 Ryo)</p> <p>MY RESULT TODAY :<br /> You had 19 Ash-Covered Shafts appraised, and got:<br /> Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Silver Shaft, Copper Shaft, Silver Shaft, Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Cobalt Shaft, Copper Shaft, Silver Shaft, Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Silver Shaft, Copper Shaft, Copper Shaft, Silver Shaft &lt;== NO COBALT SHAFT :(<br /> You had 21 Ash-Covered Tiles appraised, and got:<br /> Wooden Tile, Ceramic Tile, Wooden Tile, Ceramic Tile, Wooden Tile, Wooden Tile, Ceramic Tile, Steel Tile, Ceramic Tile, Wooden Tile, Ceramic Tile, Wooden Tile, Wooden Tile, Steel Tile, Ceramic Tile, Wooden Tile, Wooden Tile, Ceramic Tile, Ceramic Tile, Wooden Tile, Wooden Tile<br /> You had 16 Ash-Covered Gems appraised, and got:<br /> Small Pearl, Small Emerald, Small Pearl, Sham Rock, Small Pearl, Small Pearl, Small Pearl, Small Emerald, Small Ruby, Small Ruby, Sharpening Stone, Small Pearl, Small Pearl, Small Ruby, Small Diamond, Small Pearl &lt;== ONLY 1 SHARPENING STONE :( ( WHAT EVER AT LEAST WITH NO SHAM ROCK)</p> <p>An opportunistic merchant watches you come in with tons of appraisals (fifty or more!). "You know, I can help you get a better deal on that, if you give me a cut..</p> <p>Larry joins you! &lt;== ( SAME AS HARO, NO OPPORTUNITY )</p> <p>(Increase Treasure prices by 5% of maximum value!)<br /> You had 4 Ash-Covered Rare Shafts appraised, and got:<br /> Silver Shaft, Silver Shaft, Silver Shaft, Silver Shaft &lt;== STILL NO COBALT SHAFT<br /> You had 11 Ash-Covered Rare Rings appraised, and got:<br /> Gold Ring, Gold Ring, Platinum Ring, Gold Ring, Copper Ring, Copper Ring, Copper Ring, Copper Ring, Copper Ring, Gold Ring, Gold Ring<br /> You had 8 Ash-Covered Coins appraised, and got:<br /> Crystal Lens, Copper Coin, Crystal Lens, Copper Coin, Silver Coin, Copper Coin, Copper Coin, Copper Coin<br /> You had 7 Ash-Covered Rings appraised, and got:<br /> Copper Ring, Gold Ring, Gold Ring, Platinum Ring, Copper Ring, Copper Ring, Gold Ring<br /> You had 3 Ash-Covered Rare Coins appraised, and got:<br /> Crystal Lens, Silver Coin, Crystal Lens</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-320194</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-320194</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 09:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>larry = appraise all ( 50+ ash stuff ) but dont increase my change when appraising. just same as Haro ( allready as my ally ).</p> <p>there is no other way to get sharpening stone beside that lucky gamble ? i only need 1 sharpening stone to continue my life in outskirt mission.</p> <p>ahhhhh…. sharpening stone not just common price but super rare common gamble appraising price; and u need more than 1 for many of wasteland items.</p> <p>who make this outskirt/wasteland mission so very2 hard to completed !!!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-319337</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-319337</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 13:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Larry is an ally you will get when you appraise 50 ash-covered stuff(gems/coins/rings/etc.) at once. No, he don't increase your chances when appraising.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-319241</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-319241</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 10:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>larry ?<br /> he can increase my possibility when appraising ?<br /> ehmm… ash gem + ash stuff ?? u mean ash-covered shaft ? ( i didnt find any ash-covered stuff article).<br /> tq</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-319142</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-319142</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2008 08:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>appraising is completely random for the most part.</p> <p>Also, while this is a bit of a pet peeve, even if you're spelling is mostly correct, it does nothing if your grammar is really, really bad.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-318328</guid>
				<title>Re: Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-318328</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 12:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's actually pretty common to get a Sharpening Stone. Just appraise some, maybe a lot. If you don't have Larry yet, try to appraise some ash-covered gems together with other ash-covered stuff. Might land you a Sharpening Stone.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031#post-318174</guid>
				<title>Sharpening Stone</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-108031/sharpening-stone#post-318174</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 08:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>how many gem u need for 1 sharpening stone succeded at 1 appraise ??<br /> many potion or wasteland mission need sharpening stone required, and what u got only treasure items :(<br /> tq</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>