<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Radiant Village</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-105344/radiant-village</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Radiant Village&quot; - The Best Village to grind ryo</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:56:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-105344#post-311269</guid>
				<title>Re: Radiant Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-105344/radiant-village#post-311269</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 23:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>lol another fire emblem village =D</p> <p>*Air five to you</p> <p>I usually try to personally invite people with fire emblem names to my village. good luck to you though :D</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-105344#post-309571</guid>
				<title>Radiant Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-105344/radiant-village#post-309571</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2008 21:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Legault</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>106882</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Are you tired of having that high tax on your mission earnings? Have you considered goin rogue, but it's too complicated to return to your village to blow all your money on the Party House? Then the Radiant Village, the Village Hidden on the Emblem, has the solution for you! With it's really low taxes you can grind your ryo and blow them at the Party House at the same time! All we ask of you is to collect every day, and donate some contracts every once a week. Our really low taxes are worth it! How low do you think they are? 35%? 25%? 20%? No, it's an astonishing 1%!!! Yes, 1%!!! So what are your waiting for? You don't have to stay permanently, just a couple of days until you're done with your grinding. Join the Radiant Village now!</p> <p>*The Radiant Village refrains from admitting deadbeats and gifficas. It also refrains from stating that it doesn't have the Party House… yet.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>