<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>guys i really need some help plz help :)</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-111958/guys-i-really-need-some-help-plz-help</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;guys i really need some help plz help :)&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:47:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-111958#post-330866</guid>
				<title>Re: guys i really need some help plz help :)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-111958/guys-i-really-need-some-help-plz-help#post-330866</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 19:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you loop your dou level is the only thing that loops so you will stay a lv 4 when you loop. As for when i did BN starting out, seeing how you are jonin, fries are useless at this point for the most part. Just use 1 greassy nugget a day and all the rest be greassy burgers, burgers help the most. also you will want to use ichi special ramen if you can so you get a replenishing supply of greassy items and more likely to find the other allies. But overall you kinda just got to hope you pass the missions for the two allies when the time comes and hope you pass. Once you have cici and lulu or suchan and lulu, things become much easier. but i found this strategy to be the most effective. Also as a season 1 i recommend that you dont start outskirts till season 2 till you're stronger and plus even in season 2 all you can really do is collect items for making the original 4 items needed to unlock wasteland. At any point good luck with whatever you choose!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-111958#post-330764</guid>
				<title>guys i really need some help plz help :)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-111958/guys-i-really-need-some-help-plz-help#post-330764</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 16:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mekkan</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>251188</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Im a Season 1 jounin and i have CICI but i cant get the allies and items from the missions i keep failing all the time, and i havent finnish the outskirt missions its to hard and i havent started with the trade, can someone give me some tips about THE BN and i have eaten alot of greassy stuff still it doesnt help and my doujutsu is level 4, but ill start get penalties soon, so if i just loop right now without gaining and finnishing the items and allies from theese missions what will i lose? should i just keep trying? will it be better if i complete evreything right now?</p> <p>plz help me :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>