<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]&quot; - Posted this in &#039;Missions,&#039; earlier...But I need to know which is easier to get in one week!</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:41:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-346224</guid>
				<title>Re: 4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-346224</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 03:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Chris</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Lulu's a boy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-344592</guid>
				<title>Re: 4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-344592</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 22:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Don't listen to the others. Do BurgerNinja. Wasteland will take you much longer because you'll have an impossible time getting the 10 note pages you need for The Paper.</p> <p>No trade =&gt; probably no Hyuk =&gt; no source of note pages except the party wheel and wasteland missions =&gt; average 3-4 pages per day AT BEST =&gt; 2-3 days AT LEAST before you can get the paper.</p> <p>And that's just getting one ally. Chunks can take a day or two, depending on how lucky you are. The "Eye of the Storm" mission takes at least 1 extra day because you'll need to use Floating on Air assuming you have it. If you don't have it, it could take longer than a day to be able to hang out with all three allies. Furthermore, making boots and a coat, and making sure you have at least a silver scythe could take a while.</p> <p>Point, Wasteland will take you much longer than you have time for. By Season 3 or 4, you'll be able to fly through it, but first Season Wasteland is just plain tough, let alone doing it in a rush.</p> <p>Furthermore, you don't actually have to complete BurgerNinja. You get the bloodline after the first "Shift Manager of Doom" special mission, and then use it to help you complete BurgerNinja. I'm not saying BurgerNinja is a good bet, but it is a better bet than Wasteland.</p> <p>I'm guessing you have 6 days left. Here's what you do.</p> <p>First off, Dumpster Dive EVERY DAY. That's in addition to this.</p> <p>Day 1: Get as many Greassy items as you can.</p> <p>Day 2, Part 1: Finish getting Greassy items. Hopefully, by now you have at least 2 burgers, 2 fries, and 1 soda. Ideally, you should have 2 nuggets as well.</p> <p>Day 2, Part 2: Start "Super Size" Special Mission. Down 2 Burgers, 2 Fries, and a soda. (Not in that order). If you have the nuggets (2) as well, down them too. Spend the rest of the day running BurgerNinja missions for AP. Also, using arena points, if you have them, for ingredient hunts (Dumpster Diving) isn't a bad idea.</p> <p>IF YOU ARE REDEYE OR WHITEEYE:</p> <p>Day 3: Finish Super Size. Spend the rest of the day running BurgerNinja missions for AP, greass, and ingredients. If you have the arena points, using them for more ingredient collections (Dumpster Diving) may be worth while too.</p> <p>Day 4: Eat some diet ramen. Down as many greassy items as you can. I'm assuming you're level 4 Dou by now.</p> <p>If you have 140 base appetite, your best option would be 2 nuggets, and 2 burgers, which would (with Cici) give you a 26% chance of passing Lulu or Su-chan's missions. If you're only level 3, you'll only have a 17% chance.</p> <p>If you have 170 base appetite (ie. your village has an Enormous buffet), your best option is 2 nuggets, 1 fries, and 2 burgers. If you're level 4, that gives you a 37% passing chance; if you're level 3, it'll be 26%.</p> <p>If you have 190 base appetite (ie. you have a hollow leg), your best option is 2 nuggets, 1 fries, and 3 burgers. If you're level 4, that gives you a 48% passing chance; if you're level 3, it'll be 37%.</p> <p>If you have 220 base appetite (you have both), your best option is 2 nuggets, 1 fries, and 4 burgers for a 58% or 48% chance depending on level.</p> <p>I'll assume you don't have a full 260 base appetite.</p> <p>Your objective now is to get either Lulu or Su-chan. (Lulu is better.) Ideally, you should be able to get both, but if you can't, that's okay. Depending on your level/appetite, it may take a few tries to just pass the mission, let alone complete it. There are 24 missions, and you're looking for 2 specific ones, meaning it could take about 180 stamina just to see either mission. If you have a lot of smoke bombs saved up for your Sannin run, I'd consider using them here.</p> <p>Day 5, Part 1: (If you already have both Lulu and Su-chan, ignore this step.) Regardless of which ally you got yesterday, missions should be much easier now. If you got Lulu, put her in your team BEFORE consuming any greass items. She and Cici make a very good team that reduced the appetite cost of all items by 10%. Unfortunately, Su-Chan offers no such bonus. Consume all the greass items you can and go after the other character.</p> <p>Day 5, Part 2: Complete "Shift Manager of DOOM." The hardest part of this is a Nin Diff: 14 Succ: 14 check, which can be a little tough, especially since you get no help from allies or jutsu (unless you have Value Meal (RE only)), but it shouldn't be too bad. If you fail, just keep running it until you pass. Complete it and you'll have your bloodline.</p> <p>Day 6: Sannin run.</p> <p>IF YOU ARE A LEGACY:</p> <p>Day 3: Finish Super Size. Consume an Ichi Special Ramen and then run more BurgerNinja missions. If you run into either "Grill Monkey" or "Sobbing," use Flying Thunder God Technique. Hope you get the ally. If not, oh well, there's not much that can be done.</p> <p>Day 4: If you got an Lulu on Day 3, then consume some Ichi Ramen Special and put her and Cici in your team. Consume as many greass items as possible, but no more than 2 nuggets and 1 fries. If you got Su-chan on Day 3, then do the same, but don't consume any fries. If you got neither, eat some diet ramen, then just consume 2 nuggets, 1 fries, and as many burgers as you can on that day.</p> <p>If you hit an ally mission that you don't already have, Flying Thunder God it. Hope you get the ally. If not, you have to pass it with stats, which is hard. Don't hesitate to use smoke bombs if you have them.</p> <p>Day 5: Complete "Shift Manager of DOOM." The hardest part of this is a Nin Diff: 14 Succ: 14 check, which can be a little tough, especially since you get no help from allies or jutsu, but it shouldn't be too bad. If you fail, just keep running it until you pass. Complete it and you'll have your bloodline.</p> <p>Day 6: Sannin Run.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-343992</guid>
				<title>Re: 4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-343992</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 22:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RazyVan</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>146953</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>OKay then make sure to be marked against it.<br /> And yes,BN allies are a pain to get.Even if you do find them quick there's Shift Manager of DOOM left whihc is an even bigger pain.Eye of the storm would be your best bet.Good luck.</p> <p>Next time,make sure to get bloodlines early on though.I've had my 4 for about 3 weeks now and I haven't hit my timer.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-343590</guid>
				<title>Re: 4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-343590</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 00:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Toumaru</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>220510</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Alright- Thanks for the advice, guys. ^_^<br /> Looks like I've got a few days of straight Wastelands ahead of me, then…</p> <p>Just when I thought I was done. xD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-343585</guid>
				<title>Re: 4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-343585</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 00:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mikelorus</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>231303</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Agreed with above.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-343573</guid>
				<title>Re: 4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-343573</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 23:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Persona</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Eye of the Storm is probably your best bet, getting the allies in BN is a major pain.</p> <p>Good Luck.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793#post-343513</guid>
				<title>4th Bloodline Choice [Urgent!]</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-115793/4th-bloodline-choice-urgent#post-343513</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 21:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Toumaru</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>220510</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Alright, so I have a week left before I start getting Stamina cuts due to my loop cap, and most of the preparations for my run are complete. The only big problem is that I only have 3 bloodlines, and need one more.</p> <p>As it stands, I cannot obtain the Trade due to my Loop Lock, and am already pissed off about losing the Note Pages I had saved up in orer to do so. So that's out.</p> <p>I have only just started Burgerninja- Have one edible item, don't have Cici yet…But Greass seems like the easier one to get, especially when…</p> <p>On the other hand, I could go for Eye of the Storm- However, I only unlocked the Inner Wastelands today.</p> <p>So which is more likely to happen?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>