<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Sannin Run</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114226/sannin-run</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Sannin Run&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:47:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114226#post-338747</guid>
				<title>Re: Sannin Run</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114226/sannin-run#post-338747</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 08:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>im gonna become sannin pretty soon, and im season 1 and can i do the mission "2&nbsp;b a master" right after i become a sannin? or will all of my xp be gone?</p> </blockquote> <p>2&nbsp;B A Master requires you to be #3 or higher in the Top 10 Rankings that are figured each day. So you'd have to do it the day after, provided you did in fact make Top 3. And, no, the XP doesn't disappear when you do the Sannin mission.</p> <blockquote> <p>and im gonna use obsessive insight and it will cost me 90 Chakra but some people says that it costs 50 Chakra in some villages, but my village already has all the upgrades so i dont get it, shouldnt the chakra cost decrease then?</p> </blockquote> <p>If you have all the upgrades, you should also have the Jutsu Enhancement Tower, which lets you pay JXP to lower the Chakra costs of an individual jutsu, all the way down to the minimum of 50%.</p> <blockquote> <p>why do people use super potion when you can take 2 silver elixirs instead of a super potion?</p> </blockquote> <p>Super Potions give you 100 Stamina. If you can get over 20K Ranking per mission, it becomes the better choice. Otherwise, stick with the Silver Elixirs.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114226#post-338540</guid>
				<title>Sannin Run</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-114226/sannin-run#post-338540</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2008 23:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mekkan</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>251188</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>im gonna become sannin pretty soon, and im season 1 and can i do the mission "2&nbsp;b a master" right after i become a sannin? or will all of my xp be gone? and im gonna use obsessive insight and it will cost me 90 Chakra but some people says that it costs 50 Chakra in some villages, but my village already has all the upgrades so i dont get it, shouldnt the chakra cost decrease then?<br /> and i will have around 900 stamina and i will use 6 silver elixirs but why do people use super potion when you can take 2 silver elixirs instead of a super potion? plz help a little:)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>