<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Shift Manager of DOOM Part 2</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-110044/shift-manager-of-doom-part-2</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Shift Manager of DOOM Part 2&quot; - I need some help with this mission.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-110044#post-324792</guid>
				<title>Re: Shift Manager of DOOM Part 2</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-110044/shift-manager-of-doom-part-2#post-324792</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 21:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Hitomi B</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>232256</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If I calculated correctly you only have 16 Range, which makes hard if not impossible to beat this mission. You should try to get more Range. Arena Items are very helpful, otherwise only Reglia or Polar Star would help since you haven't done Wasteland/Monochrome those items are not available.</p> <p>I would suggest go Monochrome first and if at all possible get some arena items, otherwise I don't see you beating this mission.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-110044#post-324439</guid>
				<title>Shift Manager of DOOM Part 2</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-110044/shift-manager-of-doom-part-2#post-324439</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 14:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Soiuku</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Here are the items I have and I will be a Jonin in a day or two; I am a special Jonin in Taijutsu. What should I do besides getting the Parts to beat this mission?</p> <p>Soul Glove<br /> Professor's Hat<br /> Blue Flower Hairpin<br /> Heck Butterfly<br /> Sword of the Reaper<br /> Shortbunny<br /> Monster Mask<br /> Glowing Mood Ring<br /> Ninja Puppet<br /> Ninja Dog<br /> Trench Knife<br /> Soul Glove<br /> Giant Fan<br /> Swallowtail Butterfly<br /> Basic Ninja Gear<br /> Utility Belt<br /> Silver Hairpin<br /> Sascha<br /> Letter of Marque<br /> Knapsack<br /> Goo Stabilization Recipe<br /> Substitute Soul Reaper Badge<br /> Glowing Mood Ring<br /> Pink Bouquet<br /> Ninja-Mas Star<br /> Soul Candy<br /> Chakra Armor<br /> Helper Pin<br /> RingEye<br /> Reaper Blood - Shikai<br /> Desert Robes<br /> Captain's Jacket<br /> Necklace of the First HoCage<br /> Counterfeit Permit<br /> 11DBHK's Birthday Hat<br /> Dog Collar<br /> K-Dog's Headband</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>