<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Tote help?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723/tote-help</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Tote help?&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:33:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723#post-362347</guid>
				<title>Re: Tote help?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723/tote-help#post-362347</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 08:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jolan</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"10 bingos will cost you 320 stamina."..assuming most of them are in my range.I'm level 81, have 22 base range + a Hacksaw, so I should be able to track ninja from level 68 to 94, but the trouble's in Grim Prediction, I'll have to use most of my stamina for that + the charging.I've settled on a team - Bones, Doughman and Blind Fury.Already have 8-9 Notes so that won't be a problem.Thanks for the tip about the Bingo Armour though, will definitely get one!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723#post-362107</guid>
				<title>Re: Tote help?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723/tote-help#post-362107</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 01:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's not that tough, just wait on the mission until a good number of your Tote targets are within your range. In the meantime, bash kaiju.</p> <p>If you really want to work it out, though, it's still pretty simple. 10 bingos will cost you 320 stamina. Save 30 or so for charging chakra, so 350.</p> <p>So, if you can hit 5 out of 10, then you'll need GP for 5 of them, an additional 500 stamina for 850, which isn't that hard. Assuming you start with ~400/day after bonuses and such. Then +60 (at least) for code. +100 for a super potion, another +100 for ramen. If you do your first bingo with wasteland allies, you can probably down another super potion, and if you wait to use your weekly +100 stamina for that day, that'll bring you to at least 700 stamina, 800 if you can down two potions. For the rest, NWW fights, Warrior Highs, putting in the code again later in the day, and of course, the video challenges.</p> <p>Edit: As far as a team goes, as long as you have doughman and a good number of note pages, you should be fine. Note anyone without note protection. Anyone who does have it, well you've got doughman for that. (They could be using tools of the trade, but I've never seen it used, and still, use a striking snake jutsu, and you'll probably oneshot them.</p> <p>Also, if you really want to make surey you don't screw up, you could buy a bingo armor on the day of your attempt. Would probably help if any of your targets are kaiju kage.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723#post-361496</guid>
				<title>Tote help?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-121723/tote-help#post-361496</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 10:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jolan</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>266710</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm able to hit at least 5 of my targets per day, including setting the spies and Grim Prediction.Should I wait fora day with targets I can bingo without GP (aka in my level range), or should I prepare just like for a Sannin run, with as many Stamina boosters as possible?<br /> Also, any tips on a team?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>