<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s&quot; - Getting the most out of attacking monsters</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:40:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366393</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366393</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 21:23:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You only need enough Range to hit the Difficulty of the Kaiju. But as long as you hit that Difficulty, anything beyond that is superflous.</p> <p>For every roll that hits the Difficulty, you deal 1 point of damage. Each Auto Success is also 1 point of damage. After that, multipliers take effect.</p> <p>But if the Kaiju has a difficulty of 10, a roll of 10 will do just as much damage as a roll of 30.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366392</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366392</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 21:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What some here seem to be forgetting is that most people who can do 350+ damage/hit aren't missing their rolls. They have strengths of +9 or +10, which means every roll is a success. They maximize rolls, not strength or range. (Hell, they already have 30+ range anyway.)</p> <p>If you want to do max damage, just put together as many damage modifiers and level boosters as you can. If your strength isn't high enough that you can be sure you'll hit with every roll, then maybe you should focus on finding what items you're missing that would give you a higher strength.</p> <p>By the way, if you want to maximize hits, Strawberry Sundae.</p> <p>If you want to maximize damage, Flutie/Sticky/Tubby, Chunks/Palmface/Threads, Terri 3. If you have the appropriate EotS ally, switch him in for Terri 3/Tubby (if monster is Tai or you want to keep counting coup).</p> <p>I usually use Strawberry3, Blindfury, and Terri 3 when I'm fighting monsters, but that's just my preference. In case you're wondering, I've averaged 143 damage per strike against the most recent monster with this set up. That's without Hard Corps or Juice bonuses. With those I could do 400+ damage per strike fairly easily.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366390</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366390</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 21:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MrRigger</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Exactly. If you're making all successes, you need to up your levels. If you missing rolls, add strength until all the rolls are hitting.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366387</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366387</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 21:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Soiuku</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Aye aye aye, this is why I try to not bother with Kaiju's except to get them out of the village. So it's number of levels, NOT how much you roll?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366381</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366381</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 21:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Soiuku, you have the complete WRONG idea of how Kaiju Damage is determined. It's purely based on the number of Successes you get, not how high the dice you roll are.</p> <p>You could have 1000 range, but 1 level will only do 1 point of damage regardless.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366374</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366374</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 21:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Soiuku</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm going to have to respectfully disagree; Level determines how many dice you roll, not how high. Range determines how many sides to the dice you're rolling, so in reality, I can still do more damage with less levels. Terri Twists are a good idea yes, but Strawberry Lv. 3 is only useful for stamina and in the end, you won't gain that much respective stamina and will only be able to hit the monster about one more time. Also, if you're planning on charging chakra then it'll negate his benefit and you'll still end up with the same amount of hits. Try getting full chakra before you fight it and use Chicken Ramen to get 1,100 chakra and will only have to charge once, maybe twice. ((The 1,100 is an estimate unless you're a Legacy))</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366283</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366283</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 19:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mikelorus</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>231303</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Above advice is not very great. Your items look like you can clear most, if not all the rolls, so in that case you want to keep your blood at bankai since levels determine your damage output. If you are trying to get a drop then have T3 for whatever kaiju it is. From there, you have to evaluate your position. Is there only one kaiju? Are you planning on bashing for an extended amount of time with the stamina you have?<br /> If there is only one and you plan to kill it and want the drop, then add T3 then the appropriate wasteland allies (the +8 lvl/range ones, and the +3lvl/+3 range ones). If you are making every single success flawlessly, then add the +10 lvl final wasteland ally.<br /> If your village is going on for extended periods of time, then you want a more generic team. This may not maximize your damage, but you will get the most out of your stamina. I would advise T3, Straw3, and blind fury.<br /> You can go above your tolerance to a full 12 twists for a lot more damage output as well.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366269</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366269</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 18:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Soiuku</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While range is clearly no problem for you, you might want to try summoning the correct summon for each monster; Slug for Nin, Snake for Gen, B.D. for Tai. As for your level problem, I suggest trying to get at least 3 referral points, so that you can get a Helper Pin: +1 Levels, and Coolness Badge: +2 Levels. If you have Cobra-Kai try activating it instead since a higher range means a higher probability of a higher attack. Be sure to use a Team that applies to it, regardless. About summons: USE THEM ANYWAYS, IT HELPS GET ROLLS HIGHER AND HIGHER. ((Sorry for flaming)) Anyways, you're going to want as high of a range as you can get since even 10 rolls of 10 is still 100 whereas 10 rolls of 14 is 140 so range counts a lot more, and you're well set with the level factor.</p> <p>Use these teams:</p> <p>Tai: Terri Lv.3, Bruce Jr. Level 2, &amp; Emosuke Level 3.</p> <p>Gen: Trapchan &amp; Z-Dog OR Flutie Level 2, Trapchan, &amp; Threads.</p> <p>Nin: Venus, Sticky Level 2, &amp; Yuri Level 2.</p> <p>I really hope I was of some help.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366095</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366095</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Warchariot</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sure if that'll help, I tend to have a problem more with the actual levels than range, I tend to use both wasteland allies and terri giving my 14 levels and plenty of range for anything I have to fight, don't tend to use summons for kaju fighting since I don't have probs with the range. Here's my item list</p> <p>Professor's Hat<br /> Heck Butterfly<br /> Ninja Dog<br /> Soul Glove<br /> Ninja Puppet<br /> Dog Collar<br /> Swallowtail Butterfly<br /> Sword of the Reaper<br /> Monster Mask<br /> Chakra Armor<br /> Silver Hairpin<br /> Thrill of Battle<br /> Giant Fan<br /> Warbound<br /> Goo Stabilization Recipe<br /> Basic Ninja Gear<br /> Trench Knife<br /> Desert Robes<br /> Streamlined Focus<br /> Sascha<br /> RingEye<br /> 11DBHK's Birthday Hat<br /> Pinchy Claw<br /> Soul Candy<br /> Dark Band<br /> Substitute Soul Reaper Badge<br /> Sannin's Premium<br /> Training Sash<br /> Reaper Blood - Bankai<br /> Sevens Trophy<br /> The Note<br /> Awesome Pants<br /> Captain's Jacket<br /> Storm's Path<br /> Shortbunny<br /> The Cote<br /> Officer's Pay<br /> Utility Belt<br /> Knapsack<br /> Hall Pass<br /> Hollow Leg<br /> Blue Flower Hairpin<br /> Letter of Marque<br /> Creepy Love Letter<br /> Pink Hair Dye<br /> Codec<br /> K-Dog's Headband<br /> Stealth Suit<br /> Love Love Paradise<br /> Golden Star of Wisdom<br /> Golden Collar of Power<br /> Late-Night Snack<br /> Shiny Belt<br /> Firebrand<br /> Granola Camouflage<br /> Regalia<br /> Fruits Basket<br /> Catgirl Entourage<br /> Pokerballs<br /> Soul of Steel<br /> Perfect Hair<br /> Lab Coat<br /> Persocom<br /> Hacksaw<br /> Poisoned Daggers<br /> Groupies<br /> Money Printer<br /> Magical Wand<br /> Plug Suit<br /> Tire Tracks<br /> Bear Coat<br /> Basic Blueprints<br /> Ancient Blueprints<br /> Cowl of the Second HoCage<br /> Pistol of Repeating<br /> Solid Shades<br /> Dustcloak of Sneaking<br /> Scythe of Razing<br /> Boots of Walking<br /> Destiny Fulfilled<br /> Wheel of Cheese<br /> Knightmare Frame<br /> Big Mouth</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366094</guid>
				<title>Re: Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366094</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 14:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Soiuku</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Can I get your full permanent items list? You should calculate in range, teams, summon(s) being used, and all items available as well as blood-state.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306#post-366088</guid>
				<title>Max damamge to Kaju&#039;s</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-123306/max-damamge-to-kaju-s#post-366088</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 14:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Warchariot</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I thought i'd ask here as well, some people in my village are able to do around 350 damage to a kaju in a single hit and i'm way off that, so I thought i'd try and compile a list, and see if there is something huge that I am missing, I currently have;</p> <p>Poisoned daggers<br /> Groupies<br /> I'm a (27/27/27) sannin<br /> Bring Down the House Jutsu<br /> Terri Twist's (my current tolerance is 4)</p> <p>I also have all the added stamina for attacking monsters though this does no good since i'm looking to do more damage per attack, so labs coats, tire tracks, tsukiballs and strawberry level 3, (missing the arena items). Is there anything i'm missing so I could further maximise my damage?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>