<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>only for heroes... heros village is recrueting</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401/only-for-heroes-heros-village-is-recrueting</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;only for heroes... heros village is recrueting&quot; - i need people who loves to join in building something.. i would love to use your experience in building the best village in the game.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:55:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401#post-395355</guid>
				<title>Re: only for heroes... heros village is recrueting</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401/only-for-heroes-heros-village-is-recrueting#post-395355</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 16:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Swan21</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>93166</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Indeed, keeping a low tax rate is good(2% is impossible unless you are only planning to have 2 villagers), but you really should have had a few more commitments before initially making the village.</p> <p>P.S. "you will help in taking the decision, (in real life i am a manager ;) .. you will provide your experience, and we will help other new players in this game" That is something that many villages already do, a lot of kages ask their villagers which upgrade they want and to make some decisions for the village. Also, you may need new players before you can get any experienced players to join. You should aim for getting new players into your village until it is firmly secure in members before trying to get many experienced players.</p> <p>Good luck, but try to get some commitments from other places as well(another game you play, real life, sites you hang out at), not just the BvS sites.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401#post-392878</guid>
				<title>Re: only for heroes... heros village is recrueting</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401/only-for-heroes-heros-village-is-recrueting#post-392878</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 15:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Na77ool</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>hahahahhaa man.. i am gonna keep my word.. since so far it is empty :s</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401#post-392101</guid>
				<title>Re: only for heroes... heros village is recrueting</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401/only-for-heroes-heros-village-is-recrueting#post-392101</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 17:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sebmagic</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Just for your information, the minimum tax rate is the number of person in your village. So the more you get in, the higher the taxes get. Still, what your offering to all newcomers is low taxes for a while.</p> <p>Good luck with your village.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401#post-391987</guid>
				<title>Re: only for heroes... heros village is recrueting</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401/only-for-heroes-heros-village-is-recrueting#post-391987</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 14:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Na77ool</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Guys.. the tax rate will be 2% for the next 10 days :) … and afterwards, i will consult with the villagers on a fair tax rate.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401#post-391986</guid>
				<title>only for heroes... heros village is recrueting</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-132401/only-for-heroes-heros-village-is-recrueting#post-391986</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 14:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Na77ool</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>guys.. in other villages.. you are either a villager or a leader … but in heros village.. you will help in taking the decision, (in real life i am a manager ;) .. you will provide your experience, and we will help other new players in this game, help me in building the best village in this game, and make this village yours.</p> <p>join every one :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>