<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;The Eleven-Tailed Fox - The Demon Within&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;The Eleven-Tailed Fox - The Demon Within&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:57:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-1808551</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-1808551</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 19:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>hexhex</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1666574</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>well, there is the option of instead of preparing 10 days for a single fight&#8230; you fight eleven tails twice per day. Or if you're feeling really crazy, you summon 11's on Day 1, use 2-days-favor, wait until after dayroll, use another two days favor, then proceed to buy the Mahjong life and try to kick its ass. If you fail, you fight two more that day.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-1388725</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-1388725</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 10:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You're correct, it's 12% base, as it starts out at 11 days alive (1% base + 1 per day). As for how many days, if you use the extra life favor the first day, each day you add 1 day alive, but remove 2 days from the favor&#8230;.so&#8230;.11 favors plus the extra life one, 12 favors, if I'm not mistaken.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-1388602</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-1388602</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 05:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Becca</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Would one of you mind putting up the death chance for the Eleven Tails? Because I don't know where some of you got the base 9% percent chance, as mine started off at 12% and ramped up to 19% (1% drop due to perms, but I didn't have Bullet Time).</p> <p>Also, for some of us that despise MJ/can't-win-even-with-scripts, any guesses on how many favors it'd take without MJ's Zawa-Zawa?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-999249</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-999249</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 22:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>cat fight over the rng?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-971019</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-971019</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 13:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I agree with this statement, this is 100% about me ^_^ U know, this is ma all-through-game strategy, but tactic changes time to time for different goals :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-970906</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-970906</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 08:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>20 points is useful sometimes, but not always. :3 I've put off doing it for the past while myself simply because I've been doing other stuff. :3 There's no need to rush through the game to get to the end and twiddle your thumbs waiting for new stuff to come out. Doing it at an average pace gets you there quicker than you'd think.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-969037</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-969037</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 11:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Oh… U really understand my words almost in opposite way… Fuh… OOOOKEY… I'll use simple constructions. I reminded of basics just 'cuz they need TIME! MOST wanna kill 11TF and then revenge-demon ASAP for AWESOME POINTS(20.SECRET TROPHY.). Player SHOULD KILL 11TF BEFORE FESTIVAL. TIME IS ALL. THAT IS.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-968671</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-968671</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 22:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's not that they have no patience (though I'm sure there are those who don't) but that the entire concept of Mahjong is just something they can't quite wrap their heads around, or simply don't have the -time- to do so more often than not. Heck, I only use the script to give me a free "hit this button to discard your selection/cancel pon/kan/chis without clicking". Secondly, anyone who gets to the 11TF SHOULD KNOW that you can't fight two Phases at once, because it's the end of the content. It's basic knowledge. Same with curing corruption, as it's REQUIRED to be able to fight another Phase- Something that you'd have had to have done personally at least five times over (since you can buy four Lost Weapons, though not R00t rank). Same with hacking et al for the 11TR. Posting basic Phase-fighting information on the 11TF page is silly. That's what the R00t Guide is for (even if it's not). Seriously, someone needs to fix the lack of Phases in that guide. &gt;.o Just because you don't rush to do all "new" content as fast as you possibly can doesn't make you a loser. Waiting can be bad for you, certainly, but just because something CAN be doesn't mean it ALWAYS is.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-967753</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-967753</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 16:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Script isn't a cure. It's a weapon. "silly goose"s even have no patient to read all short majongh rules re-written by McM for BvS players.(=&gt;playing MJ badly=&gt;have few MJXP=&gt;spending 2 more days and trying to find patience for Demon-fighting, trying to get lifes amount for 3 hits) I'm not even talking about wise using of script(btw, I'm not using it anymore after compleating Majongh) Count one more fact: 11th day is NEAR! And I also wanna Kimono of Shadows for PW and peoples SHOULD KNOW about the way to kill root-boss in 9 days, 'cuz 1st, u can't fight 2 phases at one moment, 2nd, u should cure after winning-corruption, 3rd, u should prepare (at least re-hack when previous hack-timers will go down, and farm bits/core if needed) for this Revenge-fight, and so on. And if u couldn't - wait ONE MORE MONTH(!) for this summon. SO:if u are not starting boss - fight in about 20 next days after festival - u are complete looser (else u are risky and lucky and will kill Demon with more than 1% basic DC). I strongly suggest a way doing this faster. As Russian proverb says: Two the worst things in the World are to wait and to running down :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-967672</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-967672</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 14:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You aren't accounting for any of the cheats, though. And there are at least a few worth buying. Myself, i bought them all; But to go without any of them would be a severe test of patience, and I'm sure that the majority of people that do play don't play fair, especially since it seems <a href="http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/TheComputerIsACheatingBastard">The Computer Is A Cheating Bastard</a>. I'm well aware that Sue and K-Dog give awesome bonuses- as I said, I've beaten MJ entirely. The problem with MJ is that those games stall you out in relatively long sessions where you're at the whim of the code, sometimes taking half an hour or more. It's very time intensive unless you just use the script, but as it's designed just to go for reach as quickly as it can, ignoring discarding potentially dangerous tiles, it isn't useful past say Lil Rack in character battles at most, and about Normal otherwise. From my understanding of what people have said about Temple Pro, only the people that actually like it and play it outside BvS ever bother playing it more than a few times, before giving it up as hopeless. There's also the built-in frustration of constantly failing against the same character battle over and over and over again. Personally, I think McM shouldn't have developed the playstyles of each enemy to be representative of one of the three types of play, as it makes it very hard to win. Anyways, I digress. I've been ranting. &gt;.&gt;</p> <p>Not everyone can successfully beat the higher ranked MJ games where you actually get decent points for second-third as well, making easy victories in lower difficulties the norm. Zawa Zawa = poor use of resources against the Eleven Tailed Fox, plain and simple. You can wait two more days and spend two more favours to get the same effect, that doesn't go away at dayroll in case for whatever reason you just didn't have the stamina to defeat him. There is no benefit to doing it two days earlier unless you're a silly goose who ended up waiting until the second of the month to summon it, and you want to unlock the 11TR. Even then, simply being patient and waiting another month is the better choice, as Reach is almost mandatory for high-rank WKai. A good majority of the people in the PHC when asked would rather deal with not getting Reach rather than playing MJ some more. Ask them yourself sometime.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-966838</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-966838</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 12:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Today is 9th day:</p> <p>"…You have completed R00t, as 1056 have before you! Congratulations!…" :)</p> <p>P.S. I got 3rd life from summon just to be safe :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-966012</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-966012</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 13:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Wiki quote:<br /> Level MJXP to next Unlocks<br /> 1 4,000 Super Easy and Easy Difficulty<br /> 2 7,000<br /> 3 10,000 Medium Difficulty / Lil' Rack Character Battle<br /> 4 13,000<br /> 5 16,000 Medium Hard Difficulty / TACOS Character Battle<br /> 6 19,000<br /> 7 22,000 Hard Difficulty / Sue Lvl. 2 Character Battle<br /> 8 25,000<br /> 9 28,000 K-Dog Lvl. 2 Character Battle<br /> 10 31,000<br /> 11 34,000 Temple Pro Difficulty / Triple H Lvl. 2 Character Battle</p> <p>4+7+10+13+16+19+22+25+28+31=175 k MJXP :)<br /> So if u are not MJ-cheater u might get some of Zawa Zawas and Reaches while getting levels to open new allies :)<br /> Sue 2 and K-dog 2 are AWESOME enemies that gives awesome bonuses when they became ur friends :)<br /> And difficulties add to game more interests :)<br /> On a side note about MJXP farming after getting ALL majongh trophies: 2 games(but u can MORE, right?) a day (cheap in ryo, right?) with Steel Set and Reach Script(helps to be a bit more attentive) earn 2-5 k MJXP a day(not 1st place also earn MJXP, I prefer TemplePro and 2nd-3rd places, but u can train for 1st-2nd with a bit lower difficult) =&gt; in a week with a tail (= a bit more than a week) u are waiting the demon to be weaker, u easy can earn Zawa Zawa even if u've cheated hard during LONG-MAJONG-WAY… :)<br /> P.S. I have no Lightning Draw :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-965867</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-965867</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've completed all of MJ as well, and I certainly do not have 150-200K MJXP. I have all of 50K at the end of MJ. Not only that, but most people (going by a study of public opinion in village, multivillage, and PH chats) really don't like MJ and/or don't play it very well, especially at the major wall of Sue2 (with her unseeable discards) and K-Dog2 (11K points at start is HATE). Expecting someone to be at or near the end of MJ instead of simply having farmed up another easy two favours to spend (and saving that MJXP for Reach for Wkai especially) is just silly. Spending two more days to prep without using such a heavy, luck-based, consumable (Yes there's skill to MJ, but it's mostly in the luck of the draw and discards, since you can't bluff AI) is far more worth it. Besides, you can use the extra days as grind days.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-964962</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-964962</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While I've done Majong (from 1st battle to finishing TrippleH lvl2) I've got 150-200 MJXP. +While u are fighting with the phase u can't fight usual phases or kaiju so most wanna do this faster. On other side u spend time for farming favours and with a bit of prepare (hack on 8th day, buy all at fields bonuses on 9th day) demon dies on 9th day.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-964952</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-964952</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What you're forgetting is that Zawa Zawa ends at dayroll. At 30K MJXP, that's a very expensive life, while the cost of two favours to get the stays-through-dayroll extra life and reducing it down to 0% extra death chance brings it to a total of 11 favours, Zawa Zawa is best saved for multiple Phases in one day, not for anything else.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-964173</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-964173</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 14:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>1st day: summoned big-boss and used fovour - he has 9% (losed 2%) base and 1 favours total used<br /> 2nd: 8%, 2 (gained 1&nbsp;% and losed 2%)<br /> 3rd: 7%, 3<br /> 4th: 6%, 4<br /> 5th: 5%, 5<br /> 6th: 4%, 6<br /> 7th: 3%, 7<br /> 8th: 2%, 8<br /> 9th: 1%, 9 fovours in total need to get the lowest DC at this phase<br /> Then lives: 1 basic + 1 legacy + 1 zawa zawa + 1 offline romance + 1 from twiling gardian = 5 in total = 3 hits of kaiju to kill player. If to use +1 life favour there will be STILL 3 HITS!</p> <p>SO: at this page should be written that u need 9 favours to win him safely, not 11 as written now. :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-661395</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-661395</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 06:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay, let's take this from the top, and make it as simple as I can:</p> <p>Lycoris is not the cost you pay to start fighting the 11-Tailed.<br /> Lycoris is the item you have to give up in order to get Eleven Tails.<br /> It's the exact same process as giving up a Polar Star in order to get a Holy Spur, except you get Lycoris back immediately afterwards.</p> <p>11-Tailed Revenge works in the same way, only you have to 'give up' Eleven Tails to get Kimono of Shadows.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-661362</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-661362</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2009 04:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Then I wonder why it bothers listing the item cost for either, seeing as how they're the only two phases that I know of that take an item to drain, rather than stamina/ryo to fight. Maybe that's so you *have* to have the item involved first?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-661125</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-661125</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 18:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DemonDream</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>121940</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>In order to avoid confusion, You do not lose the items for draining either of these phases. It says cost, but it does not take the item from you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-661043</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-661043</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Lycoris (and Eleven Tails for Revenge) is the cost for DRAINING, not FIGHTING.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-660805</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-660805</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 08:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I understand that part. What I was referring to is that the "cost" for fighting the 11's is a Lycoris (for original) or an Eleven Tails, according to the guide. Would you lose that permanent item, not getting it back, should you lose to the phase? It only mentions you getting the item back in the defeat messages…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-660458</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-660458</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The penalty for losing to ANY phase is the same: Corruption. None of the 11s are any different.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915#post-660253</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-157915/the-eleven-tailed-fox-the-demon-within#post-660253</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 08:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So, if the Lycoris is the cost for draining the phase, but you get one back for beating it…what if you lose your last life to it? Likewise, if you lose to the Eleven Tails Revenge, do you have to fight the original phase again, to get your Eleven Tails item again, so you can face Revenge again?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>