<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Post Recode Changes</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-163754/post-recode-changes</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Post Recode Changes&quot; - Bvs turned upside down</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:19:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-163754#post-514221</guid>
				<title>Re: Post Recode Changes</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-163754/post-recode-changes#post-514221</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 08:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>North</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>132728</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I don't find it relevant to add that kind of information. That is more Trivia than usefull information. My point of view on a wiki is that it should provide the information as concise as posible. Along with that, the information should be easily reachable.</p> <p>Adding the old information is useless. Who knew about it and forgot it, good for them. They can get back on track fast enough. For the ones who never knew of what was before, the information is useless.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-163754#post-513112</guid>
				<title>Post Recode Changes</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-163754/post-recode-changes#post-513112</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 16:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I came back after taking a break for a few months. I left immediately before the recode and coming back I was lost and confused for a good few days. I've assimilated once again and can handle myself (but the day after I got back I tried to do my Sannin run, I had no idea what I was doing and none of the numbers were adding up -.- ). Obviously not all the pages have been updated with the changes post recode yet (Xp Guide) but those that have were changed only in the details that were affected by the recode with no evidence that there was anything different before.</p> <p>I think that for sake of ease of transition and historic reasons as well I suppose, as changes are made like that a tiny note could be added mentioning this particular part of the game used to be significantly (or slightly as the case may be) different before the recode and perhaps a brief summary of how things changed.</p> <p>Of course this action isn't necessary with regular everyday updates, balance changes, and tweaks in the game, but the changes after the recode were quite massive and I think this might help clarify a bit. I also think it's a shame that there is no evidence of majestic components of the game's past like the [classic] arena ever existing (unless you go into the page history but most people won't bother).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>