<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Z-points and how u spend them for better performance in z maps</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538/z-points-and-how-u-spend-them-for-better-performance-in-z-ma</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Z-points and how u spend them for better performance in z maps&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:08:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538#post-532054</guid>
				<title>Re: Z-points and how u spend them for better performance in z maps</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538/z-points-and-how-u-spend-them-for-better-performance-in-z-ma#post-532054</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 18:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Unless you have a plan (usually Medic or Engineer) for your first lvl 5, max out Speedy. It's the only skill that is useful in just about every situation.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538#post-532009</guid>
				<title>Re: Z-points and how u spend them for better performance in z maps</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538/z-points-and-how-u-spend-them-for-better-performance-in-z-ma#post-532009</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 17:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Andrew</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It really depends. Good villages will be organized and have roles for everyone.</p> <p>Typically the roles break down like this:</p> <p>1. Attackers. Groups of Four people that head for the Arms Depot, then begin closing and sealing Gates/rifts. Depending on the size of village and map you may have multiple groups. Mine has Two. Good Skills: Speedy, Immune, Healthy, Thorough, Cleave, Sniper.</p> <p>2. Support. A few people need to be support. These guys run all around healing people, building bunkers/hospitals, and usually also pinging the Map. Good Skills: Medic, Engineer, Runner, Gardener, Thorough, Speedy.</p> <p>3. Defenders. A few people that run along right where the Zombja wave is coming in and keep the Zombjas from getting to the village while the gates are being closed. They do NOT need to stick close to the village, they need to stay around the oncoming Wave. You need just enough Ninjas to keep the wave back, too many seriously hampers their Z Points. Good skills: Healthy, Thorough, Engineer (for pinging and bunkers), Gardener (mines can help keep Zs and Zettas back), Speedy</p> <p>4. Clearers. These guys are mid game roles. At the beginning they help clear a path to the Gates and Rifts, but once a path has been made, they should run around and start clearing the middle reaches. Eventually they should meet up with the Defenders and push the line of Defense Way back. This Role is a semi-role and is often merged with Support. Good Skills: Thorough, Speedy, Cleave, Medic, Engineer (for pings), Immune, Healthy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538#post-516013</guid>
				<title>Re: Z-points and how u spend them for better performance in z maps</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538/z-points-and-how-u-spend-them-for-better-performance-in-z-ma#post-516013</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 04:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you ask me, i would say immune 4 then engineer 5 because the ability to build a hospital helps a lot in the harder maps.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538#post-515949</guid>
				<title>Z-points and how u spend them for better performance in z maps</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-164538/z-points-and-how-u-spend-them-for-better-performance-in-z-ma#post-515949</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 03:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yaray</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>258401</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>so i was wondering where everyone has spent their z points on… so far this are my stats:</p> <p>Your Skills:<br /> Medic: 1 Sniper: 4 Speedy: 5 Immune: 3 Healthy: 2 Thorough: 1 Careful: 1 Cleave: 3</p> <p>any suggestions on what to upgrade next ???</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>