<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>So, referral question...</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-173167/so-referral-question</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;So, referral question...&quot; - Can I use my desktop computer for a new character?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-173167#post-550594</guid>
				<title>Re: So, referral question...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-173167/so-referral-question#post-550594</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 19:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Faroth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>298298</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If the computer in question is on the same network you most likely have the same IP address externally to the Internet. Because of this you won't get any referral points for any new alts. However you are allowed to make 3 characters so there's nothing stopping you from playing one of each bloodline at the same time.</p> <p>If you for some reason have several unique IP's you might get referrals but there is supposedly some other method the system uses to spot cheating. Though I doubt you'll get smashed with the Banhammer for it you might get a warning if you do try it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-173167#post-550514</guid>
				<title>So, referral question...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-173167/so-referral-question#post-550514</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2009 17:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Davinator</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>352682</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So, the way I work, I have multiple desktops at home with which I am free to do with as I please. Question is, am I gonna' get a big old BANHAMMER to the face if I create an account on one of these computers to try different stuff out and get a referral point? Nothing IP related, just wondered if 11DBHK would be watching me. Thanks in advance! (Also, first post WOOO)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>