<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Arena help</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234/arena-help</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Arena help&quot; - Probably would have made a shadow reference, but unsure ont eh cursing policy ^^</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:09:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234#post-602110</guid>
				<title>Re: Arena help</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234/arena-help#post-602110</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 00:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sannin does not mean that they are stronger, sannin is just a title you attain at lv.60+. A lv. 87 Jonin can easily be stronger than a lv. 63 Sannin. Even if their levels are the same, the jonin may have multiple monster drops and have higher strength than the opposing sannin. I just recommend attaining as many strength, range, and level items that you can get. Using your awesome on the levels and possibly range abilities could prove helpful.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234#post-601502</guid>
				<title>Re: Arena help</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234/arena-help#post-601502</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 12:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Novaix</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>333449</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have doughman and warrior of power, but I also need help with the dark hour, as aforementioned. And I doubt that the majority of sannin are weaker than the strongest jonin.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234#post-600330</guid>
				<title>Re: Arena help</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234/arena-help#post-600330</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 16:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Xeserex</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>267044</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd recommend not fighting during the Dark Hours, since you'll easily be fighting ninja alot higher level than you. Start saving your money for one big push. Also, if you over-level as a Jonin, you'll have good shot at winning 15+ .</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234#post-600175</guid>
				<title>Re: Arena help</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234/arena-help#post-600175</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 12:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Faroth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>298298</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd recommend you to gain as many levels as you can and since your village has an Epic Monument to go Sannin as well. As it is there are a lot of strong S2 Jonin+ around and it's very unlikely that you'll face 15 that you can beat without buying far too many fights. This will also seriously help you with the Dark hour fights, wait with fighting during those times until you've gotten Warrior of Power.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234#post-600134</guid>
				<title>Arena help</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-186234/arena-help#post-600134</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 10:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Novaix</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>333449</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm S2 Jonin, with a fair amount of permanents. I need doughman (and also seriously after the warrior of… whiteeye l33tness.) for monochrome, does anyone have advice for the arena? I can never seem to win enough fights to get close to the 15, and can never win enough dark hour fights to keep my moon above new moon waning. Apart from using emergency rations (Takes kinda long to farm them…) what advice does anyone have?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>