<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>getting an assignment as a village leader</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-187175/getting-an-assignment-as-a-village-leader</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;getting an assignment as a village leader&quot; - How can I be a leader while there is already a leader?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:07:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-187175#post-604125</guid>
				<title>Re: getting an assignment as a village leader</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-187175/getting-an-assignment-as-a-village-leader#post-604125</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 12:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>When a kage idles out, leadership is transferred to the character who has been in the village the longest. The only way for you to get leadership is to not leave the village (which sends you to the bottom of the list) and wait for your turn.</p> <p>Or if you have The Five Rings and some amount of Ryo that escapes me, you can leave and form your own village.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-187175#post-603726</guid>
				<title>getting an assignment as a village leader</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-187175/getting-an-assignment-as-a-village-leader#post-603726</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 21:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lorjena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>387016</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Since July, my village doomed because the leader, who is responsible for repairing upgrades (helping for repair as a normal member doesn't help), planning to invade and making announcement for everybody to know what to do, is idle since then. No one of us villagers have been in contact with him, and the assignment changes every month because the ones being the "new" leader don't do anything and afterwards, all of these replacements are also going idle or leave the village. Of course, I can leave too, but it's a pity for my village and now I'm feeling responsible. Because "no one cares", I want to be the leader (without permission of the leader because he's idle),<br /> so how can I become a leader?</p> <p>Thanks in advance.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>