<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Manetheren has 5 open spots</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-190941/manetheren-has-5-open-spots</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Manetheren has 5 open spots&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:35:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-190941#post-614795</guid>
				<title>Manetheren has 5 open spots</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-190941/manetheren-has-5-open-spots#post-614795</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 14:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rand</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is what I offer:</p> <p>*We are a Tier 3 Immortal Realm with almost all Upgrades. (today it's 149 I believe)</p> <p>*We are summoning kaiju every single day, and we switch between Majors and Minor kaijus (1 major - 2 minors - 1 major - 2 minors aso), and Terri 3 users have very good chances at getting winning the minor drops, since a good many players of Manetheren have a full set already. Also we have a slayer-list as a means of distributing the leader's spare drop (I don't keep any of them for myself) and a fair competition that regulates the distribution of Demon Spirits.</p> <p>*We are doing hard Zombja maps within 3 days or less and you get 5 Z-rewards for participating in a map.</p> <p>*We are among the game's official Top 10 villages nearly every day.</p> <p>*We have Science 4 active every time a player requests it.</p> <p>Now here is what this is about:</p> <p>5 of my players have suddenly stopped playing and I have open spots to be filled. Everyone is welcome! I do not care whether you are a strong veteran of Billy, or new to the game and inexperienced.<br /> The only 3 things I care about are 1) that you <strong>do your village actions every day</strong>, 2) that you are sure you want to keep on playing BvS for some time at least, and 3) that you are not talking rude or in a 'lol ur haz mine noze'-kind of way; it hurts my eyes to read that kind of language.</p> <p>Now, if you are looking for a good village with a nice and helpful community, please apply to Manetheren and I'll let you in ASAP.</p> <p>Hope to see you soon^^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>