<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>bloodlines</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880/bloodlines</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;bloodlines&quot; - what blodd line is easy to get</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:09:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880#post-633516</guid>
				<title>Re: bloodlines</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880/bloodlines#post-633516</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 04:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>zeroshadowragnarok</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>96760</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While what Faroth said is true about The Trade, you should try to get the others as well. do them as jonin for the additional range boost.</p> <p>List of Bloodlines:<br /> The Trade: <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:thetrade">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:thetrade</a><br /> Eye of the Storm: <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:wasteland">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:wasteland</a><br /> The Power of Greass: <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:burgerninja">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:burgerninja</a><br /> Mister Roboto: Get first in a Robo FIGHTO tourney<br /> Mysterious Power Bloodline: get 50 loyality points<br /> Silver-Eye: Get 10 Claymore activations during invasions.</p> <p>Eye of the Storm, The Power of Greass, and Mysterious Power Bloodline i know for a fact loop. Silver-Eye I'm not sure but i heard that it does.</p> <p>also I've been known to give advice in game such as comparing item lists with people so they know what they need like maybe a few more range/levels might be helpful for you. (player name: Ryden)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880#post-633503</guid>
				<title>Re: bloodlines</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880/bloodlines#post-633503</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 03:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Faroth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>298298</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Try going for The Trade. Bingo some people with Note-pages and the jutsu Epic Dog Urination Technique. That will give you Hyuk and then just keep him in your team and collect apples and notes before doing the quest (requires bingoing a village leader).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880#post-633210</guid>
				<title>bloodlines</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-196880/bloodlines#post-633210</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 20:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>suke</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>314626</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm season 2 right now and a special jonin in order to become a jonin for season 2+ you need 3 bloodlines. so far i have 2 reaper and legacy, but i can't get a third. i tried to get greass and waste land, but i was getting no where with greass. On the first part of the wasteland quest i'm always on success short. What bloodline is the easiest to get. I've been training for a while, and 5 more levels and i'll be ready for sanin. So what should i do and which bloodling is easiest to get.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>