<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;PizzaWitch&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;PizzaWitch&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:10:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1329728</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1329728</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 23:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That's wrong. You only lose it the first time. You need to HAVE one every time, but it only destroys one the first time you do it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1327521</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1327521</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 20:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Becca</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Need to update the bit about the Polar Star. You don't just lose it the 1st time you go through the Antidote/HARO quest, but every time you do the quest each loop through. I'm coming up on my third run through (I'm bored at the moment, so why not?) and it nabbed yet another Polar Star from me. I keep a running checklist of all my perms, which is how I remember.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1140812</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1140812</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>..Considering that you're a member, you have Wiki editting rights. Could have fixed it yourself. &gt;_&gt;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1140398</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1140398</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 23:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Dogfight cannot be done. Reason: Karen IS a requirement. Please update the faq so that getting karen comes before Dogfight. I'm a little disappointed, for some reason&#8230;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1134619</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1134619</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 10:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Depends where you are but once pizzas become available they rule. Don't even need strength much when you can spam so much levels and range but there is at least ultimate pizza for it if nothing else. Also there's the Extra Sausage team which you can get from right at the start of PW, and it's pretty much the best team around for Dou stat bonus.<br /> Recommended season&#8230; well I would say S15+. It can be done S3+ I guess, and I'm sure plenty of people do it S10, but the important part is you should do it the same season you want to do root, since you should be doing both alongside each other, at the same time. looping those 5 extra seasons gives you 5 more base drain, 5 more drain range, and 5 more Dou levels, since you should hit the peeping quest each every season while you speedloop. It also makes it easier for you to get a full set of golden items if you have enough favours, as you can just pop some of the 'make me top 3' abilities with your favours and get an easy golden items from that quest each season.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1134552</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1134552</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2011 06:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The best source of Dou Strength is the Ultimate Pizza. You'll want to chug down about a half-a-dozen of those for the final check of the Super Hard path.</p> <p>There's a Jutsu that gives Dou Strength too, but it uses Pizza as a reagent, so Strength is pretty scarce. Levels are easier to et, and Range isn't too had either.</p> <p>Season doesn't matter so much, except that it raises your maximum base Dou level. My crappy alt finished PW in S11 without too much trouble.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1134149</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1134149</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 17:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>oh, an recommended season? I'm training my stats so i can challenge this thing, but i'm in S10</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-1134113</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-1134113</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>besides the all-too-infamous nuggets, what are some popular strength sources for here? my Dou strength is never above +1 without help</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-935717</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-935717</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2010 13:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Not a high level player</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Dario, it just is one of the three stats - like Tai, Nin and Gen. They just are called Drive, Drift and Destruction here.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-885434</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-885434</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2010 12:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Dario</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What does destruction do? I think there should be an explanation for the stats.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-753192</guid>
				<title>Initialize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-753192</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 17:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Stain</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You forgot to add that before you can start with easy rides, you need to unlock them with the ride: "Initialize"</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-724789</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-724789</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 19:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Once you have access to the PizzaWitch menu, one of the options is Make Pizzas.</p> <p>In order to make them, you need Ingredients, which you get by appraising the PW Ally Drops (Frost-Covered Packages, etc). Pizzas which you have the ingredients to make will show up in a list, along with how many of each Ingredient they require.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-724467</guid>
				<title>Making Pizza</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-724467</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 12:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lich</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98769</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What I need to do to make pizza?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-668079</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-668079</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Exactly.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-667835</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-667835</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So what does it mean, +10 Edge on regular missions? Kinda like Drain edge, where we have a shot at extra rolls?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-665795</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-665795</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 04:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you complete the quest Minimum Safe Distance, you get the Epilogue where you lose Lulu and Su-chan becomes Cipher.</p> <p>If you complete the quest Infiltration, you get the Epilogue where you lose Su-chan and Lulu becomes Cipher 2.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845#post-655303</guid>
				<title>what i have so far...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-203845/pizzawitch#post-655303</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 16:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jediwaldo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>104443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I didnt want to steal someone's thunder with this page. But so far i have written a guide to PW that is a little more indepth and less redundant.<br /> Guide to PizzaWitch<br /> Requirements:<br /> Gen/Nin/Tai<br /> Levels: 35+20<br /> Strength: 10+<br /> Range: 36+</p> <p>Doujutsu<br /> Levels: 25+<br /> Strength: 0<br /> Range: 18 (prefer 20+)</p> <p>Steps to Pass Pizzawitch the Unlock Quest:<br /> Quest Checks:<br /> Doujutsu 20 difficulty, 10 successes<br /> Doujutsu 10 difficulty, 500 rolling successes<br /> Need to get to 20 range first.<br /> Use Team of Lulu + Su-chan for a total of:<br /> * +2 Doujutsu Levels<br /> * +4 Doujutsu Range<br /> * +1 Doujutsu Strength<br /> Eat 2-4 Greassy Fries for 2-4 more range<br /> Eat 1-2 Greassy Nuggets for 1-2 more strength<br /> Use rest of appetite to eat Tasty Pizzas<br /> All the above can be skipped and replaced with a Greassy Royales.<br /> Once you are into PW missions and have compelted a few, Using all Yummy Pizzas is recommended and a team of Lulu lvl.2 and Su-chan lvl.2<br /> Lulu Mission: Be in an Advertisement<br /> Dou 15 diff, 25 Suc<br /> Nin 30diff, 27 suc<br /> Tai 34 diff, 25 suc<br /> Su Chan Mission: Tell Everyone about PizzaWitch<br /> Dou 20diff, 15 suc<br /> Nin 25diff, 30 suc<br /> Tai 35diff, 20 suc</p> <p>Unlocking Rides</p> <p>To unlock rides, you must complete the quest Behind the Wheel.<br /> This quest becomes available once you’ve obtained the Pizzawitch Uniform and completed 50 PizzaWitch missions.<br /> To complete the quest, you must have obtained:<br /> Lulu 2<br /> Su-chan 2<br /> Polyester Delivery Jacket<br /> Scuffed Delivery Hat<br /> Tattered Driving Gloves<br /> Tacky Keychain from PizzaWitch missions.<br /> R00t Password</p> <p>Once you complete the quest, you will receive the item License to Speed and unlock PizzaWitch deliveries in the Village menu.</p> <p>Deliveries:<br /> You are limited to 4 deliveries a day with no booster or awesome in rides.<br /> Go ahead and do the introduction to deliveries quest until you pass it.<br /> Once you do that.<br /> Do Easy Deliveries until you have upgraded your stats to your rides max (drive 3/drift 3/ destruction 3) and you start out at 2/2/2.<br /> Once you have upgraded your stats, go ahead and complete dogfight delivery to unlock normal deliveries.<br /> Once you have beat Dogfight, go ahead and farm up 30,000 tips to get the Ninja Wagon ride. (The Magic bus will become useful after you have more than 2 passengers.)</p> <p>Quest: SuperSpy (Karen get)<br /> Requirements: License to Speed, Access to Easy Rides<br /> You will need to be hanging out with Lulu and have over 100 awesome.<br /> It has a check of:<br /> dou 10diff, 10succ<br /> nin 10diff, 10succ</p> <p>Quest: Shower Scene (Karen lvl. 2 until dayroll)<br /> Requirements: Lulu in team or hanging out with Karen<br /> Simple quest no further explanation</p> <p>Quest: Grind<br /> Requirements: Karen, Cici, Access to Normal Rides<br /> You need also:<br /> Over 200 awesome<br /> I have 20 Sharpening Stones and 40 Metal Scraps<br /> Also the quest has a dou 10d10s + tai 15d15s check<br /> Rewards the Item: Grind Core which gives -1 successes.<br /> This item quest/item unlocks high level PW missions which is then used an ingredient for a level 5 item upgrade. Also, gives access to most of the rest of the PW allies.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>