<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Russian village to blow up - Blown up, Soviet village created</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-205679/russian-village-to-blow-up-blown-up-soviet-village-created</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Russian village to blow up - Blown up, Soviet village created&quot; - Russian village has been blown up and the Immortal Realm of Soviet is built upon it&#039;s ruins.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:35:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-205679#post-670752</guid>
				<title>Re: Russian village to blow up</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-205679/russian-village-to-blow-up-blown-up-soviet-village-created#post-670752</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Faroth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>298298</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Original post updated.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-205679#post-659434</guid>
				<title>Russian village to blow up</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-205679/russian-village-to-blow-up-blown-up-soviet-village-created#post-659434</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 22:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Faroth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>298298</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>We're getting ready for the Impossible Mission and only need to get 25 more villagers. So if you're looking to get Survived the Impossible or just want to help, come and join - anyone that can stay active is welcome. We have all the requirements filled except for village size. When we have enough members I'll start the IM.</p> <p>Requirements:</p> <p>Requirements status:<br /> I have Billy Lvl. 3 and Emosuke Lvl. 3: Yes<br /> Leader of an Epic village: Yes<br /> 50-Ninja Village: 50/50<br /> with 70 or more Upgrades: Yes<br /> at least 15 of them from Monsters: Yes<br /> I am Sannin: Yes<br /> Have The Note: Yes<br /> Have The Tote: Yes<br /> Have Bankai: Yes<br /> Have Cobra Kai: Yes<br /> Have all three Sannin themes: Yes<br /> Have Eye of the Storm: Yes<br /> Have Not Wasteland Disease: Yes<br /> Have sealed the Spirit of the Nine-Tailed Fox and/or the Spirit of the Demon of the Sand into a Theme: Yes<br /> My Moon is Full: Yes<br /> I am a Sannin Leader of my Epic Village: Yes<br /> No Monsters are attacking: Portal summoned</p> <p><strong>*Update</strong>*<br /> Russian village has been blown up and the Immortal Realm of Soviet is built upon it's ruins.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>