<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;PizzaWitch Garage&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;PizzaWitch Garage&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:07:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1005581</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1005581</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 08:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>unless your unspeakably lucky, and are farming the market for kaiju drops</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1003491</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1003491</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 02:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>To sum it up: Crazy Hard is generally not a good idea. Only do it for ryo and lulz when you dont need tips, coins, or WKai bonus damage. Extremely close to useless since even the ryo is barely an increase with the low drop of Awesomonium Coins</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1003486</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1003486</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 02:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>well, since this is a PW discussion he immediately thought of PW progress, or Tips. however, you gave me the simplist satisfactory answer….. as you pointed out, (except WKai) selling Awesomonium Coins is the best thing you can get from rides. sorry Prince, i tried to read the maths, but im too lazy. Something about losing tips even if you trade down with only a very small chance of getting Awesomonium Coin anyway =D</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1003150</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1003150</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 19:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sancdar</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>347541</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Long story short there is no profitable reason to do it, there are only two reasons: One to unlock Crazy Hard work in the back, which it should be noted is inferior to Extra Hard manual, but obviously better than Extra Hard work in the back when pressed for time, and Two to collect Awesomium coins for… er… 'being prepared' or something. Idk.</p> </blockquote> <p>Tips aren't used for anything, but Awesomium coins sell for 100k. Your definition of profitable and mine don't match up.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1002949</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1002949</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 14:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>How about you look at the topic and the maths before you disagree with it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1002696</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1002696</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 06:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Eh, once you get Fierce As the Flame, even CH deliveries aren't really all that crazy. I can do 'em pretty much every time…other than the occasional autokill :/<br /> Sure, you do spend some tips on getting OLR's, but if you trade away most of the other stuff (pretty much, keep what the script suggests), you should get plenty of them, and still make plenty of tips. If you're through upgrading gear, and aren't quite yet to WKai, I see no reason to drop back down.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1002538</guid>
				<title>Crazy Hard Deliveries</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1002538</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 00:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sena and I had quite the debate about this so Sena went and did some pretty extensive research on this -which quite frankly didn't get the recognition it deserved- and it's all here preserved in this topic.<br /> <a href="http://animecubed.com/billy//forum/viewtopic.php?f=36&amp;t=17452">http://animecubed.com/billy//forum/viewtopic.php?f=36&amp;t=17452</a><br /> Long story short there is no profitable reason to do it, there are only two reasons: One to unlock Crazy Hard work in the back, which it should be noted is inferior to Extra Hard manual, but obviously better than Extra Hard work in the back when pressed for time, and Two to collect Awesomium coins for… er… 'being prepared' or something. Idk.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-1002324</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-1002324</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 20:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok, so I've pretty much mastered hard deliveries (thanks guys =D). My question now is what's the point of running crazy hard deliveries? The optimal ride setup for extra hard suggests that it's a billion times easier than crazy hard, for a penatly of 5k tips base…. Plus if you're still upgrading gear the awesomonium coin makes diamond coins that much rarer. Since the awesomonium coins are useless except to sell and the tips are lost in cards and failures, what's the point if doing crazy hard deliveries?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-988929</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-988929</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 06:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you're passing hards with only 10 deliciousness, then I definitely would suggest you drop down to easy/normal, to farm tips for better rides, and lulu. Lulu is pretty much essential, until you have a really good ride, if you want any chance at getting tip coins. Better to pass a normal ride with 150, 200 deliciousness, than to barely pass a hard. Plus, the only difficulty really worth working in the back is crazy hard, I'd say, unless you just don't have time to do them. PW isn't one of those "breeze through it" kinda content areas. You gotta start out easy, improve your ride and all, and work your way up.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-988884</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-988884</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 04:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You do know that refusing to loop is just making you extremely slow and inefficient, right?<br /> As long as you know that, if you willingly sell yourself short, that's not my business anymore.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-988874</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-988874</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 04:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thanks prince. I actually do have my epitaph now, I just need to recompile for my tai discord and get my hacks/mono keys til One Sin. I'm just being lazy about it because I was hoping for a sci4 day. I spent all my tips on cards today, no passengers from midnight run but I got some deliciousness stuff from easy street. Still no eviltaxi. I'm passing hard rides with like 15 deliciousness left =/ but Ive only failed one out of like 10ish, so I was thinking that I'd finish my 20 hards and then work in the back since I'm not even close to 100 deliciousness. At ~15 delciousness working in the back would give me quite a bit more tips =/ lol</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-988265</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-988265</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 10:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi kwigyo, I don't know much about your situation but I hope that I can give you helpful advice.<br /> First of all, don't get the rides awesome just for that purpose, you don't need it. Don't worry about upgrading your gear apart from Digital Keychain, which is essential and a great thing to prioritise, not to mention that it is the only way to get rid of your Grind Core (-1 success) aside from looping.<br /> [Subsection about Digi keychain: Its main costs are Soundless Jade -a medium difficulty untradable LW- and 20 Lightning Essences. On the previous upgrades in the chain you must have used 4 Sapphire Ryo coins and 3 Ruby Ryo coins, both available even on Normal rides. It also gives you more rides, which means more tips and coins! If you do not have the coins for this upgrade (or rather the preceding levels), you may want to try doing very well at normal rides as jimfromtx suggested. Which brings me onto my next point…]</p> <p>LuLu. Perhaps Evil Taxi's biggest advantage is that you can equip two passangers, so throw on White Witch and LuLu for +50 deliciousness. He is available in the Midnight Run packs which Hard unlocks.<br /> Regarding Work in the Back, it's awful. It really is not very good, it gives you less tips and problably less coins than you can earn. You have to spend a few cards to get tips and coins, crack a few eggs to make an omelette, don't let that part put you off. However, if you can't get above 100 deliciousness, then 10% is at least better than none. But again, in this case it would probably be better to go back to normal if you're that desperate for ruby/sapphies. The other gear upgrades won't really help your deliciousness much anyway.</p> <p>Now for the personal advice from what I can, from the outside, try to deduce… You're season 4, you have all 4 tradable lost weapons, however you are not R00t rank and never have been, as such you have not been able to claim your lycoris. You do not have pink taser or time reversal cube. In fact, even before One Sin stages, you do not have Epitaph of the Twilight, so I believe you are having some difficulty beating the discords.<br /> For these reasons you cannot get a Soundless Jade any time soon and thus cannot progress any further in your PizzaWitch progress… after hard comes the extremely boring Cans of Sauce grind, which does not loop, followed by the Digi Keychain check. I know it is not what you asked but at this point I can only recommend you loop to S15+ and get this far into r00t that you can make the digital keychain, simultaneously running Hard/Normal rides since they cost no stamina and are free daily. By then you should have a good stock of Midnight Run cards and enough tips saved up to buy the Mach Eleven and a few levels too…</p> <p>tl;dr (but I took all that time to see what you needed…), don't do shifts unless 1. You have no good cards, or 2. You can't even get 100 Deliciousness, or 3. You have no time. Don't restat into rides, they're useless (sometimes useful for WK or high-level coin grinding, but that's situational…). Get LuLu a.s.a.p. for free deliciousness bonus every ride. Consider doing normal rides if you only need sapphire/ruby.</p> <p>Giving way too much detail as always,<br /> -Prince</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-987839</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-987839</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 21:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimfromtx</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I went through all of PW easy (including fully upgraded gear) without lvl 3 ride awesome. Drop back down to the easier rides, and do those, running plenty of melty cheese cards, to get the coins to upgrade. Hard is much easier once you have upgraded gear. And don't even think about doing crazy hard without fierce as the flame, it's just…crazy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-987714</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-987714</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 18:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Given the choice of doing rides or working in the back, I'd take working in the back every time. Doesn't cost you any cards, doesn't take any effort, what's not to like?</p> <p>Personally, I took my time with PizzaWitch, just doing shifts for some time while I focused on doing other stuff in BvS… by the time I got back to PW, I had tips and coins to spare.</p> <p>I think you're better off keeping the storm awesome, but I'm hardly an expert. :-)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-987674</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-987674</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 17:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So i'm trying to upgrade my gear, but my deliciousness is never high enough to get coins. Would it be worth doing shifts? I'm on hard now, haven't unlocked any shifts because I flew through easy and normal. Also, would it be worth spending 1mil ryo and losing my storm awesome for ride awesome and double coin chance?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-858106</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-858106</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 11:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Agent Inari</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>392886</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Same as JimWorm. Also, I get that the text in the card "Game Spoiler" is about Final Fantasy 7, but what does "TV Spoiler" refer to?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-850092</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-850092</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 08:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay then…Hold Together. 50% chance to survive a burn. I'm assuming this means that *if* a card would have been burned by its use (you hit the wrong part of that 80%, or whatever it is for the card you used after), then it's a 50% chance of not losing it after all? If so, then…does that include the Hold Together itself, is there a 50% chance you won't lose it, by its very nature?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-840075</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-840075</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 03:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The chance determines whether you get a coin. If so, you get a Ruby. Then a completely seperate set of Rolls are performed to see if you get a better coin than that.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353#post-840030</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-204353/pizzawitch-garage#post-840030</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 01:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you work in the back on a higher difficulty, is there an equal chance of each type of tip coin, or is the 10/25/40% weighted somehow? For example, if you work a normal, which can give only ruby/sapphire, would it be a 5% chance of each?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>