<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Is it possible to get Nadeshiko in the Festival time?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-202331/is-it-possible-to-get-nadeshiko-in-the-festival-time</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Is it possible to get Nadeshiko in the Festival time?&quot; - Is it a valid strategy?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:48:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-202331#post-649559</guid>
				<title>Re: Is it possible to get Nadeshiko in the Festival time?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-202331/is-it-possible-to-get-nadeshiko-in-the-festival-time#post-649559</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 19:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>No. During last festival, there was a bug at the very beginning where you could go in the tunnel an unlimited amount of times. One of my characters was hanging out with 15 or so allies, and no Nadeshiko. The way the system checks for hangouts at dayroll means that you must use friend points. The reason is that the hangouts from the previous day are wiped before checking for new hangouts and Nadeshiko.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-202331#post-649555</guid>
				<title>Is it possible to get Nadeshiko in the Festival time?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-202331/is-it-possible-to-get-nadeshiko-in-the-festival-time#post-649555</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 19:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KuroiAoi</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Will it work?</p> <p>I mean, as we know, the Festivals occurs in villages at the 11th day of each month, and there is a place called <strong>Tunnel of Love</strong> that allows us to hang out with our current team.</p> <p>So, if being hanging out with 4 allies is a requirement to get <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Nadeshiko</span>, would it be a valid strategy to use this day to hang out with 3 allies and then use the Make Out Mood Enhancer to get the hanging out stats with another one? Would I get her this way?</p> <p>Thanks in advance.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>