<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;The Race&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-213692/the-race</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;The Race&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:45:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-213692#post-1391715</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-213692/the-race#post-1391715</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2012 06:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It sounds fair, but durability is already low in this setup, with -350 from equipment and +150 from 3 Emergency Countermeasures, leading to a total deficit of 200. Mach Eleven has only 200 base durability, and of course one must equip Su-chan for another 200. But D-ability slots are filled up, and as you said the other 3 D-abilities are really quite essential. So one or more of the Emergency Countermeasures would need to be removed, losing 50 durability and 50 drivetrain (the card has no penalty). Special Sauce on the other hand takes 50 drivetrain, and gives only 30 delicousness.</p> <p>Considering that even with all 3 emergency countermeasures we have a result of -200 drivetrain (again, the other three D-abilities causing this seem essential) which is including the +50 drivetrain buff from an equipment and +150 from the Emergency Countermeasures, drivetrain is not a breeze either. While of course one must have a certain degree of investment in their jacket by this point, I cannot encourage a reliance on high levels of it since that would waste more time at the point one should be doing pw. A strategy like this might not guarantee success but it does give you a serious and dependable chance with room for your own preparedness to improve it if you can. That, I think, is the essence of the PW guide. Doing it quickly and smartly is the only fashionable way to do it these days, and pw is one of the rare chances to excel in relatively early content.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-213692#post-1391222</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-213692/the-race#post-1391222</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 16:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Dracos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1197540</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'll toss in a note that I got killed 3 times trying that setup and one time just being stupid.</p> <p>The Beyond the Limit is needed because you need to be at speed 8 or higher by the very first step of the way.</p> <p>Without a max level glove, the setup only has about a 75 percent chance of making it through the first two gates. Wouldn't be a big deal, but it's autofail, rather than repeat. The glove raises it to 85 percent.</p> <p>Using the +10 cards on the two double challenges is pretty wise. Makes them almost certain passes.</p> <p>What got me the third time was actually deliciousness though. The setup leaves no room for deliciousness going down and nothing you can do with that. In my runs so far, durability hasn't actually dropped and a high jacket makes drivetrain an irrelevant thing.</p> <p>I'd recommend more deliciousness d-abilities. Special Sauce for instance. Keep one durability one, but that way there's a way to respond to either durability drain (seems rare) or deliciousness drain (is gonna happen)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>