<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Speedloop guide to slow</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314/speedloop-guide-to-slow</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Speedloop guide to slow&quot; - I have started speed looping and have found the guide to be slow. It says that you need to be done most of the starting things, but it tells you to do things that slow you down: bingos, reaper.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:14:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314#post-943111</guid>
				<title>Re: Speedloop guide to slow</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314/speedloop-guide-to-slow#post-943111</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 21:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rabid Rob</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>261044</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I speedloop in a day, and yeah, Bingos are definitely not worth it. Even though I can spend money to guarantee each bingo is a win, the stamina costs before I get returns is way too high.</p> <p>Reaper, on the other hand, I use smokebombs to go just for Strawberry when C-rank missions open, get the Captains Jacket (xp bonus) and Mr. Tea (cheaper quests, ranking booster). Currently I think it's worth it, especially since I still need to run the +1 Dou level quest.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314#post-712555</guid>
				<title>Speedloop guide to slow</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-223314/speedloop-guide-to-slow#post-712555</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2010 22:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Hokorippoi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>448532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have started speed looping and have found the guide to be slow. It says that you need to be done most starting things, but it tells you to do things that slow you down: bingos, reaper.</p> <p>Here is the time table of what I 1st loop has been like so far.<br /> Day 0, loop day: Loop, Chunin, Special Jonin.<br /> Day 1, 1st full day: Jonin.<br /> Day 2, 1st Jonin only day: Taijutsu lvl 23.</p> <p>Looking at the ap I get, I should be able to loop in 2-3 days max.<br /> Bingos and reaper would have added a few days.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>