<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Face To Face 2&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Face To Face 2&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:57:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1064660</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1064660</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 21:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>FUn fact: F2F2 used to be much, much, MUCh more difficult. BAW and general hate for it caused MCM to end up changing it, as I recall.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1054847</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1054847</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok, question answered. F2F1 will be available to me, but not F2F2, which requires looping after F2F1…. Just for anyone else that cares. Also, @prince, the reason I remarked that this is so easy is that the 2 F2F deliveries ARE identical, save for the requirements to start them and the rewards. As the final ride and the final step in PW, it seems like this should be harder (by the way, apparently I fail at math because as long as you have the village upgrade, you don't need to be RedEye. You'll meet the required speed and therefore have 86% chance to pass)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1054823</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1054823</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 16:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Question: I finished PW easy but started looping between getting my Racers Edge and F2F1. So when I beat PW Hard, this delivery will come up, but will F2F1 also come up since I haven't beaten it but I have my bloodline? Or do I need to do another season of PW Easy? Maybe this is the wrong place to post this, and maybe I've already asked somewhere else, but oh well. =)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1045820</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1045820</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 03:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Let's both pretend your first post didn't happen because we know that was based on an older setup :P No disrespect to that person, they're my old village-mate now quit, but that was a year ago. You suggested Crimson Lotus but that ride is redundant… so instead I was just talking about the two from the 28th.<br /> Anyway I think kwigyo's thinking that 'the only real obstacle is the speed one' is pretty sound, because after all you can do the whole ride with very high stats thanks to the MachEleven, unlike the Crimson Lotus which was originally designed for it. Your durability may start low, but that is why there are 3 Emergency Countermeasures. It shouldn't be too difficult aside from that one obstacle, assuming you don't have awful bad luck for some reason.</p> <p>Considering how at this point you would already have Cipher2, rides cost no stam, and there's nothing after this* but two trophies, people shouldn't be in too huge a rush to beat it instead of powering up their ride and stuff. On the other hand this is the F2F2 page: players would be doing this who-knows-how-long after they've beaten F2F1… and considering how they're nearly identical, why they would even have a problem with it at this stage is beyond me.</p> <p>*The "Calling" Theme, which has never done what it promises due to there being no Reaper's game yet, is only useful for getting the Player Pin, which itself is only useful for unlocking the non-existent Reaper's Game. It's now even more awful in that it must be activated in place of the theme <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/theme:power-of-sound">Power of Sound</a> which is irreplaceable for Glowslinging (which of course happens each and every day once unlocked).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1045790</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1045790</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I would note that my initial post was made before the page was revised; when I posted it, there was no mention of the White Witch, and the recommended setup was slightly different. I haven't tried the revised version. (I have only one account, and I've already passed this.) I'd also note that there's more than one test to pass here; it's also a long course on a ride that's stretched pretty thin…</p> <p>That said, yes, the challenge is getting your equipment good enough to ace this, rather than the ride itself.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1045757</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1045757</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 02:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes, it is easy. Yes, we know The White Witch increases speed, that's why it's recommended. As he says I believe you can reach 24 speed, however this is only if you have the majorkai upgrade police lights from the sexy lady cops or instead are RedEye bloodline (which at time of writing is not advisable in the slightest). The former is of course not possible in Tier2, however this setup will work for people there anyway. The percentage chance [for that one hurdle] will of course depend on your circumstances going in, (more on this below) but regardless, if you have 40% chance it is more than enough for this situation. For a ride you can do 7-9 times a day WITHOUT awesome in rides, the only real restrictive factor is the cards. But, at this point you have access to Extra Hard rides, which are the best place to farm tips. The setup also uses only one Style card, but if you have the village upgrade in question, correct me if I'm wrong but I believe you can then eliminate the style card with no major consequence (unless you're for some reason trying this redeye).</p> <p>Regarding the two earlier posts (I meant to reply to those last month…), let's look at the Drive stats for that one Speed 24, 9d3s check. Base 11, The White Witch +1 (Passenger), Basic Turbo +1 (Common Equip), Infinite Potential +1 (lasting D-Ability), Initial Drive +10[once] (D-Ability), (<a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:wasteland-highway">Wasteland Highway</a> +1 (village upgrade from custom kaiju 1 EvilTaxi), and <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:driving-music">Driving Music</a> +1 (perm drop from custom kaiju 12 Dave). So that makes 14 for the ride, +10 once, +1 from village, +1 from perm. Up to 26 Drive for the speed hurdle, 9d3s makes… 92%? 49% if you're riding T2 or lacking 1 speed for some other reason. Although you could consider incorporating the equip Safety Harness if you think it would help, this setup is both strong and versatile as it is.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-1044656</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-1044656</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 18:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>brinhe</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm not sure if this is taken into account anywhere, but The White Witch adds 1 to ALL stats. Including D-speed. 24 speed, gogo.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-987621</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-987621</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 16:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"40% chance success as nonRedEye" even after the long haul of upgrading all your stats and equipment and such doesn't quite strike me as "really easy."</p> <p>That said, yes, once you've finally managed to fill all the requirements for doing this, actually doing it is, well, doable. It's the journey that's the point! :-)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-987603</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-987603</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Is it just me or does this ride seem really easy? With 13 in all stats (11+1 for White Witch and +1 for the entire ride D-card) and then other bonuses like the gloves, the only problem is D-speed. Which, with this setup is taken care of. Using the Max Speed D-card immediately, you have 23 speed. The only thing that becomes a problem is the 10d3 (9d3 +1 speed difficulty, the penalty isn't even present as a RedEye) which is countered by the +10 drive D-card. 23 levels for 3 successes is a 40% chance success as nonRedEye, but as a RedEye it's a 86% chance</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035#post-970668</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-221035/face-to-face-2#post-970668</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 00:48:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm not sure I'm confident enough in this to add it to the page itself, but after trying and failing with the vehicle configuration recommended on the page, I had better luck with this one:</p> <p>Vehicle: Crimson Lotus<br /> Equipment: Ridiculous Spoiler, Cobalt Supercharger, The Roar<br /> D-Abilities: Beyond the Limit, Emergency Countermeasures, Infinite Potential, and 2 Flat-Out Run<br /> Jacket: at least the Wasteland Delivery Jacket (300 Drivetrain)</p> <p>Requires playing your cards right and a bit of luck with the RNG, but it worked for me.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>