<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Franklin Badge&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011/franklin-badge</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Franklin Badge&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:46:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011#post-946698</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011/franklin-badge#post-946698</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 17:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rika Covenant</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually, he is incorrect, due to his statement that it was translated to the NES as Earthbound or Earth Bound, variances in exactly the format of the title notwithstanding, when it was not. It was to be localized as Earthbound, true enough, however it never was. Marketing issues pushed it back from the original release date in 1990 to Fall 1991, and then it was put on indefinite hold (sadly). The reason that happened was because the SNES came along- and who would want to buy an NES game for the older system when there was something new and awesome out now? Phil Sandhop, who was the localization producer for the game, has said as much. There is an interview of him regarding the prototype Mother cartridge that has spawned the Earthbound Zero ROM, that can be found here: <a href="http://www.lostlevels.org/200407/200407-earthbound.shtml">http://www.lostlevels.org/200407/200407-earthbound.shtml</a> The SNES game, Mother 2, was sadly the only one localized and it was the one that used the name Earthbound, without the capital B or variances of title (Between EarthBound and Earth Bound, the latter of which, considering the original content of the first game, makes more sense).</p> <p>The fact the SNES game is named Earthbound is far and away more known than the Mother series, though most people who know of the game beyond a passing rememberance know the series under its original name series; Due to the level of trivia-type informative blurbs contained throughout the other pages of the BVSWiki, leaving in the reference would be best.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011#post-929819</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011/franklin-badge#post-929819</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 00:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Skarn22</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>372883</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually, neither of you are wrong, because the name "Earthbound" was at one point used for both games, it is technically an alternate name for both.</p> <p>The fact of the matter is it technically is a reference to all three games. I say we either re-write it as such or remove the "mother" reference altogether. Probably the latter, since only a few people would even recognize the japanese name…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011#post-902053</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011/franklin-badge#post-902053</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 03:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually, you're incorrect. Mother was to be localized originally as Earthbound, however it was Mother 2 that was localized as Earthbound instead on the SNES. Many fans have demanded a port of both the original Mother and the newer GBA game Mother 3 to North America, but it still as of yet has not been ported over. The Franklin Badge has been in all three games (confirmed not just from research, but from playing all three games, either under fan translation (1, 3) or the original SNES cartridge) and is iconic to most North Americans under Mother 2/Earthbound with Ness and Paula et al.</p> <p>You who wrote the above note are ill-informed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011#post-734785</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-229011/franklin-badge#post-734785</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 02:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nymphonomicon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91001</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The "Notes" section needs to be rewritten. For starters, the game that it claims the item refers to is actually Mother 2, the only Mother title to see an English release so far. The original Mother was a Famicom title, it was translated for the NES as "Earthbound," but never saw an English release.<br /> Granted, the reference is valid since the Franklin Badge is an iconic item that has appeared in all three Mother titles to date, but whoever wrote that "Note" was ill-informed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>