<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Crazy Hard&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Crazy Hard&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:57:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1105490</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1105490</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 06:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Mostly just Heroes Quest.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1098437</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1098437</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 10:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"Known content"? What is known content? Kind of like Pirates, Nations, SWATBU, houses, dating, new zombja maps, new Avatar Abilities, new Rides, and of course Heroes Quest… yeaa… unless some of these are rolled into Heroes Quest, which as we know is aimed at top end players who've completed everything up to and including WorldKaiju, I wouldn't hold my breath if I were you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1098389</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1098389</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 09:43:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While I completely agree with you, trying to infer that Awwesomium Coins are entirely useless and should be avoided when there is known content coming out that will in all likelyhood involve them is something that should be avoided.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1096919</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1096919</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 00:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Smokeblossoms were put into another sink BECAUSE they're useless and there are too many. He just put another duct tape solution on one of many old lingering problems… that doesn't mean that awesomium coins are any less useless, or that stockpiling them now won't make him go 'I need to make a sink for awesomium coins'. It wouldn't be the first time he's looked at the biggest hoarders and judged the whole playerbase's counts by it. Just because there are ways to fix a problem down the line that doesn't serve as an excuse for creating the problem in the first place…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1096766</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1096766</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 22:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>No, Lunatic Rides come out when we get to do more with the Overworld, which the Hero Quest is going to let us do. As for the Awesomium Coin thing- yeah, useless. That's what people thought about smokeblossoms. Now thanks to hanafuda, they sell like hotakes. Never doubt the man's ability to make something seen as useless and turn it into something needed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1095044</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1095044</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 11:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have no idea what you're talking about… regardless, here's the data. <a href="http://www.animecubed.com/billy/forum/viewtopic.php?f=36&amp;t=17452">http://www.animecubed.com/billy/forum/viewtopic.php?f=36&amp;t=17452</a><br /> Crazy Hards right now are just inferior to top Extra Hards: undoubtedly so in terms of Tips, debatably so in terms of Ryo Coins. In my opinion we should just leave them alone until we have full stats, Fierce as the Flame and plenty of tips for cards, and then unlock CH work in the back… and then leave them alone. Manual EHs give way more tips profit anyway, and awesomium ryo coins are currently as useless as oxyblasts at time of writing. Crazy Hard rides are just another example of a content McM didn't finish with the excuse that it was going to be done later, and then moved on to procrastinate over something else entirely…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1012211</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1012211</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd like to point out a slight observation of mine. Some time ago, someone doubted the efficiency of Crazy Hard in comparison to lesser difficulties. For the most part, all you get is coins that serve next to no purpose other than ryo farming. The point—marketplace farming for kaiju drops. I know i must NOT be the only one who finds it difficult to either obtain crazy large amounts of ryo for MPfarming, nor the only one who finds toying with Counting Coup crazy hard in comparison to others who could use those drops for either themselves, or for MP ryo farming. don't ya think that the coin system was made to go around all that?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-1012189</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-1012189</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2011 22:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mister C</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>285121</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have PW gear at max, and still when I use the second set-up, I start at -40 durability… are you -sure- that's gonna work? O.o</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683#post-982205</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-243683/crazy-hard#post-982205</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 17:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I advice to use Cobalt Supercharger instead of Ablative Armor for suggested tactic. Btw I have full set of upgrades, so 8/8 Drift goes well, but Drive seems like is needed to charge. :)</p> <p>P.S. It is not really needed to stay at speed 1 till 5 cards use, but I do not sure what is base equip for this decision.</p> <p>P.P.S. This is PERFECT to use just 2 speed mode (8) or (3). Use 8 even if u'll have 3 or slower check next, but u won't meet this with 8 points of speed, i.e. 8+8+3 is better than 3+3+3… :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>