<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;BillyMaze&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;BillyMaze&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1505012</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1505012</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 13:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Xiandora</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>220955</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I don't remember where I saw it, but I do remember seeing someone wanting to confirm it IS randomly generated for each user at each new festival, and no carried over into new festivals.</p> <p>I dotted down all information about what happened at last festival BillyMaze manually and can confirm that it is now useless.</p> <p>*Edit* Ah, I saw on the actual BillyMaze page. Someone edit out the parenthesis wanting to confirm it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1303586</guid>
				<title>White Eyes is better than it sounds here</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1303586</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 17:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Dracos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1197540</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>White Eyes doesn't just mark an incorrect direction once, but on every single room.</p> <p>Legacy gives you a pass on 1 room. Leaving without allies, 9 right out of 45 remaining choice options on the road. Good choice.</p> <p>Red Eyes gives you 3 passes on mistakes. Leaving without allies, 10 right out of 47 remaining choice options on the road. Terrible choice.</p> <p>White eyes marks 1 off on each. Leaving without allies, 10 right out 40 choice options on the way, and your chance of guessing right on any room goes from 20 percent to 25 percent.</p> <p>Olmek removes 1 choice option. You also get 3 free choice options. Brings you down to 36.</p> <p>Tacos I've had activate every time once and only once. Not sure if she can do more or less, but this removes 4 choices and gives you 1 guarentee. Combo'd with Olmek it leaves you with needing to guess 9 right choices out of 32 to get to room 11. Not a sure win of course, but pretty good odds.</p> <p>I haven't found the other allies reliable for activating. Snakeman removes 1 choice each time he activates. Spot if he activates drops it to 8 right choices out of 28.</p> <p>Add the billymaze script, and it will correctly give you the back half of the maze.</p> <p>Not sure if anything gives better odds than that, but there's my ramble. White Eyes is definitely the right choice for billymaze provided your target is to finish it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1044029</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1044029</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2011 13:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Snail486</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Which is also suggested by Probability Theory. There will always be outliers in any statistical distribution that the human mind will attribute to something being non-random.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1035854</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1035854</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 15:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Snail, I disagree. Probabily theory may say that, but in truth I've only seen Ninja be the answer in 1 room out of the 5 or so mazes I've done. I didn't even know it COULD be an answer until I failed all 4 directions that room, I thought it was just a joke.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1029116</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1029116</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2011 21:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Snail486</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Probability theory states that for any given room there is an equal chance for any of the five exits. You should keep track of what slots you took so you can find your way out, but you can't accurately predict what an exit will be based on the previous rooms.</p> <p>The RNG is the hand of Probability. Any behavior that it displays, probability theory predicts.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1001034</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1001034</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2011 05:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Luneth</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Of course, I fail at my own example as I just said the one I personally knocked out with my fake WhiteEye was a probable one, but you should get the logic. Let's say I wasn't WE there. JSE are the second best choices, which means slot 5 is the best indicator since slot 3 is wrong. 5E looks like a very strong pick, and would be my second guess there.</p> <p>You should get the idea by now. Just keep track of everything. Everything.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1001033</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1001033</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2011 05:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Luneth</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have found that you can use simple probability theory to increase your chances of guessing right as you proceed down the maze.</p> <p>I'll outline how I walk the maze here, structured the same way I put the lines into notepad. An Area generally looks like this at first-</p> <p>1&nbsp;E: ?N, ?W, ?E, XS, XJ</p> <p>I outline in order; what Area it is, where I entered from, the 5 choices (J for ninja, because N is north), and whether or not I know the direction is good via ? (For unknown) and ! (For correct way.)</p> <p>The trick is to, once you get about 4-5 Areas in, start keeping track of what direction and slot have been used overall. If my first 5 Areas are as follows:</p> <p>1&nbsp;E: !N, XW, XE, XS, XJ<br /> 2&nbsp;N: !J, XE, XS, XN, XW<br /> 3&nbsp;S: XS, !N, XE, XW, XJ<br /> 4&nbsp;W: XJ, XN, XE, !S, XW<br /> 5&nbsp;E: !E, XW, XS, XJ, XN</p> <p>and I get a 6th area as such (I'll pretend to be WhiteEye here):<br /> 6&nbsp;S: ?S, ?J, XW, ?N, ?E</p> <p>Than a trick I use is to count how many each slot and direction have been used. In this case, we get the following:<br /> 11241<br /> NJNSE<br /> We can see that slots 3 and 5 haven't been used yet. We can also see that West has not been an exit yet either. And in this fake area 6, we have a slot 3&nbsp;W open. There's a much higher chance that the unused 3W is the right one than, say, the 4N because we have gotten a slot 4 already and 2 Norths.</p> <p>The logic will be defeated by the RNG sometimes. In fact on my foray back out to find out how much Ryo you get, I did not have a single exit in the third slot on the way in for the entire maze. But by using this logic, I have reached, and will probably do so every time, the end of the maze as WhiteEye with no allies and only a 512 stamina GiT where when I was new at it I failed twice as a RedEye with the 2k+ GiTs and full allies.</p> <p>Also, I'm fairly certain the room you're "sent to" upon failing is nothing more than a random from Area 1 to the area you're on. I don't really think failures in the maze do anything but make you use GiTs, especially since with a perfect log of the maze you should never repeat a failed direction.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-1000347</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-1000347</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2011 05:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>anima</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>@ Luneth</p> <p>how can you be experienced @ maze-going? is there a bigger pattern i don't see?</p> <p>as far as i know it's just random so even if it is your 100th maze if RNG hates you on that day and you have an average of 2 wrong picks per room you will end up with 16384 as red-eye ^^</p> <p>btw i screwed up on my way out today (because i am stupid and i looked @ the wrong line) and yes:</p> <p>if you screw up at area 5 you land @ area 5 ^^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-999973</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-999973</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 17:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Luneth</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Just for fun (because at this point I'm so experienced at maze-going I can do it without any of the allies we've found so far), I decided to quit the maze while at Area 1 on the way back in to see how much Ryo I'd get.</p> <p>It turns out you only get 125 if you do that. The Ryo amounts don't double on the way out the way they do on the way in- each area only has the amount you see on the way in.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-947092</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-947092</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 01:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It would be BEYOND BAW if it kicked you to a random location- and besides, it might accidentally shunt you out to Area 1. I've no doubt (and minor testing with a friend who also plays) that it sends you right back to where you screwed up.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-895187</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-895187</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 15:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Skarn22</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>372883</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Does anyone have a definite answer to Lintor's question? At least one person I've seen has said that they did not move at all from making a mistake. In fact, they made several mistakes due to confusion but remained in area 9… So maybe I already have an answer.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-848007</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-848007</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 22:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>TACOS' help is "TACOS hops up and down and STARES at you… O_O" . That means go East, as she's strong in that direction.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-847550</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-847550</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 07:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lintor</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So, if you hit A11, and fail on your way out at stage n, I notice it gives you the option to get it together " AAAAA AAAAAAA (256 AAAAAAA)"<br /> Question is, where are you? I mean, I just misread my notes, and I could escape if I knew where I was. Are you still at n where you failed? Somewhere between n-10? Somewhere between 1-n?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-829841</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-829841</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 19:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>AmineHsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164570</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I mean on how to know where to go on the way out. I read McMaster's 'warning' and copied down what I thought was all the information, I didn't realize till it was too late that the order the options were in was part of that.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-829717</guid>
				<title>Re: AmineHsu</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-829717</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 15:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>rveach2</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>275216</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You mean a solution to solving the maze? There is none, it is randomly generated for each user/festival.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-829708</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-829708</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 15:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>AmineHsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164570</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Why is there no solution on the page? Especially the copying down of the order of the directions I thought was both non-obvious and rage worthy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-827578</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-827578</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 21:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You don't stay in Area 11. Once you get there, you're automatically sent back to Area 10. Therefore, the most Ryo you can get is from giving up in Area 10, for 64k Ryo.</p> <p>The Grand Prize, <a class="newpage" href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:oxyblast">OxyBlast</a> is obtained by reaching Area 11, and successfully navigating back to the entrance.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-827274</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-827274</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 11:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>The TubStar</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>39418</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So what is the prize at A11? Has anyone made it out with the grand prize yet? Or does it continue on with the progression Anima noticed, making the prize at A11&nbsp;128,000 ryo? (A9 being 32,000 and A10 being 64,000, assuming it follows the same pattern)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-827141</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-827141</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 05:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>There are 2 keys to successfully completing the maze:<br /> 1) Write down each correct direction. The right way never changes except from month to month.<br /> 2) Write down which direction you entered the room from, and which of the 5 options that direction is.</p> <p>For example:<br /> you enter Area 1 from the South..<br /> East West South Ninja North</p> <p>Remember South, and that the 3rd option was South. This is <strong>EXTREMELY</strong> important for getting out of the maze.</p> <p>There are 11 Areas. Once you reach Area 11, you snatch the prize and then have to escape from the maze. You're automatically sent back to Area 10. Once you get there, though… ALL text will have changed to a string of AAAAAA.</p> <p>The way to get out is to follow the directions you entered the area from.</p> <p>If you entered Area 10 from the East, you need to go East, which means you also need to know which of the 5 AAAA directions actually IS East. Repeat this 10 times, and you've escaped the maze.</p> <p>Which means the REAL hard part is figuring out the first 10 Directions through trial and error.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-826949</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-826949</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 19:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>anima</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>you have only one try on billy maze per month.</p> <p>if you enter it you get a screen that tells you from where you enter and 5 directions to choose from. for example:<br /> <em>"you enter Area 1 from the South.."<br /> "East West South Ninja North"</em></p> <p>only one of the 5 directions is right. if you choose the wrong one you get<br /> <em>"You wander for a while, and don't see anywwhere new..<br /> Wow, you got really lost there and tired out. You are going to have to Get It Together<br /> if you want to keep going.."</em><br /> and are set back a few areas. The way always keeps the same btw, no matter how many times you get lost.</p> <p>You have 3 free "Get It Together". After that it costs 1 stamina, doubling every time you have to use it. (1,2,4,8,16,32,64,128,256…)<br /> Moving costs no stamina btw.</p> <p>every area you get in doubles the ryo you get for giving up starting at 125 ryo:<br /> A1&nbsp;125 ryo<br /> A2&nbsp;250 ryo<br /> A3&nbsp;500 ryo<br /> A4&nbsp;1000 ryo<br /> A5&nbsp;2000 ryo<br /> A6&nbsp;4000 ryo<br /> A7&nbsp;8000 ryo<br /> A8&nbsp;16000 ryo</p> <p>my guess is that A11 is the center. (i only came to A8)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-826795</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-826795</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 13:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>The TubStar</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>39418</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's definitely different for each person, my 1st 3 rooms were East East Ninja, in that order, though if you end up back in an earlier room, the direction that worked then is the same, so recording your steps helps immensely. Though for some reason even if you pick the right direction it may not send you to the next room.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714#post-826699</guid>
				<title>Mazey Maze!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-252714/billymaze#post-826699</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 08:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Remeko</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>204808</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Legacy is, the first area gives you the correct direction. :D On mine, i got north… and from there, i made a little list, till my stamina costs went through the roof. :/</p> <p>Area 1 North<br /> Area 2 West<br /> Area 3 South<br /> Area 4 West<br /> Area 5 Ninja</p> <p>i can't edit the page though, so could whoever can, put up the legacy? Also. This directions list may not work for you, as it might be different for each person… though, apparently, the directions don't seem to change when you get sent back to the start. :/</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>