<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Om Nom Trophy?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Om Nom Trophy?&quot; - FairyGuy has a trophy named Om Nom on his forum signature on the official forums... Is it real?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:14:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-977475</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-977475</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That's part of global warming- and don't let the crackpotists try to dissuade you- It is happening. It is taking longer, and it's being more subtle than was originally forecast, but it still is occuring. You can see it in things like the unseasonal weather occuring all across the world; Philippines are getting much much more rain, Canada is going without snow well into December (We had our first snowfall sometime around Christmas, to give you an idea), freak winter weather to the tune of 120 MP/H winds and six-metre high waves…. Not to mention snow in Carcassonne (To explain: It is in the southern part of France, and has a number of very warm winds blowing from the south keeping it seasonable. Much like Alberta gets its Chinooks where you can go outside in the middle of winter in Calgary and wear only shorts and a tank top).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-976303</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-976303</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 11:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes, a headache it is softly told… But when you see the flooding in Philippines… Seems like we really destroy our home…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-976299</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-976299</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 11:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That's because mass media has become mass hysteria- If it's not OMG DRAMATIC it's not "news". You can find far more interesting news- stuff that isn't overly dramatized- online. Of course, try to stay away from any politically charged site- Newsweek, for example, is neo-conservative, Politico has its share of left-wing and right-wing writers and commenters… ANd they'll both give you headaches, etc. etc.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-975755</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-975755</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 20:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Cruel times… Though speak, that the history develops cyclically… Сan it be a new coil? News on TV looks terribly almost every day!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-975133</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-975133</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 01:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ninja did whatever they had to to fulfill the orders that they were given, that is correct. Ronin were the fallen samurai, however, and they were little more than hired killers. Not assassins, just killers. Like the difference between a guy with a rocket launcher and a guy who sneaks around with a silenced PP7. :P As for the Samurai themselves- They did make up a large portion of the defenses of a Daimyo, but they were more akin to his Right Arm; They were his enforcers as well as his shield. And while yes, they did have the code of Bushido, many *ahem* "smart" Samurai would find small ways to bend and break them- They weren't held to as rigourously as we once thought. For example of someone trying to bend those rules and failing- A ronin, who had sold even the metal blades of his swords for money for himself and his family to eat, wandered to a Daimyo's castle and requested (as is acceptable in bushido) that he be allowed to commit harakiri so he might be buried upon the Daimyo's land; He did this to have the Daimyo take pity upon him and give him work… And instead had to disembowel himself with a bamboo sword, taking minutes to do the deed, instead of the usual one-two seconds.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-974567</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-974567</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 10:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>45 people classes? o_O If we had 25, this is a very bad rare situation… I've read much about such "politics", like "America was almost at Revolution, but they gave a black guy to people and everyone felt all right". Do u remember South Park episode, when government at young America decided to have as much wars as possible to became "stronger", but to allow people to go on demonstrations? Very ironic…</p> <p>I always thought that Samarai is like Knight (Security?) of Senior with specific The Code of Honour. Ninja were basicalдy without such The Code (used to say "without honour") or were "Fallen Samurai"(like Daimyo was killed, but Harakiri wasn't done by Samurai).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-974472</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-974472</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 05:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Nononono. It's not that democratization marches on- It's that corrupt corporate fascism marches on. Don't confuse the two. There are plenty that do still deserve defense, as well. Innocent children, for example; Or the teachers fighting to keep their jobs to teach children properly, instead of classes being shunted into 4 day weeks with ~45 people classes. Also note that Bush was elected to government because of Clinton's 'immoral' behaviour, causing people to panic. He professed to be heading towards a more moral America, and they gobbled it up. There's sadly a LOT more rules, usually hidden just out of sight, in the US than there are in the old USSR. And they're all based on restricting or removing freedoms, while giving the appearance of granting them. Honestly it would be for the best if the US collapsed under its own weight, and had to rebuild itself. It's old, bloated, and corrupt from the inside out.</p> <p>As for ninja: The idea that most were little more than hired assassins is false, in actuality; Most served a Daimyo much like the Samurai did. They just served from the shadows… Much like spies do in today's society. It was a simpler time, when it was not so law-entangled a thing to feud or kill. As for your calling them defenders- actually, it is true. Often they would be acting in defense of their Daimyo's interests, making sure his position of power was stable.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-974194</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-974194</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 22:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It isn't that bad that this reference is medieval. Bad that this is Utopian. Nowadays people are very selfish, wanna have all and doing nothing. Studiing at university just to get diploma, not for knowledge or vocation. Wanna drink alcohol, dance, f***, sleep, eat and laugh on stupid shows, films, etc. Nobody wanna defence smb. Nobody deserves defence. World is cruel. "Democratization" marches. At Soviet Union much more attention of government and education system was on moral. "Do this(be kind, healthy, clever, etc.) 'cuz this is good." There were not "Do as u wanna, just do not kill anyone xP" with hidden system of manipulation, as it exist today… All is not so bad as I've said in my country (Belarus), but if all will be changing in such "west" manner, everyone will forget about all good that is considered with the word Paladin… It will be used as synonym of the word Fanatic…</p> <p>Maybe that's why I prefer positions of east culture, like Shinobi. They were like Hitmans centuries ago, but this romantic image of Noble Attacker, that kill killers(Evil Shinobies), like anti-killers, that is telling at Naruto series, is really awesome. U can name them defenders, but this is question of semantics: glass is half-filled or half-empty? ^_^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-974136</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-974136</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 21:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Kudos on the achievements. Except for R00t (which if done at S4 only gives cause for silly bragging rights of "I did it safest and most expensive") I've done all of the above myself. It's not that big a deal.</p> <p>However, calling defense cowardice is truly arrogant of you. Cowardice is the lack of courage in facing danger, pain, or difficulty, or in short, the lack of courage; which is in turn defined as the state or quality of mind or spirit that enables one to face danger, fear, or vicissitudes with self-possession, confidence, and resolution. Defense and cowardice are two completely disparate concepts that share no commonalities. Oft it is the defender who stands at the fore of a battle, be it wits, words, or brawn, and protects his or her chosen charge: usually a person or multiple persons, or an abstract concept such as peace, or a nobler concept such as that of a Knight's Oath, or multiple charges through a more general concept of obligation, such as a chivalrous person might find themselves in if, for example, a woman was endangered. They have no personal stock in that woman, however their chivalrous nature would dictate that they champion that cause (that of freeing the damsel in distress).</p> <p>Truly, the defender is far more brave than any attacker, for they must strive not only to protect their charge in a physical sense, but spiritually and mentally as well. It is always the Paladin that falls last, having defended his compatriots to the last, rattling breath he draws before passing on. While the terminology above illustrates a medieval setting rather than contemporary, it's still applicable.</p> <p>There are more modern examples, but I am tired, and cannot think of one. I'll leave it at this.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-971067</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-971067</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 14:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sicilian_defense">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sicilian_defense</a> "…giving it more codes than any other opening…" (referes to ECO score system)</p> <p>"The best defence is a good offence"<br /> ( "Meanings and Origins of Phrases, Sayings and Idioms". Gary Martin. <a href="http://www.phrases.org.uk/meanings/proverbs.html">http://www.phrases.org.uk/meanings/proverbs.html</a>. )</p> <p>I often think about defence like about сowardice, like "Oh, I 120% can't do this!". When I attack I prove my bravery, at least for maself. Self-expression is in activity. Via est vita! Game is for fun but it has it's own philosophy…</p> <p>I made OOT as s1(before tacos) and got 4.2-4.3 millions and was 3rd between ALL runners this day (1st and 2nd were about 4.3-4.4 and far stronger than me).<br /> I made Burger Ninja as s1.<br /> I finished ALL Wasteland as s3(with runes).<br /> I got "golden quests" items via ranking at s1-s4, others got from story pages at s4.<br /> I finished Root(with revenge) as s4.<br /> Mono awaites for Eclipse at ma s5 :)<br /> And also much of minor …<br /> This is like ma Bushidō… Defence is wise, good, blablabla… But only as a rest before killing strike!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-970936</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-970936</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 09:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>No, the best defense is a good defense. I'll direct you to Clausewitz, who spoke of it originally, and from which we have dummied down and in fact -perverted- the truth of it. Defense is the stronger principle. <a href="http://www.au.af.mil/au/awc/awcgate/clauswtz/clwt000e.htm">http://www.au.af.mil/au/awc/awcgate/clauswtz/clwt000e.htm</a></p> <p>It's not the offensive line that gets the best players in American Football, after all. It's the defensive line, whose job it is is to stifle the opposing offense, wearing them down without gaining any distance. Or the offensive wrestler or boxer that gets the advantage of the defensive one. You let your opponent wear themselves out on your defense and then counterattack in their moment of weakness. Certainly you see the really offensive fighters obliterate their opponents a lot- but for the most part they're fighting someone who is also an offensive fighter, and they simply out-aggression their opponent. If you watch the really talented, wily boxers- the ones who've been around for awhile and are still active people, because they haven't taken much damage and haven't been debilitated by what they have taken- who utilize techniques like Ali's famous rope-a-dope to tire out Foreman. Certainly in some games, like Soccer and Basketball, it's more meritous to have the ball in the opponent's field all the time- However, it can be easily argued that the skills required to do so involve defense, in the sense of retaining control of the ball- again, relating to fighting on your terms, not theirs. Or, to use a more contemporary example: Keigo's win in a SFIII tournament. <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xSGW7CwD5GM">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xSGW7CwD5GM</a> Repeated parries into a monstrous counterattack.</p> <p>As for the awesome: I stated that he's been trying to balance them now. Apparently my definition of "now" is far broader than most though. Go back a year, a year and a half ago and you'll see a lot more imbalance in effect. Not that it was necessarily a bad thing. It kept people eyeing it wondering when they'd get more to get that one more ability, keeping interest in the game.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-969060</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-969060</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 12:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Last half a year I looked through Awesome list time to time for planning and never saw such a 5 point disballance. And this 1 point trophy is also a very good joke, but McM's :)<br /> P.S. The best defense is offence.<br /> P.P.S. <a href="http://www.animecubed.com/billy/forum/memberlist.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;u=75">http://www.animecubed.com/billy/forum/memberlist.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;u=75</a> xD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-968662</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-968662</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2011 22:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That is not correct. First off, there is the 1 point trophy for reaching S111. Secondly, there have been MANY cases in the past where there has been an uneven number of awesome. In fact back before WKai and PW and the Festival et al, a lot of people were eagerly awaiting more content so they could round off their waiting awesome and pick up a new ability. Just because he's been trying to balance them now doesn't mean it's been as such in the past; There's also the simple possibility that there's another hidden trophy somewhere (assuming this to be a real one in this case) that would have equalled it out.</p> <p>Again, the initial "joke" of causing people to scramble for an answer was funny. The end comment directed at everyone in general? Rather offensive.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-967763</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-967763</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 16:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>NB! : ALL AWESOME ABILITIES ARE ROUND! (ends with zero) When 5 APoints trophy created, there is another to do 5+5=10. :)</p> <p>And this is GREAT practical joke :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-967713</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-967713</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2011 15:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Then he should have put something in showcasing it wasn't real. It's rather obvious that when people see something like that, -made very deliberately in an attempt to pass it off as a real achievement-, that they will want to know about it- Especially when it comes to something as high-profile as Awesome for purpose of buying abilities, and for ranking up (among the competative). A good example of it done right is the "turn undead" action picture that someone has, that specifically has a label available (either immediately visible or behind a spoiler tag) that those curious can check to see if it is real and not just something they've missed before.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-966025</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-966025</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 14:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I don't think, that those "fyi…" words were a joke. I think they were "Cry of a soul" - equal spam is SO annoying… Yer, rude way, but souls are different and I understand him partly and respect him for his "basic" idea :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-965863</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-965863</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 08:12:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The joke of the trophy, I liked. The "fyi it's a joke you morons" bit? Not so much. He could have been much more nice about it. In my opinion, that ruined the funniness of the gag trophy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-964964</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-964964</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>He-he :) His joke (I really liked it ^_^ ) made his mailbox full of spam :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-964957</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-964957</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 10:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The "Fyi it's a joke you clowns" did not exist when the question was initially asked via this forum. He must have added it afterwards because of many people asking him if such a trophy actually exists.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-964239</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-964239</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 16:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://www.animecubed.com/billy/forum/memberlist.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;u=2452">http://www.animecubed.com/billy/forum/memberlist.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;u=2452</a></p> <p>And NB this words in signature: "(fyi it's a joke you clowns)"<br /> P.S. Just remembered: When I was s1 genin/chunin by mistake I did as this "trophy" says and no effect :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-963975</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-963975</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 06:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Source or confirmation?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-963677</guid>
				<title>Re: Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-963677</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's not a real trophy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393#post-963209</guid>
				<title>Om Nom Trophy?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-295393/om-nom-trophy#post-963209</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 10:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As the summary says, FairyGuy has the trophy shot on his Forum Signature on the official forums saying he earned it 12/11/10. It states "You Bargletronned before you Nommed". Is this a real trophy, and if so, is it obtained by simply using the Bargletron before you eat anything that day?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>