<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Glowslinging&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Glowslinging&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1866146</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1866146</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 04:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>dreamgor</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1513115</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>@Chiller: Yes, that's no longer true. I can confirm this. However you used to lose the streak when you got the Nailbiter bonus. It happened to me but I can't confirm that.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1865977</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1865977</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 23:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Chiller</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Getting the Nailbiter bonus (finishing a fight with 2 or less HP) also makes you lose your streak.</p> <p>Not true! You only lose the streak when u win with negative life (when u and enemy have negative life, u win the game, but your streak vanishes).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1499408</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1499408</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 05:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Following instructions: +100 xp!<br /> Reading the label lvl 0<br /> Experimenting lvl 0<br /> Ingenuity lvl 0</p> <p>[S1 goes &quot;Wiki, how do I get Deadly Rave?&quot; and it tells them. S1 asks Deft the same question and he says &quot;It's the same as a simple FA + SoS&quot;]</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1499228</guid>
				<title>Deadly Rave conversation</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1499228</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2012 01:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Dracos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1197540</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Deft teaching newbs new tricks :)</p> <p>Dee (Lusty Village) &quot;I must've already found the first 3, but didn't write them down so, no good. Oh well. *nods* I get it now. I'll pass it onto the wiki too so there's something there.&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:07 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;But it could say 3 into, yes&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:06 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;It's the same as a simple FA + SoS&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:06 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;Yep&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:05 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;Fang of emptiness I think the EX thing is..&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:05 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Dee (Lusty Village) &quot;If I go GC-GC-FA (SoS) and get 1, then I know it starts with FA?&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:05 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;You know it's the first 4 (since there will be two FAs)&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:03 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;The wiki has no experience or opinion. S1 goes &quot;Wiki, how do I get emo3?&quot; and it tells them. S1 asks Deft the same question and I say &quot;Don't bother with him in s1&quot;&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:03 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Dee (Lusty Village) &quot;so if I use GC-GC-FA (and SoS) and get 3 bit, I know that's the first 3?&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:03 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Dee (Lusty Village) &quot;*laughs* I'll put it on there when I understand it. *reads and thinks over* Hmmm.&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:02 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Tyr (Shoukyaku Village) &quot;Hm? Don't let it interrupt your explanation, but I'd be curious to know why. I find it a valuable resource, if lacking sometimes.&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:02 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;You just continue in that fashion, rememberring that no move will be used twice. So take off all damage mods and drop back a turf and you might even get it in 1 fight. Also that EX move that uses HP but gives EX&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:02 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;Not a freaking chance. Do not like the wiki&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:01 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;Okay! So you're looking x into a 10 bit gambit! So let's say you use FA and SoS and don't get that. Your first move isn't FA. You then try AC and it says 1 into 10! So you know your first move. Now do AC AC and something else like&#8230; FA and SoS and it might say 3 into a 10 bit gambit&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:01 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Tyr (Shoukyaku Village) &quot;Put it on the wiki and then you'd never have to do it again. Just direct 'em there.&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:00 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;(Yay explaining sound of silence&#8230; Don't I love doing this XD)&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;7:00 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Dee (Lusty Village) &quot;Well, I have a couple of times, but not sure what to make of what it tells me?&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;6:59 PM<br /> #</p> <p>The Deftblade &quot;Use sound of silence and you can get it in one day :)&quot;</p> <p>2012-07-04&#160;6:56 PM<br /> #</p> <p>Dee (Lusty Village) &quot;Hey Deft, any advice on getting Deadly Rave? Gonna spend then next 3-4 days on trying to find it, so I can do the last miku on saturday.&quot;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1347591</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1347591</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 23:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovenant</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>644535</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually, what it does is give you 20% bonus talent if you use Kin Goku Satsu, instead of getting just normal talent for a perfect victory, as PV and KGS null each others' talent bonus/loss. Thus it can be useful in that respect for being able to finish battles very quickly without losing a lot of talent for it, esp. when you haven't defeated the boss and need to farm.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1346109</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1346109</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 07:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>taltamir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>663175</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thanks for the info. Using final stage uses up a slot without making you stronger, meaning a perfect victory is LESS likely to occur.<br /> It does guarantee a nail-biter as you say though. However there is no point to ever using it. If you are CERTAIN of a perfect victory then you should be fighting in a stronger turf for more talent. And losing costs 3/4 (multiplicative not additive) of the talent&#8230; At the absolute best 10% extra gives you extra 100 talent (on portal of awesome) due to being 10% of base talent. and it would be insanity to use it there since the enemy has an ex ability that drains 1HP from you even if it fails to hit and it uses it often.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1280385</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1280385</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 14:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Perfect Victories (Take 0 damage) give +50% Talent, and Nail-Biter Victories (Win with 2 or fewer HP) give +10% Talent, and if you win with Final Stage on, you're guaranteed to get both of these bonuses.</p> <p>It's not a joke, it's just not very useful.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1280382</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1280382</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>taltamir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>663175</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Final Stage sets my HP to 1, but not enemies. I tried it on Parking Lot's boss and a regular encounter on Rickety Bridge. Both had their full HP while I had 1 (even with autogaurd btw).</p> <p>Is this a joke ability? Does it actually have a use?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1242687</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1242687</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 23:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It just means that the talent bonus only occurs when the item is equipped/active. Though since none of the 11k abilities count for your total slots, no idea why you would unequip any of them o_O</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1242676</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1242676</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 23:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Might sound a bit ambiguous but believe me it's permanent, all skills are (well, they're not active when you don't equip them, but they stay available)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1242674</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1242674</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 23:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Andrew1716</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>615346</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>For the item My Horse Is Amazing +20% Talent for this match (does not count towards total slots), does the &quot;this match&quot; part mean you only get it for 1 match?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1188170</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1188170</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 18:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes, and since they don't take up slots, most of them should be bought as soon as possible (LBW, 9 lives, Avalon, Excalibur)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1188132</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1188132</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 17:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Agent Inari</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>392886</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have a question about the Abilities your allies teach to you (the ones that cost 11k Talent and don't count for Ab slots). I assume that they are permanent skills that don't go away after one battle (unlike the one-shots you can buy at Mahjong and Hanafuda), am I right?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1187353</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1187353</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 16:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yea PL boss is really hard. Fighting in Rooftops and then Rickety Bridge is not a bad idea because they give you more xp. And when you have no choice but to grind levels, more xp is a good thing.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1187255</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1187255</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 11:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Btw Rooftops seems like much easier than Parking Lot O_O with level 5(+1+1) in all battle stats I cannot beat Parking Lot boss, but in few blows path through Rooftops opponents. What do u think about it, guys?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1177542</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1177542</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 04:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I wasn't really saying that anyone disagreed with that first part, more giving my rationale behind it.</p> <p>And I've been in parking lot for awhile, but then again, before GS came out, I was getting quite good exp simply from the main event bonus. It took me awhile after I got to PL to beat the rave, but I can confirm it is indeed possible. But I've got lvl 4's in most rave skills anyways. Most likely I was just slower in progressing on GS than I was in the main Con.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1177353</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1177353</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 23:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I agree with jimwormmaster, though I understand neither why he speaks as if anyone disagreed with his earlier claim that one should go to the rave post-gs for free duels weekly (which he now appears to second), nor why he entertains the idea that anyone would have beaten the rave by the time they get to Parking Lot.</p> <p>(Here's my reasoning on that last one. GS was released 5 months ago. Beating the rave without high dance and FO requires many level 4 rave skills, but rising star/glowslinger -i.e. unlocking gs- requires only level 3s. Assuming the subject unlocked GS as soon as possible and progressed at a decent speed, beating the rave with high dance and FO way above PL levels should come well before getting eough levels in the conventional rave skills.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1176573</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1176573</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 05:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Risk only activates if you've used that move before. So, you can get one more use of each of the 5 moves without factoring in risk. Kinda useless&#8230;if you do it right, your risk won't be high enough to matter much anyways. And I second using the rave for GS fights, especially if you've already gotten Fateful Encounter. Even if you're only at the parking lot, you can get 200+ talent per fight, easy. So that's like&#8230;400-800 talent, at least? Hard to get that much glowslinging exp, though flipping out is easy, same goes for dance. But good luck getting that much in the attack skills in a day, much less 4 hours!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1176571</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1176571</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 05:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Plus a lot of the skills that are usually available during that time are pretty easy to get too. Thus, if there's nothing you're hunting, do the Rave. Then you can save your talent for GS attacks and abilities.</p> <p>Also, what in the nine hells does Flashy Thing actually -do-? it says it sets move uses to zero, but- does that mean it makes it so your ex combo setup is reset? or what?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1174038</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1174038</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Though once you have fateful encounter, and thus you've pretty much beaten billycon other than glowslinging, the rave is definitely better, for 2-4 extra fights that day. At that point, you're probably at least at the parking lot, so you could get like 1k talent or so in that 4 fights.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1174004</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1174004</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 19:48:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I disagree. Doubled rewards for 4 hours is almost certainly more valuable than 4 cool and 600xp between some pretty common skills, and then the fact that two of them are actually GS skills. If you're using glowslinging skills at levels that would carry you through beating the rave then 200xp is minor. Also, Posing is one of the easiest rave-non-gs skills to level up to 4.<br /> BillyCon Hours would be much better spent getting double xp from panels.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1173266</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1173266</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Tactics thinger should be added somewhere; Not sure. If you have already gotten Glowslinger and are Glowslinging, spend the time to go to the Rave and just get the award for Excellent, until your level up dance/flipping out/posing until you get the Fateful Encounter.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1145947</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1145947</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>WingedCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>57091</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Check the Billy Idol page. Those bosses are over there.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1105316</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1105316</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 03:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DrBilly</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>779419</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Upon defeating the MemoryMiku, this text appears:</p> <p>The MikuMiku slumps as you connect with a direct strike, slicing her in two. She looks back at you, closes her eyes, and - smiles? - as she unravels, digital light and echoes of music that never completely go away..</p> <p>Congratulations!</p> <p>You have received Glissando!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1054871</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1054871</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 17:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Not sure where exactly we'd put this, but I'm thinking we should put the ally level-up messages somewhere. For starters, Bruce Sr's to lvl 2 is</p> <p>Bruce Sr. watches your form, and wants to help improve it!</p> <p>I forgot to note down Mr Smith's, and I'm not up to the others yet…but I thought I'd help where I could.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1053338</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1053338</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 02:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Can we get some cleanup done for Glowslinging, bringing everything to individual pages, and a guide being written by someone experienced with it? This page is suffering the same thing that the main BillyCon page is suffering.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1048148</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1048148</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DrBilly</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>We don't have the blurbs for fighting the BillyCon MikuMiku anywhere on the site, it seems. I'll post it here so some enterprising fellow can put it where it belongs.</p> <p>The other MikuMiku fall to the wayside, and allow you to battle one-on-one with a single opponent.</p> <p>She looks you up and down. "How can you still Hear? your kind have been cut away for as long as We can remember. Even those few that remain are but wraiths holding on to the lost, but you.." Her eyes gleam.</p> <p>"You still Sing."</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1029809</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1029809</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 05:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You asssume incorrectly. It only sets the person with it to 1 HP.</p> <p>But, hey, look at it this way. If you win the match, you're guaranteed both a Perfect Victory bonus AND a Nailbiter bonus. for an additional 60% Talent.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1023716</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1023716</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 19:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So I'm assuming that Final Stage sets both you and your opponent to 1 HP… Wouldn't it be vest to use this in every fight combined with some +levels items or abilitys? Especially against bosses with like 50 HP?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1014305</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1014305</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 13:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Skarn22</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>372883</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay, I just added a bunch of stuffs to the areas tab, since it didn't seem to really fit anywhere else: The enemies' base HP, changed base levels to level range, what mikumiku abilities and what EX attacks they have. This is necessary information for someone who wants to plan out their strategy. However, I mainly went off of memory, so I didn't fill out every field and there's about a 90% chance that at least one thing I put was wrong &gt;_&gt; cut me some slack, here! :P But anyway, I wouldn't trust the information there 100% until it's been confirmed( the ?s removed).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1012382</guid>
				<title>Banner</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1012382</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 04:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>tressert</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>206985</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Did anyone happen to grab the splash banner for this? If you did, you should include it in the files.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-1006595</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-1006595</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 17:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>socrates</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's Deadly Rave, not Killer Rave. Unless that varies form person to person too, but everyone else I've seen that has gotten it calls it Deadly Rave too.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-998545</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-998545</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 03:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Skarn22</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>372883</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Silly is correct. However, the point is to get at LEAST the required amount.What I mean to say is there is no real difference between scoring 1600 and 4999. Your goal, then, is to bring your score up to at least 1600(for glowslinger). I changed the formatting to say that, it should be fine now I think.</p> <p>Oh yeah, and, um. I did some other stuff too. Hope you guys like it &gt;_&gt;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-997332</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-997332</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 22:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Silly</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"The Light Fantastic is the third step: in order to finish the quest, you'll need to either have The Glow, or the Glowslinger permanent effect, which you can get at the Rave by getting 1600-3199 Excellence."</p> <p>Should be 1600-4999 Excellence</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-981632</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-981632</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2011 22:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>anon</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Was a bit bugged today and ended up against 3rd boss in idol, forgot to copy name but stats are 11/11/11/11/11 with 20 HP and a skill that does +5 to its spin</p> <p>Second boss drop is Semiquaver it gives 20% discount to dealers room purchases</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-971900</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-971900</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 06:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Shien</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>548531</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I somehow didn't even notice that my order was still sequential. That's probably right, then.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-970989</guid>
				<title>Gambits</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-970989</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 12:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Conster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>415429</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I tried getting a Gambit with random order, ending with WR, but didn't get it. On the other hand, I got Denouement for FA/GC/TP/WR/AC and for GC/TP/WR/AC/FA, and Crescendo for GC/FA/AC/WR/TP, so my guess is it's simply about sequential or counter-sequential order, and the start skill doesn't matter.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-969486</guid>
				<title>Gambits</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-969486</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 21:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Shien</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>548531</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The info for Crescendo and Denouement is wrong.</p> <p>I'm not entirely sure, but I'm guessing that all you have to do is use all 5 attacks and end with Wake-Up Reversal for Crescendo, or all 5 attacks ending with Alpha Cancel for Denouement.</p> <p>I know I've gotten Crescendo with TP/GC/FA/AC/WR, and Denouement with FA/GC/TP/WR/AC.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472#post-969254</guid>
				<title>Turf Bosses (Bully)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-296472/glowslinging#post-969254</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 17:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Does anyone know if the stats for bosses are random or set? Here's the stats of the Bully (Playground Boss) when I fought him:</p> <p>Bully<br /> HP: 8<br /> Skills: AC: 3 FA: 2 GC: 3 TP: 3 WR: 3<br /> Items/Abilities: Poi Cables</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>