<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Tags</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Tags&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:14:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012#post-986504</guid>
				<title>Re: Tags</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags#post-986504</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 18:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>North</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>132728</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/sam510" ><!--[if gte IE 7]><!--><img class="small" src="http://www.wikidot.com/common--images/avatars/358/358542/a16.png" alt="Sam510" style="background-image:url(http://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=358542)" /><!--<![endif]--><!--[if lt IE 7]><img class="small" src="http://www.wikidot.com/common&#45;&#45;images/avatars/358/358542/a16.png" alt="Sam510" style="filter:progid:DXImageTransform.Microsoft.AlphaImageLoader(src=http://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=358542,sizingMethod='scale')"/><![endif]--></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/sam510" >Sam510</a></span> is right. We will only use generic tags. That is the point of tags for that matter.</p> <p><strong>Tags examples:</strong></p> <ul> <li>item</li> <li>quest</li> <li>mission</li> <li>potion</li> </ul> <p>Tags with the name of the item are useless. I spent some time at one point to purge the tags list of them. If you search for something you can very well use the search box. There is no need to add 2 useless tags to it. It pollutes the tag cloud.</p> <p>Thank you for your contributions.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012#post-986312</guid>
				<title>Re: Tags</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags#post-986312</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 15:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Adding "Sharktooth" as a tag doesn't help people find the Sharktooth Necklace. One can easily find the Sharktooth Necklace by entering "Sharktooth" into the search box on the upper right, even without its getting its own tag.</p> <p>There is also no particular utility in tagging all the necklaces in-game, though I will grant that if somebody were to tag <em>all</em> of them, it might have some value as trivia.</p> <p>Tags are useful for categorization, for finding other members of a set. Tagging all eight Lost Weapons (and no other items) "lost-weapon" can be of use for those trying to get them all. On the other hand, adding "Jet" and "Set" as separate tags for Soundless Jade, as you have just done, certainly doesn't help anybody find that item. Tagging Book of the Twillight "lost-weapon," as you did the other day, is outright misleading, as it's nothing of the sort; as seen in the text for the Cursed Wave trophy, there are only eight of those. All superfluous tags do is add clutter and make the tag system less useful, making it harder to find the signal amongst the noise.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012#post-985823</guid>
				<title>Re: Tags</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags#post-985823</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 02:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>richie17</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>144602</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ideals made by players are not all alike. We all have different ideals on what to tag and if a tag pertains to one item then let it be there, you should only remove a tag if it is incorrect, in this case it is correct to assume someone would type those words and the tag will pop up that item, or remove a tag if it contains inappropriate wording.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012#post-985812</guid>
				<title>Re: Tags</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags#post-985812</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 02:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>richie17</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>144602</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Tags are used to be able to find such items or things. "Necklace" may be used for other items too. ex)Necklace of the First HoCage, Sharktooth Necklace, and 11DBHK's Gold Necklace.</p> <p>This website is used to help people throught bvs, this means while even thought adding "Sharktooth" was not consistent to you, it helps people with the tag of Sharktooth since it is part of the item's name.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012#post-985746</guid>
				<title>Tags</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-303012/tags#post-985746</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 00:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The use of tags around the wiki is inconsistent at the moment, but I think it's safe to say that if a given tag is being used for only one page, the tag shouldn't be used at all. (e.g., there is no reason why "Sharktooth Necklace" would be tagged "sharktooth" or "necklace")</p> <p>In general, I'd be inclined to stick with making the use of existing tags more consistent, rather than adding new ones wholesale. (e.g., if you notice that most trophies have the "trophy" tag, and one is missing it, go ahead and add it)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>