<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:23:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1069973</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1069973</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 23:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is why I never bothered to try and reapply for forum privledges. Mod who was involved in the issue was the one that banned AND was given a thumbs up for it by McM, blatantly breaking his own rules? Yeah, no. You set your rules as a legal code, you follow them yourself. /endrant</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1003702</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1003702</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 09:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>EDIT: wait… if they're going to question comments here, never mind</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002454</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002454</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 22:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ednari</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <img src="http://i96.photobucket.com/albums/l193/ednarimal/whateveryousay.jpg" alt="whateveryousay.jpg" class="image" /><br /> this is the warning i received and, honestly, i'm surprised <p>not only am i being told that the post on the bvs forum really didn't break any rules and that my original statement is a lie(which is blatantly untrue, as the prior 'unofficial forum' thread degenerated into "we want to talk without being told it's drama" in something like 2 posts, i can't check as it was deleted), i'm being warned about OTHER PEOPLE'S POSTS, which says to me that even if my original post here said "bunnies and kittens and let's make an unofficial forum somewhere" i'd still have been warned if drama ensued</p> <p>does the "no drama" rule allows a moderator's power to extend across the vast stretches of the internet to sites they have no control over, even though my edited post was written specifically stating that there be no drama on the official forums, and had been respected as no posts were made there?</p> <p>i don't even see a reason to try to appeal because evidently, as fax stated, it had to have gone through multiple moderators to get a warning, so multiple people thought drama anywhere was well within their jurisdiction to deal with</p> <p>i just don't know anymore, i guess if i want bvs to be fun i can stick to just the game, seems to be the only option at this point, since even if a new forum is founded and advertised the first time a drama thread comes along the mods will consider it their duty to harass people on the official forum about it</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002139</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002139</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>But on a good note you can stop trolling my threads since I won't be making anymore right, you and CN sure did like being my internet stalker sorry I ruined your hobby.</p> </blockquote> <p>I can honestly say I have no idea what you're talking about.</p> <p>"Moderating people who receive significant numbers of reports" is not "stalking."</p> <p>The CN hasn't been anything, official or otherwise, in a long time.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002131</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002131</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 16:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>portwizard</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>181794</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>But on a good note you can stop trolling my threads since I won't be making anymore right, you and CN sure did like being my internet stalker sorry I ruined your hobby.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002121</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002121</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 16:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>If you want to apply rules strictly, apply them to everyone equally.</p> </blockquote> <p>Again, how are you certain this this is not currently the case?</p> <blockquote> <p>Dramallama became so subjective that it is just used to warn certain people (or avoid warning), thus preferential. I'm not saying this could be intentional, just not equal for everyone.</p> </blockquote> <p>Evidence?</p> <blockquote> <p>But still, I don't know how the hell you considered that thread being a case of dramallama, when (almost) the same thing was posted in another thread several minutes earlier (Super fail Super jack thread).</p> </blockquote> <p>The other thread was "I got sniped, this sucks." Portwizard's thread was "I sniped some dude twice, ha ha. Also am I a horrible person y/n?" Either you say no, and the person who got sniped gets pissed and starts drama, or you say yes and are flaming. There is no correct answer to this question that cannot end in a warning for one or more people. As such, it was moderated as it fit under the dramamongering clause.</p> <blockquote> <p>If you read the "Stuff that goes in here" thread made by EvilTaxi, which describes the Juice Bar subforum (in which portwizard posted), you'll see that something is wrong in the decision the mods made.</p> </blockquote> <p>"Bragging" is different than "ha ha you suck I'm going to rub your nose in it." "Bragging" is "Hey look, I have fifteen thousand stamina today," not "Man I love picking on people."</p> <blockquote> <p>Being a player means you can relate to other players, and most likely, at some point they started some drama, flaming, other nasty stuff. This means they should be able to differentiate between serious/intentional drama and possible future drama, after a couple of posts.</p> </blockquote> <p>Again, how are you certain this this is not currently the case? How can you possibly know what is going on in someone else's mind (unless you have latent psychic powers you're not telling anyone about)? You don't know the reasoning behind a warning, you don't know all the warnings that are given out, and you don't know how many reports are passed over and dismissed as they're not an issue. There are ten—TEN—active moderators/administrators who hand out warnings and/or ban individuals. Some of them are more on-the-ball about getting to reports faster than others, but each of them are held to the same standard and follows the same guidelines.</p> <p>There is no way to remove subjectivity from the moderation process, but we do confer with other moderators before nearly every warning that is not cut-and-dried. And when I say 'cut-and-dried', I mean stuff like bumping a thread in Village Relations before 7 days: it is a rule violation and there is no way it cannot be one. Flaming, trolling, dramamongering, and similar, subjective, content-related posts never fall into this category and are looked at by several moderators before a conclusion is reached. In many instances, a post is edited, the offending material is removed, and a verbal warning is given out if the poster does not have any existing outstanding warnings, coupled with a note to reread the forum rules. Repeat offenders are assumed to have reread the rules and are not given such grace.</p> <blockquote> <p>The difference is similar to thinking about Bromance literally and internet-y. You'll understand my point, I hope.</p> </blockquote> <p>I see your point. Unfortunately, a moderator cannot afford to err in favor of a poster and must instead rely on the rules, particularly when the poster in question already has several warnings (both expired and active). Relying in favor of a repeat-offending poster leads to people pushing the line further and further back. It leads to people taking advantage of loopholes and exploiting administrative trust.</p> <p>You don't get a final warning out of the blue: you have to have a history of violations in order to acquire one.</p> <blockquote> <p>I'm not touching that forum again.</p> </blockquote> <p>Your presence and your time are your own: use them as you will. But if you spend it on my forum, you have to play by my rules.</p> <blockquote> <p>Btw, fax, did you get a warning for your "incitation to baw" with your "topic wrote: baw baw badwdiwwity baw" thingy?. I'm just curious, cuz i reported you for that one.</p> </blockquote> <p>I got a stern talking to and a note on my file, yes. This is worse than a warning: having bossman angry at you is not a pleasant time. Don't for one moment think that the administration has free reign: we, like any other player, have guidelines we have to follow, and in many cases ours are stricter than others.</p> <p>What it really boils down to is respect: people who repeatedly start drama, troll, and flame on my forum have no respect for my administration and the administration of the other moderators, have no respect for the other users of the forum, have no respect for the rules of posting laid out by the administration to promote what they find to be an optimal environment, and have no respect for the amicable place that the forum is supposed to be.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002075</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002075</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ba2</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm not touching that forum again.</p> <p>Btw, fax, did you get a warning for your "incitation to baw" with your "topic wrote: baw baw badwdiwwity baw" thingy?. I'm just curious, cuz i reported you for that one.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002018</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002018</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>portwizard</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>181794</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>FYI before you go thinking I told my personal story? You'd be right I did but I didn't tell my half I logged the whole thing for my village to see just as it happened.</p> <p>So the anger here isn't simply about ednari's post, and wow blue you had been quite about it until now.</p> <p>Don't forget you got me on Yahoo bub :P I'll try to log in to that more often.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1002001</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1002001</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you start quoting from my post, please don't use just the convenient sentences.</p> <blockquote> <p>Preferential treatment defeats the reason of rules in the first place.</p> </blockquote> <p>If you want to apply rules strictly, apply them to everyone equally.</p> <p>Dramallama became so subjective that it is just used to warn certain people (or avoid warning), thus preferential. I'm not saying this could be intentional, just not equal for everyone.</p> <p>But still, I don't know how the hell you considered that thread being a case of dramallama, when (almost) the same thing was posted in another thread several minutes earlier (Super fail Super jack thread).</p> <p>If you read the "Stuff that goes in here" thread made by EvilTaxi, which describes the Juice Bar subforum (in which portwizard posted), you'll see that something is wrong in the decision the mods made.<br /> [edut]</p> <blockquote> <p>Somewhere along the line, the mods seem to have forgotten that they were also players and they were also breaking such rules.</p> </blockquote> <p>Being a player means you can relate to other players, and most likely, at some point they started some drama, flaming, other nasty stuff. This means they <span style="text-decoration: underline;">should be</span> able to differentiate between serious/intentional drama and <span style="text-decoration: underline;">possible future drama, after a couple of posts</span>.<br /> The difference is similar to thinking about Bromance literally and internet-y. You'll understand my point, I hope.</p> <p>[edut2] I'm writing this in the breaks I take from work. I didn't forget you, don't worry… I'm just too tired to check who's on, usually.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001951</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001951</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>i fail to see how ednari's post did this. This is bullshit and a half</p> </blockquote> <p>Linking to content that violates the forum rules or the Animecubed TOS falls under the purview of the rules. The removal of said link, then, is the result, and the posted reason is the moderator in question's reasoning (protip: it isn't me).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001950</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001950</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 12:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>If the mod is involved personally in the conflict, he should not be able to do anything regarding the conflict and let a 3rd party make a decision with objectivity (not subjectivity). A good example of 3rd party would be all the mods to brainstorm and decide who's being wrong, or McM dealing with it.</p> </blockquote> <p>And what, pray tell, makes you believe that this isn't the case?</p> <blockquote> <p>Somewhere along the line, the mods seem to have forgotten that they were also players and they were also breaking such rules.</p> </blockquote> <p>Uh, according to what? The rules are posted at the top of every forum. If you cannot follow them, you get a warning. Get enough warnings, you are banned. Pretty straightforward, and pretty much the rules of near any forum.</p> <p>The rules boil down to three things, anyway. "Don't be a dick"; "don't do anything illegal"; and "follow the Animecubed TOS".</p> <p>Most of the time, the mods are merely responding to reports that other, non-moderator users are submitting via the Report button in the corner. Generally, though, if someone who isn't a moderator thinks you're rulebreaking, a mod is going to as well.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001941</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001941</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ba2</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"This post was removed by a moderator.<br /> Reason: Drama, flaming, false information, failure to follow rules for disputing moderator action.<br /> If you'd like to plan and launch your own forum, feel free to do so (here or elsewhere) in a way that doesn't involve personal attacks or other violations of the rules."</p> <p>i fail to see how ednari's post did this. This is bullshit and a half</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001807</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001807</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 06:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Godlike law of forums: Mods are always right, end of story.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001792</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001792</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 06:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If the mod is involved personally in the conflict, he should not be able to do anything regarding the conflict and let a 3rd party make a decision with objectivity (not subjectivity). A good example of 3rd party would be all the mods to brainstorm and decide who's being wrong, or McM dealing with it.</p> <p>Somewhere along the line, the mods seem to have forgotten that they were also players and they were also breaking such rules. Acting all high and mighty now just mean they're hypocrites.<br /> Preferential treatment defeats the reason of rules in the first place.</p> <p>If they're not being objective. they do not have the right to place warnings.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001752</guid>
				<title>Re: OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001752</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 04:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>portwizard</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>181794</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>lmao they seriously deleted the post about an un-official Forum? pricks to the end, but fair warning the owners/admins of the Wiki normally ban those that don't follow McM's request so I wouldn't discuss this here either, wow BVS down hill fast.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001688</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001688</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 02:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ba2</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i'll poke someone this week, its really gettin annoying…., i dont like to reread 10 time what i write everytime i post there ¬¬.</p> <p>Also, 1 more warn and i'm banned xD ( i lol'd )</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806#post-1001677</guid>
				<title>OMG FINE, UN-official forum discussion</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-307806/omg-fine-un-official-forum-discussion#post-1001677</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 02:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ednari</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>since we can't even talk about talking somewhere else on the official forum without bashing into the "dramallamaing" filter, let's do it here</p> <p>please, someone find a better alternative quickly</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>