<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Big Shammy Lvl 2</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561/big-shammy-lvl-2</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Big Shammy Lvl 2&quot; - Something missing from his page.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:32:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561#post-1159090</guid>
				<title>Re: Big Shammy Lvl 2</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561/big-shammy-lvl-2#post-1159090</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 11:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>All is right, bro, the most players know this and even if not this effects are listed at character's/hanafunda pages so if u are looking for this info at wiki u would find it :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561#post-1158935</guid>
				<title>Big Shammy Lvl 2</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-362561/big-shammy-lvl-2#post-1158935</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 04:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nytol</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>919249</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I apologize if this is in the wrong spot. I must say that this wiki has been very helpful in using BvS and possibly kept my interest in the game.</p> <p>The reason I'm making this post is that I notice much of the content for Flower Wars has been added, but I noticed something that seems missing. I accidentally left Big Shammy Lvl 2 in my party over night when I first got him and I noticed I had an extra free game for Flower Wars at day roll. On my main screen listing my bonuses it was listed as he played games with me through the night. I'm without the exact phrase at the moment, but I've used the extra free game lots of times.</p> <p>I Noticed Cato Lvl 2's over night bonus was listed and wanted to point out that I think all of the Flower Wars characters possible have an overnight bonus. I am not a very high level in Flower Wars so I can not check this for every one.</p> <p>Anyway I just wanted to point this out in case no one else noticed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>