<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Welcome..&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820/welcome</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Welcome..&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:43:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820#post-1759360</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820/welcome#post-1759360</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 12:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>yoyoel</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>well, it's true that huggly teddybear counts as one perm instad of 4, the item checker does not count the spirit of the demon of the sand, the spirit of the nine tails or monoract, so there are 74 kaiju drops in total</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820#post-1412120</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820/welcome#post-1412120</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 11:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm sorry you feel that way, but please have some patience as the people who have made these are only human, players like the rest of us and typically with no help from the game maker other than what we gather on our own. They're also largely based on player feedback&#8230; what's missing, what's good and what's not&#8230; I think in this case you were mistaken because it lists in perm count rather than physical number. It's up to date and accurate in that regard, but not displaying the way you'd thought. If you think that's not how it should be, or an explanation should be put up, you could use the tab for feedback and see if he's interested.</p> <p>p.s. I'm not sure if the script maker still plays anymore but I know both aren't so passionate about the game as they once were, so spending their time programming something that has very little use for a dwindling playerbase under 3k is probably not a high priority, or interest.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820#post-1411917</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820/welcome#post-1411917</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 22:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Agent Inari</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>392886</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The Item Checker has just betrayed me. It listed me as having exactly 70 drops, but turns out it counts the Huggly Teddybear as 4 items! Which means I still am 3 items short. *Sigh* 18 TACOs half-wasted because somebody did his work <em>almost</em> right.<br /> Looks like there are only 71 different drops in total then, not 74.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820#post-1279247</guid>
				<title>5k stam</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820/welcome#post-1279247</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 22:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Prem-aka-Prince</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>304978</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is the opening quest to a line of content called 'Hero's Quest', which is designed to come after all current content at time of writing. You need to beat R00t and PizzaWitch both ways, and then beat WorldKaiju content. The recommended season is 24+ (recommended for PW hard and WK) and you MUST complete glowslinging to unlock the quest.<br /> By the time a player does all this and qualifies for HQ, their daily stam should be 860. Awesome points should be invested in full Appetite and Glowslinging as standard. If they're in a strong village capable of running science 6 daily they can expect their daily app to be 900 more often than not, which is 15 TACOs (+1 for free from Cipher level 2), +20% roughly when using TACOS ally in team. From the expected 19 tacos you get 3,610 stamina. Add that to your daily base stamina (let's say somewhere in the region of 1-1.4k) it's not all that difficult to get naturally. Then there are plenty of appetite boosts in the game -an extra TACO at this point would give you 290 stamina, increasing with each TACO. Then there are non-free stamina boosts themselves- 300+300 from a weekly free favour from Eleven Tails (the reward you get from beating R00t) and one of your own, 200 from Z-Reward&#8230; I'll also mention party house juice for more app (better than the stam juice by far), and a couple of Flower Wars powers (the Mahjong power gives +app which is more advisable).</p> <p>It's even easier if you care to use a TACODELUXE or few, or wait until Festival day [the 11th of the month] &#8230; but those two make it a little bit too easy. If you're ready for Hero's Quest, you'll be able to pass this check without breaking a sweat. If you're not, you probably can't unlock it yet. But if you just seek the know-how, I can edit this post with links on the keywords and more detail where requested (as if it wasn't long enough).</p> <p>p.s. I'll point you to the permanent item checker in regards to perms. <a href="http://timothydryke.byethost17.com/billy/itemchecker.php">http://timothydryke.byethost17.com/billy/itemchecker.php</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820#post-1279119</guid>
				<title>Stamina</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-370820/welcome#post-1279119</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 19:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ritsuna</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1208510</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok, seeing as how I don't have mad stamina gathering skills&#8230; perhaps it would be a good idea to list how someone can get 5000 stamina to pass that part of the quest? Perms needed, where Stamina can be gathered, appetite items that help/are needed, that sort of stuff.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>