<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Hero&#039;s Quest&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Hero&#039;s Quest&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-4289264</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-4289264</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 23:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Aldraia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>628021</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Are we <em>sure</em> that completing a Monument mission before you have enough Unfinished Compositions for that monument gives you the boost to item find chance? Because I tried that with the eighth and it didn't seem to work.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1903724</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1903724</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 13:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>taltamir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>663175</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>[quote]Message from Authority2:<br /> Limits refunds 100% the amount of extra Spiral it lets you bring along, but still only 50% for the 100. This fits the information you gave in the wiki - if you had Limits 1 and ended with 101, 50 is refunded plus half of the remaining 52, giving 76.<br /> If you brought along 250 Spiral using Limits 3 and you spent 100 or more, that means that you'd have less than 150 left so it would refund everything, but if you'd ended with over 150 then the remaining Spiral would still be cut in half.<br /> If you have further concerns, let's discuss them in the Dicussion page on the Guide.[/quote]</p> <p>Yea, I have concerns, namely you are telling people to not get limits because it doesn't refund their energy, which is lies and a bad advice.<br /> 1. It explicitly states that it refunds the energy<br /> 2. I tested it and observed it refunds the energy.</p> <p>Now, I was unaware of the exact amounts being refunded (thank you for clarifying it), but in that case you should have corrected it instead of just reverting the edit, which is:<br /> A. Lazy<br /> B. Changes 1 slightly inaccurate statement (saying it always gives back 100%, instead of just during the most typical play scenario) into a blatantly false statement (saying it never gives back any additional spiral).</p> <p>Also, you should have posted your argument in this discussion page to begin with instead of pming me.</p> <p>PS. I tested and on finishing with 216 I got back 183 which confirms your math. I am going to edit the page from its current blatantly false state to the corrected formulas that you yourself provided (not back to the erroneous statement I myself made before and which you reverted)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1902226</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1902226</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 14:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>taltamir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>663175</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I would like to point out that with limits giving 100% refund, I find the most cost effective to be territory 1, followed by territory 3, then territory 2, then territory 4.<br /> I take 3-5 spiral energy to finish territory 1, earning 1200 AP for it.<br /> EDIT: I just lucked out and managed to do territory 1 for a mere 2 spiral energy.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1902215</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1902215</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 13:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>taltamir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>663175</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Limits tests:<br /> Limits 0: 50% refunded<br /> Limits 1: 76 out of 102 or 101 (depending on proc of efficiency 3) refunded, aka 75%<br /> Limits 3: 100% refunded every time.</p> <p>Someone is welcome to test limits 2 at some point</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1709132</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1709132</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 23:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Juudaime</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The drop chance for dusty wheels is certainly not 100%, I confirmed it myself.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1384894</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1384894</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 18:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Raaaak</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What you are missing is that &quot;rare&quot; mission can only turn up when you do general missions.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1384512</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1384512</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 04:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>anima</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Isn't Tarnished Wheel-Farming a lot easier with 'all' missions because with all missions 23,5% of the missions have the wheels and with only nin it's 16,6% of the missions that have it.</p> <p>Or am i missing anything? like rare mission really being rare (as i seem to get them as often as normal missions)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1242243</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1242243</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 10:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Skarn22</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>372883</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It was originally bugged, all three of them were Gen d10s20. I was actually wondering what the new checks were, thanks.</p> <p>I'll fix it later if someone else doesn't first. It's hard to give good advice when I haven't actually tried the new checks&#8230;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563#post-1242240</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-385563/hero-s-quest#post-1242240</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 10:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>darkh999</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>292579</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>jediwaldo you know that you should correct that &quot;easy tasks&quot; in The Lock quest. First is Gen d60s50, second Nin d65s40 and third Tai d30s110. Setting you reaper blood to Cobra Kai is good idea :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>