<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Contributor Introductions</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Contributor Introductions&quot; - Get to know the various contributors to the BvS Wiki!</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:37:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-630773</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-630773</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 22:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>don_poleeon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>376746</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm Don P.</p> <p>I'm a somewhat of a BvS veteran. I got into BvS by just going about google for something to do.<br /> After a while of playing, it was fun. I found BvS wiki after my first week of playing and the guides and things<br /> helped me out soooo… I joined, thinking I could help someone else with my exp. and get out of ditches of the game.<br /> My goal is to make a full character story and get a "Detective Conan" arc on BvS, and maybe start a actual RPG as well.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-239740</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-239740</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 02:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>FaintIce</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>142801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Faint.Ice here.</p> <p>I got into BvS a lil over a month ago with a recommendation by a friend that also plays BvS. My charas are AisuJ, JonasZ and Robin. The first two are my "primaries" and Robin is my "joke" chara. BvSwiki has saved me a lot of hassle, so lately I've been trying to contribute, though I tend to forget too lol. Anyway, I hope to own and then blow my own village somehow, but prolly not cause I suck at recruiting peoples xD. And.. yeah.. yo B)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-187926</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-187926</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 19:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mathiu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99072</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm Mathiu.</p> <p>I came over to BVS from the Giant In the Playground forums and introduced it to the IRE games.<br /> Uzuki can thank me for one of his referrals.<br /> I'm an anal-retentive data monger that doesn't change anything without direct confirmation.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-148776</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-148776</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 22:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi I'm Cana Hatake, Inch girl or Inch-NI</p> <p>I first came across BvS when I joined Kakashi fan club at narutofan (username Inch-NI) and I was directed to it by Tpad.<br /> I went created a player Cana and then I havent stopped playing.<br /> I first came here when I searched for BvS fourms when I read the revamped how to play and it advised going to fourms talk rather than using the village menu.<br /> I came here and joined and I havent stoped refrenceing here since.<br /> Thanks for leting me join …..oh if I edit sumit could ppl double check it since I'm dyslexic thankies<br /> I will do my best to gather information!</p> <p>Inch out!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-132796</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-132796</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 20:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Teh Kaz</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>101519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hey i have been playing for quite some time i joined when i was on a forum called pokeplushies(got banned so i am booorrreed but i will not be bored on sunday)And somone has a picture of a yoshi i clicked iut and it sent me to BvS cool i thought so i joined and i always wanted to be a hokage.Playing it is real fun in my opinion and i will nnneeevvveeerr quit! XD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-114813</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-114813</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 18:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KazeNR</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>87475</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hello, new here, in most games/forums/sites I am Kaze N. R., but Kaze will do (I have found disliking how my name is mangled by the language). I'm mexican, played… umm.. a month and half or so. I created a village (just 'cause) called Dark Star a little while, I like to check here for info, and found that some of the basics were lacking so decided to apport. I gess that I know some things because I'm really new to the game.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-113473</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-113473</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 18:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NikolaSama</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>84275</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hello, here and in most games/forums I am called NikolaSama or Nikola-Sama but just call me Nick. Played BvS for 1,5 of a month I think, great game. This site was of great help to me, as it gave me info on how to get the Ro-Sham-Bo Redux party, that rocks! Also, I just like to check here for new info, like leveling your allies.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-113276</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-113276</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Moare</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>79546</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi I'm Moaré. I have played this game for over a year. It's a great game and I uses Ainn as character name. I was the secund to contribute to this wiki, and still contributes as I sees it nessesary. I knows a lot about the game.</p> <p><em>I'm a Moderator</em></p> <p>I'm currently trying to clean up the Forum</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-113056</guid>
				<title>Re: Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-113056</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 10:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>TikiTDO</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>81366</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What's up. I figure I'll keep the ball rolling and see how many other people we could get in here.</p> <p>I'm TikiTDO, and my BvS character is creatively named TikiTDO. I would honestly prefer it if people just referred to me as Tiki. I too have been playing for about two weeks, and figured I'd help edit the wiki every once in a while as it is now the best source of BvS information. When I finally make Jounin I should be able to spend a bit more time filling stuff in, as right now I'm just focused on gathering all the items/allies I can get easily. Fortunately, most of the articles that need filling are about things I have yet to do, thus I will be more active when I actually get to the point of doing them.</p> <p>Unfortunately it doesn't seem like wikidot has signature support on the forums, so unless you want to paste your signature manually in each post you're out of luck.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958#post-112143</guid>
				<title>Contributor Introductions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-42958/contributor-introductions#post-112143</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 02:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hey there!</p> <p>We've been working together on this Wiki for a bit now, and for the most part, the only person you've really had a chance to talk with is me. So I figured setting up this forum would help to develop a sense of community in the Wiki. And what better way to get to know each other than to introduce each other! So, I'll go ahead and start.</p> <p>So I'm BvS-Uzuki, but you guys can call me Uzuki. I've been playing BvS for a few weeks now and thought it was a great game, but that it was really hard to find information about it. So I went ahead and setup this Wiki to help out. My current character is Uzuki from Murder Village. I'll have to say, I've learned a ton about the game since I set things up, so I'm very much glad I did.</p> <p>I'd include my BvS signature image, but I can't figure out quite how to do that yet ;)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>