<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>On Images</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43104/on-images</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;On Images&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:39:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43104#post-112551</guid>
				<title>On Images</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43104/on-images#post-112551</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Some of you may have notice I made like 100 changes in the past hour or so, all related to image files. I finally figured out how to host images locally, and I've been converting all the ally portraits to local files instead of files hosted on Flickr.com. I think this is for the best, since Flickr does have transfer limitations, and we don't want our Wiki to be stuck in that situation.</p> <p>Here are some instructions on how to deal with images now.</p> <p>At the bottom of the page, there's a button labeled "Files". Click that, then click "Upload New File". From there, select the file you want to upload, and that'll upload the file. That file is now specifically associated with that particular page, but you can access it from anywhere on the site (so don't upload the same file all over the place!).</p> <p>Now, to link an image, you should do the following…</p> <div class="code"> <pre> <code>[[image pagename/filename]]</code> </pre></div> <p>For example</p> <div class="code"> <pre> <code>[[image allies:lil-ro-lvl-2/Lil'_Ro_Lvl._2.gif]]</code> </pre></div> <p>Will give you…</p> <img src="http://bvs.wikidot.com/local--files/allies:lil-ro-lvl-2/Lil'_Ro_Lvl._2.gif" alt="Lil'_Ro_Lvl._2.gif" class="image" /> <p>Image tags are case sensitive, so be careful with it.</p> <p>Also, you must <em>always</em> provide a page location, even when you're linking from the same page that you've uploaded the file to. If you want examples of this, look at any of the existing ally pages. They're all correct at the moment.</p> <p>All the 'summon' pages still need to be updated with the new photo format. Everything else should be done (I think).</p> <p>Please, please, please, don't just upload tons of crap. Tracking down files and keeping things clean isn't quite easy yet. Upload the stuff you were currently linking from Flickr. You guys have been doing great so far, so I know you'll do fine with this too.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>