<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Naruko Uzu&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Naruko Uzu&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:47:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356494</guid>
				<title>History, part 4, draft</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356494</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 18:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>She likes drinking sake, the colours orange and black, and swords. She forges custom-made Kitsune Swords (made with real kitsune!) out of awesomeium and gives them out for free in the PHC. You can usually find her there.</p> <p>This wiki entry was written by [[[player:<a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/player:authority2">Authority2</a>]]].</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356485</guid>
				<title>History, part 3, draft</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356485</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 18:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Since then, she has become more and more bloodthirsty, as she indulged her hobby of stabbing people with pointy objects in order to watch them bleed. When she got her paws on a science textbook from another dimension, she started doing completely unethical experiments on people. If you see her wearing her lab coat, STAY AWAY! Recently, she signed up for ninja training for the killing and excitement, and also because it's awesome. She graduated last year, when it became apparent that a being of such incredible power and bloodlust was wasted being an academy student.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356482</guid>
				<title>History, part 2, draft</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356482</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As she grew up, she found palace life intensely boring, even though she engaged in her love of pranks at every opportunity. When, at the age of five hundred and sixty-eight, both her siblings started lusting after her, she became mildly delusional from the stress. Eventually, she ran away from home after faking her death by throwing a strawman with a bag of ketchup tied to it off a cliff. Her family seems to have been convinced, as nobody has come after her&#8230; yet.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356474</guid>
				<title>History, part 1, draft</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356474</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Even though she looks like a 14-year-old teenager, she is, in fact, over two thousand years old. She is a Fox Demon Princess by heritage. Her parents, the Fox Demon King and Queen, were divorced before she was born. Even though they lived in separate castles, day after day, each found their thoughts creeping to the other. Despite their denial, they started to secretly sneak into each other's bedrooms in the dead of night to&#8230; argue&#8230; with each other. One night, after a particularly heated &quot;argument&quot; that woke the whole castle, Naruko was conceived.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356456</guid>
				<title>Fox description, draft 1</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356456</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>In her fox form, her sleek fur is the same blonde colour. When the sun shines off it, it glitters like gold. Her ten flaxen tails fan out behind her like a halo. Her movements are so graceful that she appears to be moving in slow motion, even when she runs. Her eyes, pretty in a human face, become downright adorable. When she releases her full power, her fox form grows to the size of a mountain and her fur turns a deep blood-red.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356420</guid>
				<title>Character description, draft 1</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356420</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Naruko is a shapeshifter. In her human form, her hair falls in golden streams across her shoulders like a golden river. Her eyes are a deep, hypnotizing shade of cyan-aquamarine. Six jagged scars on her cheeks form the shape of whiskers, and draw attention to her high cheekbones. When you see her, you can't help but be captivated by her smile.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079#post-1356412</guid>
				<title>Helping to improve this entry</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-436079/naruko-uzu#post-1356412</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Authority02</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1260594</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Authority2 here, and I'm going to help you, with your permission, to improve the quality of grammar in this entry, since you have admitted to your deficiency in the aforementioned area. I'll post the completed version here, and you can give me feedback.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>