<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Billy Lvl. 3</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976/billy-lvl-3</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Billy Lvl. 3&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:25:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976#post-124113</guid>
				<title>Re: Billy Lvl. 3</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976/billy-lvl-3#post-124113</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 04:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/jutsu:kido:nightfall">Kido:Nightfall</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976#post-124107</guid>
				<title>Re: Billy Lvl. 3</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976/billy-lvl-3#post-124107</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Altered Nova</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>81815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Wait, the mission for getting Billy Lvl. 3 requires 20d AND 15s?! How the heck are you supposed to win that (If you don't have the Flying Thunder God jutsu)? Take Billy Lvl. 2 along and pray that he auto-wins it?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976#post-121244</guid>
				<title>Re: Billy Lvl. 3</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976/billy-lvl-3#post-121244</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 15:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DesertJ</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>92816</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I can tell you his stats and how to get him but thats about it… Although I guess I'll just list how to get all the allies that I know of here ^^ here goes… (This information is from Random Village Forum.)</p> <p><strong>Regular Allies:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Annie - +1 Nin Range - Proctor a Chunin Exam! (11d/9s, B-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Big Bo - +2 Taijutsu Strength and +2 Taijutsu Levels! - Crush a forest of evil! (14d/9s, A-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Big Ro - +2 Genjutsu Strength and +2 Genjutsu Levels! -Talk a guard into defecting! (15d/7s Nin, 4d/8s Tai, A-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>Big Shammy - +2 Ninjutsu Strength and +2 Ninjutsu Levels! - Hide in a Shadow!(14d/8s, A-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Billy - +1 Tai level and 5% chance of automatically winning a mission! - Check Out a Ninja Centerfold (5d/2s, D-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Bruce Jr. - +2 Taijutsu strength and +2 Taijutsu Levels, but Jutsu Chakra costs are 25% higher! - Blindfighting (5d/1s, D-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>Bruce Sr. - +1 Success on all Tai missions! - Challenge a Dojo Master! (6d/6s Tai, 4d/6s Nin - C-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Bugman - +1 Level in Genjutsu, and Jutsu Chakra costs are 10% less! - Catch a Fly (7d/1s, D-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Emosuke - +1 Ninjutsu Strength! - Hiding in Smoke (7d/1s, D-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Flipper - +1 to each Level of all Attributes under 3! - Genin Exam</li> <li>J-Diddy - Four times the amount of relationship points, and +1 Levels! - Have a Shexy Pahty! (12d / 6s, B-Rank Genjutsu) or spend 100,000 ryo in the Party Room</li> <li>K-Dog - 50% chance of of getting one free success! - Complete the Chunin Exam</li> <li>K.Y. - +1 Success on all Gen missions! - Clear out the Forest of Death! (8d/5s Gen, ?/? Tai, C-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Lil' Bo - +1 Taijutsu strength, and Jutsu Chakra costs are 5% less! - Eat your Ninja Rations (6d/2s, D-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Lil' Ro - +1 Genjutsu strength! - Ninja Academy Demonstration (6d/2s, D-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Lil' Shammy - +1 strength, but every mission costs two extra Stamina. - Special Mission</li> <li>Lil' Whitey - +1 Taijutsu strength and +1 Taijutsu Level! - Feed The Summons (6d/1s, D-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Master P - +2 Ninjutsu strength - Hide From a Search Party! (9d/3s, C-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>Meatballs - +1 Level in Ninjutsu and Taijutsu! - Special Mission (have 5 kunai to unlock)</li> <li>Mr. Sandman - Gain 5 stamina when you fail a mission! - Traverse the Great Desert! (7d/4s, C-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>Mr. Smith - +20% AP - Chase Down Timmy (10d/9s, B-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>Ol' Whitey - +3 Ninjutsu Strength! - Complete Jonin Exam as WhiteEye</li> <li>Pandabear - +30% Jutsu XP - Placate a hungry Panda! (11d/6s, B-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Pinky - Jutsu Chakra costs are 15% less! - Babysit the Ninja Academy (6d/2s, D-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Red Rover - +2 Levels in Taijutsu and Ninjutsu, but -2 in Genjutsu! - Clean the Ninja Dog Pen (7d/1s, D-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Rover's Mom - +1 Range - Tame a Scout Wolf! (9d/9s, B-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Sicko - +1 Gen range - Discover a Cure! (11d/7s, B-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Smokey the Bear - +1 Nin success - Cut through a Platoon! (11d/8s Nin, 8d/4s Gen, B-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>SNAKEMAN - +4 Levels, but -50% Ryo!- Special Mission (be a rogue Jonin to unlock)</li> <li>Spot - +5% chance to find hidden items and ninja - Special Mission (have 1 Dog Treat to unlock)</li> <li>Stalkergirl - Get 1 Stamina back per mission! - Special Mission (have 1 Medicinal Herbs to unlock)</li> <li>Terri - +2 Strength in Taijutsu! - Ride Your Ninja Kite! (5d, 6s, C-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>The Rack - +4 Strength in Taijutsu, but all missions cost 10 more stamina! - Win as the Super Rare from the Prize Wheel or spend 100,000 ryo on the Prize Wheel</li> <li>The Scar - +1 Tai range - Interrogate an enemy Ninja! (10d/6s Tai, 8d/4s Gen, B-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Timmy - 20% more XP and AP, but -2 Strength and -2 Levels! - Complete the first two missions in the Special Jonin Exam</li> <li>Trapchan - +2 Genjutsu Strength - Angry Villagers! (8d/4s Gen, 5d/5s Tai, C-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Triple H - +1 levels - Create an Image for the Village Monument! (7d/5s Nin, 7d/3s Gen, C-Rank Genjutsu) or any Training Mission</li> <li>Yuri - +1 Level in Ninjutsu, +1 Ninjutsu strength, and negates The Rack's weakness! - Clean up a Shexy Pahty (12d/6s, B-Rank Genjutsu) or rare from the Prize Wheel</li> <li>Z-Dog - +4 Gen Levels - Destroy an Evil Fortress! (14d/8s Nin 8d/4s Tai, A-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Level 2 Allies:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Billy Lvl. 2 - 5% chance of auto-winning a mission, and one free success! - Defeat an Evil Pirate! (12d/8s Gen, 7d/7s Tai, B-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Bruce Jr. Lvl. 2 - +1 Tai Success, + 2 Tai Range, 4 less stamina used when sparring - Have Bruce Jr. on your team when you hit 200 spars.</li> <li>Emosuke Lvl. 2 - +2 Nin Range, +1 Nin Strength, 1 Nin Level - Special Mission (be the #2 ranked player in your ninja rank or have 11 Emo Rock CDs to unlock)</li> <li>Lil' Bo Lvl. 2 - +5 Taijutsu Levels! - Special Mission (have 1 Bag of Chips to unlock)</li> <li>Lil' Ro Lvl. 2 - +5 Genjutsu Levels! - Special Mission (have 1 Hot Picture of Emosuke to unlock)</li> <li>Lil' Shammy Lvl. 2 - +5 Ninjutsu Levels! - Special Mission (have 1 Hot Picture of Terri to unlock)</li> <li>Pinky Lvl. 2 - Jutsu Chakra costs are 15% less, get one stamina per mission, and +2 Tai Strength! - Confess Your Emo Love! (11/9 Tai, ?/? Tai, B-Rank Taijutsu)</li> <li>Stalkergirl Lvl. 2 - Get one stamina back per mission, and +1 Strength! - Save the WhiteEye Princess! (12/6 Nin, 9d/5s Tai, B-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Level 3 Allies:</strong></p> <p><strong>* Billy Lvl. 3 - 20% chance of auto-winning a regular mission, and +4 Strength! - Withstand the Eyepatch of the Soul! (20d/15s Tai, 5d/2s Gen, A-Rank Taijutsu)</strong></p> <ul> <li>Emosuke Lvl. 3 - +4 Strength, and +3 Range! - Special Mission (have 1 Razor Blade to unlock)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Season 2 Allies:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Cato - +25% Ryo on regular missions - Complete S2 Special Jonin exam</li> <li>Olmek - Get two Items instead of one for Ally Drops! - Complete S2 Jonin exam</li> </ul> <p>Season 2 Level 2 Allies:</p> <ul> <li>Meatballs Lvl. 2 - +2 Levels in Ninjutsu and Taijutsu! (Can Drift Race) - Overthrow a Captain! (6d/7s, C-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Pandabear lvl 2: +30% Jutsu AP, +1 Strength (Can Drift Race!) - Light a Fire (6d/7s, C-Rank Ninjutsu)</li> <li>Red Rover Lvl. 2 - +2 Levels in Taijutsu and Ninjutsu! (Can Drift Race) - Interrupt a Meeting! (9d/4s, C-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Smokey the Bear Lvl. 2: +3 Success on all Nin missions! (Can Drift Race) -</li> <li>Spot Lvl. 2 - 20% Chakra costs, gives you a second, additional 5% chance to find hidden items and Ninja! (can Drift Race) - Strike Down a Sentry! (9d/4s, C-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Terri Lvl. 2 - +2 Strength in Taijutsu, +2 Taijutsu Range, +2 Taijutsu Success! (Can Drift Race) - Leap a Gorge! (9d/4s, C-Rank Genjutsu)</li> <li>Yuri Lvl. 2 - +2 Levels in Ninjutsu, +2 Ninjutsu strength, and negates The Rack's weakness! (Can Drift Race) - Undermine a Wall! (8d/5s, C-Rank Taijutsu)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Reaper Allies:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Fletch - +1 Range, +2 on Reaper missions - A-Level: Sew Together a Plushie! (10d/6s Gen, Reaper)</li> <li>Hermano - +1 Tai str, +3 on Reaper missions - A-Level! Protect a Possessed Bird (12d/5s Nin, Reaper)</li> <li>MC Stripeypants - Double chance of finding things on Reaper missions - C-Level! Get a Deal at the Shop (9d/9s Nin, Reaper)</li> <li>Mister Six - +2 levels, +4 on Reaper missions - Special Mission (have all other Reaper allies to unlock)</li> <li>Robogirl - +1 Nin Strength, +3 on Reaper missions - D-Level! Go Grocery Shopping (7d/4s Tai, Reaper)</li> <li>Shorty - +1 Genjutsu Strength, +3 on Reaper Missions - unlock Reaper Missions</li> <li>Strawberry - +2 Taijutsu Levels, +6 on Reaper Missions - C-Level! Cross Over a Spirit (8d/3s Nin, Reaper) or A-Level! Research a Hollow Evolution (11d/8s Tai, 5d/7s Nin, Reaper)</li> <li>Tats - +1 Strength, +2 on Reaper Missions - Special Mission (Have Shorty and Strawberry to unlock)</li> <li>TicTac - Double Friend Points - D-Level! Count the Substitute Souls (7d/3s Gen, Reaper)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Reaper Level 2 Allies:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Shorty Lvl. 2 - +2 Nin and Tai str, +2 Gen str on Reaper missions - Special Mission (have all Reaper allies except Mister Six to unlock)</li> <li>Timmy Lvl. 2 - 20% more XP and AP and +1 Success, +2 on Reaper Missions! - B-Level! Teach a New Soul Reaper (10d/7s Tai, 8d/8s Gen, Reaper)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Trade Allies:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Anonymous - +1 Gen Range, and deals 5 extra damage per round when you're being bingo'd - Be bingo'd with a Note Page after you get The Trade</li> <li>Hyuk - doesn't do anything, just follows you around… - Get 200 style points from bingoing</li> <li>LisaLisa - Double ally bonus damage during Bingos, +20 Stamina if left in your party overnight - Hang out with Anonymous once you have The Note</li> <li>Right - +1 Nin Range, and deals 5 extra damage when you're bingoing someone - Bingo someone with a Note Page with Hyuk in your party after you get The Trade</li> </ul> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976#post-115626</guid>
				<title>Billy Lvl. 3</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-43976/billy-lvl-3#post-115626</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 00:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Anyone know his new stats / team interactions yet?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>