<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Upgrade Planning</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Upgrade Planning&quot; - Discussion of the route we want to go with upgrades.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:04:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124770</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124770</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 00:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Lots of posts since I went to work, which is good!</p> <p>Re: Gogolu&amp;Chidori. Yeah, I know NRF pretty much makes us a heavy hit target, which is why I don't think there's any need to rush it. I think hanging out at our current level of War with no NRF for a bit makes sense for us to build up defenses. I just don't want to focus on defense too much. I've been in Villages where they had every defensive upgrade available, and they still got hit regularly anyway, and they had no real bonuses to their ninja (just the war council and jonin council). Those Villages are pretty much dead since other Villages provide so much more personal benefit. I do think we need more defense before the NRF, definitely. But, to some degree, defense just doesn't do much, Villages still get attack with high defenses.</p> <p>Re: Arkantos. You'll only meet Tai ninja in the War.</p> <p>Re: Fax, Scattered Outposts is like Solidarity but it affects attack stats instead of spy stats. I'll transfer your vote over to the vote thread.</p> <p>Re: Alyson, I'll transfer your vote.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124686</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124686</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 21:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Chidon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>86059</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think we need a few more solid defenses before we buy the Natural Research Facility, but other then that I'm fine.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124619</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124619</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 19:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Alyson: Voting for War Room</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124603</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124603</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 18:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>My vote's for Potion Palace next, and then Solidarity. Isn't there an upgrade that does something similar to Solidarity…Scattered Outposts? We should get that too.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124523</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124523</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 16:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Arkantos here Btw… too lazy to login…</p> <p>I agree, the Ninjadog kennel, Sand's Tradingpost are not important at all, if you spend a reasonable amount of ryo on the Partyhouse you'll get the items anyway…</p> <p>And true, we should first get the Warroom ;) Also, I am about to become a Special Jounin (Taijutsu) if I go do the NNW thingy, will I meet Special Jounin (Taijutsu) ninja? or also Genjutsu and Ninjutsu ninja?</p> <p>Arkantos aka Shika-kun xD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124485</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124485</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 15:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You know that sign to that village is worth attacking is <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:natural-research-facility">Natural Research Facility</a>? Especially by Great Villages(ones with <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:epic-monument">Epic Monument</a>).</p> <p>So before that few stopping points would be nice, like <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:fortified-walls">Fortified Walls</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:scattered-outposts">Scattered Outposts</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:sentry-squads">Sentry Squads</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:spy-towers">Spy Towers</a>.</p> <p>Plus with upgrades and ninjas going up the ranks something should make Upkeep lower: <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:banker">Banker</a> and <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:connections">Connections</a>.</p> <p>I'm really impressed with Our Village Progress.</p> <p>Glory to Wiki.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124476</guid>
				<title>Re: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124476</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 15:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Moare</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>79546</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Good plan. They're usefull all of them. None complains about the order of upgrades either</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667#post-124426</guid>
				<title>Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46667/upgrade-planning#post-124426</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 14:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So, we're in the war now! Also, we've got a Jonin council, so things are going really well. Better than I would have expected! You may not, I also bought some spy towers for the Village. I didn't want to be sitting on a stack of crystals with no peace time bonus and no defense upgrades, so it was kind of a short notice judgment call.</p> <p>My plan is currently to continue to open up each upgrade to voting, because I think the Village really should have a say in the direction that we take things. Having said that, I think it still makes sense to have some sort of plan going into these things.</p> <p>Our next <em>major</em> goal is going to be the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:natural-research-facility">Natural Research Facility</a>. Once you get that, you're playing with the big boys, and things can get really nasty. I don't think we should rush into that without any defenses at all. I think we should really consider getting <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:solidarity">Solidarity</a> at least before we get the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:natural-research-facility">Natural Research Facility</a>. But, I don't think there's any need to rush to those things.</p> <p>Before we move towards that next level, I think we should fill some things out a little bit. Personally, I think we should go <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:war-room">War Room</a>-&gt;<a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:potion-palace">Potion Palace</a>.</p> <p>I think the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:war-room">War Room</a> really should be first, since we have a handful of experienced Jonin who are getting close to looping but don't have their Letter of Marque in line yet. Since the first two major upgrades were good for Chunins (War Council and Jonin Council), I think it'd be good to do something for the Jonin (War Room is also good for everyone to be honest. The war rewards are <em>nice</em>).</p> <p>My second preference is the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:potion-palace">Potion Palace</a>, for two reasons. First, as we'll all soon notice, when you get invaded, you lose 10 stamina for the day. Potion Palace gives 10 stamina, so it negates that penalty. This is good, since we have pretty much no defense. Second, it gives the ability to make potions, which ends up being quite useful. (You can make potions for more stamina, more friend points, or even make some permanent items. You can also get more arena games via potions).</p> <p>Other than that, some other important things we may want to consider before the NRF are the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:science-workshop">Science! Workshop</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:sand-village-trading-post">Sand Village Trading Post</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:arms-depot">Arms Depot</a>, and <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:ninja-dog-kennel">Ninja Dog Kennel</a>. However, I think these are all lower priority than the War Room and the Potion Palace.</p> <p>Thoughts?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>