<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>IMPORTANT: Read or you may get kicked from the Village</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46854/important:read-or-you-may-get-kicked-from-the-village</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;IMPORTANT: Read or you may get kicked from the Village&quot; - Do not have more than 1 character from the same IP in the Village.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:41:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46854#post-125042</guid>
				<title>IMPORTANT: Read or you may get kicked from the Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46854/important:read-or-you-may-get-kicked-from-the-village#post-125042</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 14:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay, we're really starting to have a problem with this.</p> <p><strong>Do not bring more than one character from the same IP into the Village. If you do, <em>all</em> of the characters from that IP are going to be kicked out.</strong></p> <p>It's seriously starting to hurt our Village, and it's really starting to bother me.</p> <p>Only <em>one</em> (1) character from an IP address can help the Village out (by providing ryo, collecting for resources, patrolling, etc), but <em>all</em> of the characters from that IP address increase the Village size and upkeep cost (this makes it harder for us to collect resources and to defend the Village).</p> <p>This means that you can't play one character and an alt both in the Wiki Village. This also means that if your friends play BvS from over at your house, they can't be in the Village either. I'm sorry, but this is the way the game has been designed. It's intended to discourage cheating, and it's in the game rules and has been for some time.</p> <p>I'm sorry this is the way it needs to be, but we <em>can't</em> have 4 people in the Village who are complete dead weight. And if I don't do something about it now, it's going to get worse as time progresses.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>