<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Kage Tutorial</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628/kage-tutorial</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Kage Tutorial&quot; - Tips on how to keep your village alive in the NWW?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:49:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628#post-124785</guid>
				<title>Re: Kage Tutorial</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628/kage-tutorial#post-124785</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 01:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BBBB</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95612</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>We already have solidarity and creepy traps. They got disabled because our village size is too small. TT_TT<br /> I'll talk to my second about attacking. I don't know how to do it myself. Thanks for the advice.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628#post-124776</guid>
				<title>Re: Kage Tutorial</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628/kage-tutorial#post-124776</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 01:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rand</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I would say the best way is to keep your village small for some time and choose solidarity and creepy traps as your next upgrades. It will take some time, but this way you will have less enemies.<br /> Another thing I would do is to end the peacetime, before it gets too high (one attack every 5th day or so) so you keep on making money.<br /> The ressources are not the most important thing right now, I would say, rather it's money that's lacking, so try to get all your villagers to go patrolling, instead of collecting. Only when your peacetime is +4 or so, all your villagers should change back to collecting.<br /> According to this plan you would get one ressource every 4th and two ress every 5th( the 2nd by invading) and earn money in the meantime to buy your upgrades.<br /> Last thing: As long as your village is maximum size &gt;10 all of your villagers will be able to collect, not only genin</p> <p>I hope it will be of some help ; )</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628#post-124298</guid>
				<title>Re: Kage Tutorial</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628/kage-tutorial#post-124298</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 11:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That's a really good question, and I don't have a good answer for it. I know Millennium is working on a Kage guide right now, but that's all I really know for what to suggest at the moment. Otherwise, just try what you can. See what you can do.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628#post-124292</guid>
				<title>Kage Tutorial</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-46628/kage-tutorial#post-124292</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 11:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BBBB</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95612</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay, so I'm fairly new in the game. i joined less than a month ago, I figure.<br /> My primary account (BBB) got into a village that was not yet in the war. It had few upgrades and even fewer members. While I was in the village, our kage joined us in the war. Recently, our kage left us, for some reason, and made my ninja kage without even asking or telling me anything.</p> <p>Steps I've done:<br /> 1. I've told my members not to attack. We can't defend if we're attacked, so they shouldn't.<br /> 2. I've remodeled so our maximum village size is lower. Hopefully, peacetime bonus will save us.</p> <p>Unfortunately, we don't have enough members to buy meaningful upgrades. How do I keep my village alive?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>