<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Wild and Untamed</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Wild and Untamed&quot; - Animist Life simple as that</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:32:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174#post-342142</guid>
				<title>Re: Wild and Untamed</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed#post-342142</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 17:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Shady Neo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>258030</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"I've heard of him" said a man in the corner. "supposed to be some ninja who will meet with you if your strong and treacherous enoough to abandon your village."</p> <p>The man had a forehead protector on which proved he was a ninja from Bankai Village. He didn't seem very powerful but spoke to the other ninja who all seemed more powerful with unnerving confidence.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174#post-143739</guid>
				<title>Re: Wild and Untamed</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed#post-143739</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 16:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Naruto Namikaze</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Animist looked over at the man "no never heard of this person you seek or do not seek" said Animist as he went back to his meal and began to eat his glass hidding his eyes from view as he went back to eating.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174#post-132124</guid>
				<title>Re: Wild and Untamed</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed#post-132124</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>"^slurp^ mmmmm Ramen always hits the spot"</strong></p> <p>Cana's eyes were drawn the the figure that walked in</p> <p><strong>'<em>hmm he has some power a demon none the less hmm I gotta watch him…..oh hes a reaper captain cool</em>'</strong></p> <p>Cana's wolf ears pricked up at the mention of snakeman K-dog had often talked of him<br /> She growled and sent chakra to her already poised Wolf ears to hear the conversation this man <em>she thinks its a man you never know with reapers they have no scent Cana never liked that</em> dared to strike up with a hungry Animist</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174#post-130326</guid>
				<title>Re: Wild and Untamed</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed#post-130326</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 03:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mark1</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>97210</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Mark walked in shortly after trying not to make a big scene but it was hard for someone such as himself with such unique features not too. As he walked in his hair brushed up against the arc in the doorway and his aluminum plated boots banged against the floor and his ripped captains jacket waving behind him. Mark sat next to the stranger and looked over to him.</p> <p>"Hey would you know anything about a rouge ninja by the name of SNAKEMAN?" Mark asked the stranger in a soft voice so that if there were any of SNAKEMAN'S bandits they could not hear.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174#post-128633</guid>
				<title>Wild and Untamed</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48174/wild-and-untamed#post-128633</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 21:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Naruto Namikaze</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Animist was a man of many words…nope not many…but when he did talk your learned to shut up or get the hell out of dodge either way you learned never to talk bad of him or his friends or do stupid shit with him around. But some people are just to dumb for there own good.</p> <p>Animist sighed as he caught the fist coming his way…this people just didn't stop did they break the arm in his grip he smirked when he heard it shatter before sending the last of the masked people flinging into a tree. He smirked and picked up all the bags and used clones to pick pocket all of them before taking all their useful stuff and sealing it away.</p> <p>Making his way down the road he made sure to mask his power and smiled in a wolfish kind of way before making his way to a stand and ordering some ramen…ahhh he loved food.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>