<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning&quot; - Steps on the way to the NRF.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:04:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-130861</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-130861</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 01:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Omnifox</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>83749</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>its the 2nd one XD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-130626</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-130626</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 19:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Heh. Invasion targets aren't always what they seem ;)</p> <p>You know, it's been relatively surprising how little it feels like we've been hit, to be honest. It may just help that we spend our resources as fast as we can get them. Either that, or we're just new enough that few people know we exist, so we're not on people's hit lists yet.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-130620</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-130620</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mathiu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99072</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Baramoor here (Kage of NerdFury village you're planning to invade as well, but oh well on that).</p> <p>I can say that since we got creepy traps and even one special forces, it's made our time a lot easier. Though it won't stop the serious spying it will keep one from getting chunin spy swarmed. Also, the attack upgrades have been invaluable.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-129804</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-129804</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You make a compelling argument. I'll update my first post.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-129803</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-129803</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Omnifox</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>83749</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>In a day I will be your subordinate :P</p> <p>So if you care, I recommend getting the Science!. Creepy Traps and Facility in that order. Then you will open up the other upkeep decreasing upgrades. Which will help your treasury enough to invest in the SWATBU then.</p> <p>Forget the little village defense upgrades. Those are a waste of ryo unless you plan on keeping a small village. Which is not really recommended due to the new upgrade rules that have been implemented.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-129802</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-129802</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd like to see Science! prior to an NRF, actually. There's a lot of things (monochrome pheromone, make-out mood enhancer, reversing hourglass, rotating timesphere) that you can't get without one, and there're other benefits too: double collection bonuses would be something I'd tag as incredibly useful, especially with a decreasing number of Genin/Chunin. Higher level uses (such as the one that gives everyone 50 stamina, essentially a free attack for everyone in the village) also have their benefits. With an NRF, we'll also be fighting monsters. The third-tier activation, Driving Rain, will make fighting those monsters far, far easier (and in fact may make the Shikai and Bankai in the village hit the monster's DC on every roll).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-129784</guid>
				<title>Re: 3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-129784</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ShadowHMF</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90460</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You are the boss… I don't know what those upgrades do unlees I really care about them so do what you think is best…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514#post-129783</guid>
				<title>3/22 - NEW: Upgrade Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-48514/3-22-new:upgrade-planning#post-129783</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 21:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Time for an update! We've been in the NWW for 9 days now, and, quite frankly, we've been kicking butt. We've hit some of our major milestones (we've got a <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:jonin-council">Jonin Council</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:war-room">War Room</a>, <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:potion-palace">Potion Palace</a>, and a handful of defensive upgrades as well), and I think we're getting closer to the point where we can move onto the next stage.</p> <p>I think we should seriously consider getting a <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:natural-research-facility">Natural Research Facility</a> soon. Once we get to this point, we can gain access to summons, monsters, S-Rank missions, and numerous other important upgrades. However, the competition becomes much more cut throat at this point.</p> <p>After having seen our own spying attempts, it's becoming increasingly clear to me that defense upgrades don't do a whole hell of a lot in the grand scheme of things. We should keep working on them, but truthfully, I don't think they'll really stop us from getting hit all that regularly. The only thing that will is Peacetime bonuses. We've also reached the size where <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:solidarity">Solidarity</a> and <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:scattered-outposts">Scattered Outposts</a> will do nothing for us.</p> <p>Having said all that, I don't want to get an NRF until we get the following upgrades:</p> <ul> <li><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:swatbu">SWATBU</a></li> <li><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:creepy-traps">Creepy Traps</a></li> <li><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:science-workshop">Science! Workshop</a></li> </ul> <p>I think SWATBU will have the greatest reduction in attacks against us, due to the removal of permanent spies (can't hit where you have no spies). Creepy Traps just acts as an additional bit of deterrent. Neither of these will stop attacks outright, but then again, the only thing that will is Peacetime.</p> <p>While I consider those two upgrades essential, I wouldn't mind getting the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:science-workshop">Science! Workshop</a> as well before we enter the NRF stage.</p> <p>We will, of course, continue going by the votes on each individual upgrade. But here's the trajectory I see things going.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>