<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures&quot; - K-Dog travels back to Cana&#039;s Wolf Pack to tell of Cana&#039;s  adventures in the Ninja world and other world these are the tales he will tell.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:32:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-170046</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-170046</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 14:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Cana snickered as Tats was gaping in aw at the blue figure that just dissappeared</p> <p><strong><em>I guess I should suggest that skip is ready to come ova to the other side</em></strong></p> <p>"hey Cana-chan? Uhhhh… Did you see that clone thing? How cool was that? I wonder who uses that technique…"</p> <p><strong>"huh that…. that would be the nameless face jutsu its a bit similar to SNAKEMAN's Second Face Jutsu but a whole lot better …..and by better I mean more useful…..although I has one draw back you need to pratice pratice pratice with it increase its duration"</strong></p> <p>"Oh who uses it though?"</p> <p><strong>"my best buddy Skip08 I'm a bit of a sensei to her but we belong to different villages now"</strong></p> <p>"oh well when I meet her I gotta see if I can do that technique, come on we are already late as it is"</p> <p>"Right lets go Fukutaichō"</p> <p>Tats growled</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-157548</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-157548</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 20:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>skip08</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>104023</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Skip cuddled her new puppy to herself.<br /> A melancholy smile crossed her face, it was unlikely things could remain like this for long.<br /> Soon she would reach chunnin, and would be given more difficult tasks, and her dream of being a tai-jutsu jounin was far off.<br /> She had to train, and keep training, until she reached her breaking point.<br /> Advancing further as a kunoichi was her only goal in life, and very little else took hold of her mind.<br /> Her family had trained her to work to a single mission and avoid breaking from it.<br /> Putting the puppy down she giggled lightly as he chased his tail in mirth, only to tire and lie helplessly on the ground.<br /> Stretching her arm, leg and back muscles, she started to run on the spot a little, motioning for her new sidekick to follow.<br /> The puppy looked at her, somewhat confused…just what was this strange kunoichi going to do?<br /> Bringing her hands together in front of her torso, almost in a prayer-like pose, she began to focus chakra into her bloodstream, allowing it to pulse through her muscles and provide warmth and energy.<br /> Slowing moving into the 'ready' position, Shadow stood beside her, almost mimicking her stance.<br /> What came next was most surprising.<br /> A blue silouhette, with no features other than being in the shape of the kunoichi, erupted from her body, racing off into the distance.<br /> Skip meanwhile, moved to a crouching position under the shade and security of a tree, as her eyes closed silently.<br /> Now, she could see through the eyes of the chakra clone she had created, but not for long. Her body jolted suddenly, and she reopened her eyes as exhaustion made its way through her muscles.<br /> "You like it Shadow? It's my own technique…the Nameless Face jutsu. No-one can tell it's me since its basically a clone with no copied features…"</p> <p>"Cana-chan? Uhhhh… Did you see that clone thing? How cool was that? I wonder who uses that technique…"</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-148792</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-148792</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 23:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Cana watched bewildered as Skip ran into the distance</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"UM…….She's alittle wierd"</span></p> <p>Cana sweatdropped</p> <p><strong>"YA THINK!"</strong></p> <p>Zypher cringed</p> <p>Cana looked up to see a brid flying over head</p> <p><strong>"Well Zypher we'd better go Tpad-sensei is calling"</strong><br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Should'nt we go after her"</span><br /> <strong>"You can……scratch that you will….As for me I gotta go Last time I was late Tpad-sensei made sure that 1 I hurt 2 I was trapped in one of his crazy training contraptions for a week and 3 after I escaped I was doing TRAINING MISSIONS 4&nbsp;3 WEEKS not even D-ranks but training missions…..I do not want that again…<em>Shudders</em></strong><br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">"ok 0.0 I wish I hadn't asked"</span><br /> <strong>"See ya later call me when you find her ok?"</strong><br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Ok Cana!"<em>grumbles</em></span></p> <p>Zypher sprinted along following Skip's sent untill he saw a shadow passing him he sniffed and saw a swallowtail butterfly by the shadowy figure</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"hmmm it looks like Tats from the shadow but I cant tell …..<em>Note to self get Cana to teach you how to sence reapers since they have no scent</em> Oh I gotta keep looking for skip …… hmmmm whats that a ninja dog with her…… I gotta report this to Cana"</span></p> <p>Meanwhile Cana had finished her trainin with Tpad and was currently packing her things to leave the Nightmare village but no befor she left her stash in the storehouse as a leaving present.</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"CANA……CANA"</span><br /> <strong>"Huh? Whats up Zypher?"</strong></p> <p>Zypher filled in Can on what he had seen</p> <p><strong>"Oh ok I guess that means I can teach her ninja dog skills …..when I find her again…. I take it you left her cus she had a ninja dog with her?"</strong><br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Yep I gotta ask….."</span><br /> <strong>"our next training session Zypher I promise"</strong><br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Oh ok then youd better "</span></p> <p>Zypher had known Cana long enough to know she had this uncanny ability to know waht ppl or animals were on about at random times. As Cana left the village she saw the shadowy figure.</p> <p><strong>"Hey Tats"</strong></p> <p>She waved as she dismissed Zypher but not befor giving him a few dog treats and a scratch behind the ear</p> <p>"Hey Cana"<br /> <strong>"You want me for some reaper missions Fukutaichō?"</strong><br /> "Yeah and stop calling me that Cana it sound wierd coming from you"<br /> <strong>"What Fukutaichō"</strong><br /> "CANA!"<br /> <strong>"Sory I couldn't help it"</strong> Cana said whilst popping a soul candy She turned Shinigami <strong>"Right lets go Fukutaichō"</strong></p> <p>Tats pulled his hand down his face and sighed as he entered the gate to the Seireitei</p> <p>"Come on before I do sumit I regret"<br /> <strong>"Hai"</strong></p> <p>As the gate disappeared a figure ran up and looked around</p> <p>"Funny I thought I heard Cana around here Shadow I guess not"<br /> Skip looked all around her</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-147439</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-147439</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 17:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"ehehehe I'm sorry I just dreamt that I was falling…" Skip scratched the back of her head and still muttered curses where her hairline ended, although, she argued with herself, now it would be much easier to manage and the change may attract <em>SOMEONE'S</em> attention. Cana looked at her quizically as she argued with herself, the girl's fragile state of sanity clearly showing. To her surprise, she stopped, fumbled in her side pack and found a tatty, palm-sized book that was so well used it didn't close correctly anymore. "Falling…Falling…" she muttered, scanning the pages with crazy eyes as a mad fan-girl might watch the target of their affections. "May be yielding to certain feelings…fear of rejection…" Skip sighed.<br /> <strong>"Any of that even apply to you?"</strong><br /> Skip's expression changed to one of disappointment, and putting the faded little book away she shook her head sadly.<br /> "aghrghgrhghgghgh!! WHAT IS THAT?!" Skip squealed, pointing to the black winged creature fluttering around her, that just happened to settle itself on her nose. She turned deathly pale. Letting out a scream of terror she ran for it. The poor little butterfly shaken by its ordeal, rested gently on the tree bark. She kept going until eventually, her lack of knowledge for her surroundings got the better of her and slamming into another being she was thrown to the ground.<br /> "What the…" a voice asked, seeing the poor kunoichi well out of her element. Scrambling to her knees she unsheathed a kunai, shaking as she stood up but still with a look of fury in her eyes. she had been terrified, now she was lost and afraid of the unknown before her, whose face was masked by the shadows in the trees. Her instincts told her to attack, since the being's chakra level was much higher than that of her own and a swift charge may be her only hope of escape. She was therefore, greatly surprised, and relieved, to find a small black puppy licking at her ankles.<br /> "Ehehehehehe!" she giggled softly and stroked the puppy's ears, paying careful attention to behind his ears earning her some playful nudges to continue. Picking him up she cuddled him gently and allowed him to keep lookout on her shoulder.<br /> "I wonder who that weirdo was…they've disappeared now…Finally I'm not talking to myself!" she said to her new comrade, who barked in agreement.<br /> "Ok Shadow..let's find Cana!"</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-143125</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-143125</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 14:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong><em>UH….yeah …..Scary….although she does remind me of myself as a genin though…..hmmmmm I guess She'll make my life more interesting</em></strong></p> <p>Cana proceeded to double check the forest for any traps that Skip might have missed<br /> She arrived back to find Skip now at another tree with scratch marks all around where she had obivously sleep attacked Canas eyes followd the tence arm that still held the kunai although it was now stuck on the ground between the legs of a now traumatised ninja dog</p> <p>Cana sighed</p> <p><strong>"Zypher When I asked you to watch her I didn't mean 4 you to ….ah never mind.."</strong></p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"but… I only tried to wake her cus she was having a nightmare…….Hey a little help here if you dont mind…."</span></p> <p>Cana shook her head as she gently plucked the kunai from Skips fingers careful not to trigger the ninja reflexs</p> <p><strong>"Didn't you learn your lesson when you did that to Walms too"</strong></p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"apperently not …but you were always ok with it"</span></p> <p><strong>"I'm different I raised you I'm used to you and your wierd ways of affection…..by now I think all of the Nin I'm close to are"</strong> She said whilst brushin him down</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Yeah well I dont do the affection thing unless I know that you trust the person"</span> Zypher puppy pouted</p> <p><strong>"Aww come on Zypher dont be like that"</strong> She hugged him, he grinned and then growled<br /> Skip stirred and woke up and cana turned to her</p> <p><strong>"Hey are you ok First you go and burn out , sleep and then according to Zypher here</strong> She pointed at the wary Ninja hound <strong>You were havin a nightmare"</strong></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-136103</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-136103</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>skip08</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>104023</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"ummm…..Level? Well tai-jutsu's my best skill-I like things quick so why should my ninja skills be any different?!" the brunette yelled, tripping three traps and dismantling them with shock and a smile, it seemed she enjoyed the adrenaline rush achieved from fear. She stretched her muscles and yawned. "I've been in here since 6am…a little nap wouldn't hurt ne?" she leant against one of the many trees and began to drift, hand never leaving the kunai.</p> <p>Cana sweatdropped. All this had happened in the space of 5 minutes, the kunoichi wasn't kidding when she said she worked with speed.<br /> <strong>"Crazy, hyper little chunnin…"</strong></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-134109</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-134109</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 19:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>"OK ….. <em>SIGHS … If she wants me too train her she hasta help me finish this mission</em> Well then whats your level, I know you are a Chunin at least since your going for the exam here in 3 weeks"</strong></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-134090</guid>
				<title>Re: Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-134090</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 18:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>skip08</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>104023</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>A petite kunoichi stepped out from the shadows, her long brown hair smouldering as she quickly flattened the flames with her palms.<br /> "Kami damn these stupid fireball traps!!" she exclaimed loudly, unsheathing a kunai and ridding herself of any dead hair, bringing it into a bob that ended a few centimetres below her chin. She brushed the soot from her scouser style skirt and 3/4 lengths combo, and resheathed her kunai into its holster on her back. Noticing the eccentric nin before her, she immediately entered a fighting stance, shuriken drawn as they were easiest to access.<br /> "And just who do you think you are? Did you set these traps?!"<br /> <strong>"Iie! I'm here to disable them! How'd you get in here anyway?"</strong> Cana retorted.<br /> "I…um…er….I snuck in to train…my exam's in three weeks time and I wanna make sure I pass…I've already failed three times…" she added half-heartedly, itching her neck in dismay. Her eyes widened as she realized the hair on her back was gone. "ARGHRGH if I find out who set those traps they're so…." she clenched her hands in prospective vengance. Cana began to back away slowly as the brunette entered into furious ramblings, noticing the words, 'kunai', 'tree', and 'sun don't shine' which made her highly uneasy.<br /> "HEEY!! Since I'm in the mood, Wanna spar?!"<br /> And Cana, never wanting to shy from a fight, entered her usual fighting stance, wolfishly grinning at the prospect of combat.<br /> "I like your spirit! Wanna be combat buddies? Oh, I'm Skip by the way…ehehehe…Who are you?"<br /> <strong>"Well…we're in the same village and you don't know who I am?!"</strong><br /> "Gomen, I'm not good with names…or faces for that matter…" Skip replied sheepishly, her body relaxing from her stance.<br /> Cana slapped a hand to her face at the girl's obvious ignorance. <strong>"I'm Cana Hatake, special jounin from the village hidden in darkness. Also known as the Nightmare Village, among other names."</strong> she growled.<br /> "SPECIAL JOUNIN! Hwaaaah! Cool!!" Skip grinned, shaking her fists in triumph. "Finally! Someone who can train me that's not a loser!"<br /> Cana sweatdropped and hung her head in quiet anguish. Just WHAT had she gotten herself in for?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271#post-132111</guid>
				<title>Cana&#039;s Wolfish Adventures</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-49271/cana-s-wolfish-adventures#post-132111</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 22:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
								<wikidot:authorUserId>102351</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Back when Cana was just a young puppyish cub a ninja would always travel by her pack bringing gifts, knowledge and always entertained the young cubs like Cana with tales of his adventures and the exploits of his ninja and reaper companions.</p> <p>This ninja was very excentric had a metal plate over 1 eye and constantly had his nose in a book. When he arrived after Cana's generation were born he caused quite a stirr. He had always senced potential in the Wolves of this pack and had taken some back to train long ago. Some like nico and risa had returned to the pack and tought the cubs of the ways of the ninja.</p> <p>This life had intrigued Cana from the moment she had first heard the word ninja, when K-Dog arrived she hung on his every word and every time he returned she questioned him more. Until 1 visit he asked the pack leader could he take Cana to Narutofan to assess her ability.</p> <p>The elders allowed it and Cana travelled with K-dog to the Ninja world. As they travelled K-Dog asked her</p> <p>"Why do you have bandages over your eyes Cana? Last I saw you you had perfect albit vivid colbalt crimson slitted eyes?"</p> <p><strong>"Well"</strong> Cana began</p> <p>"Hold on let me guess you poked your eyes with a kunai?"</p> <p><strong>"Nope I'm recovering after having had an eye infection"</strong></p> <p>"oh..ok…<em>hmm she is gonna have a white eye limit now…</em>well whats the matter….?"</p> <p><strong>"Who goes there show you self"</strong></p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"woah your good K-Dog didnt sence me yet"</span></p> <p>"Ah… there you are t-Pad"</p> <p><strong>"huh?? Who is he K-Dog-sensei?"</strong></p> <p>"Your new sensei Cana this is where I leave you"</p> <p><strong>"oh.. ok.. I'll see you again wont I"</strong></p> <p>"Yeah when you are chunin"</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">"Alright till then K-Dog she's safe with me"</span></p> <hr /> <p>After a months training with t-Pad (and still sparing). Cana Joined White Wing's Village (the nightmare) And made Chunin</p> <hr /> <p><strong>"Yay I did it"</strong></p> <p>"Yeah you did Cana I knew you would"</p> <p>Cana swirled around</p> <p><strong>"K-DOG!!!"</strong></p> <p>"Woah dont slobber over me would ya…….Um Cana would you get off me"</p> <p><strong>"oops ok"</strong></p> <p>A couple of seconds later ater wipins some wolf slobber and dust K-dog turned to Cana</p> <p>"Cana I'll be travelling back soon so we gotta make stories for me to tell or have you got some for me?"</p> <p><strong>"Oh I've got some to tell Sensei!!!"</strong></p> <p><strong><span style="text-decoration: line-through;">-</span>-</strong></p> <p>Cana Entered the forest of death to remove traps and any ninja that were lurking around</p> <p>As she removed yet another trip wire</p> <p><strong>"<em>whats with these nin and trip wires have they no imagination….</em>huh whos there behind that tree with the scorch marks"</strong></p> <p>A shadow emerged……..</p> <hr /> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>