<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>For anyone who cares... The Season Two sannin exam:</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50266/for-anyone-who-cares-the-season-two-sannin-exam</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;For anyone who cares... The Season Two sannin exam:&quot; - Copypasted data. I&#039;m not going to bother raking screenshots.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:49:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50266#post-134952</guid>
				<title>Re: For anyone who cares... The Season Two sannin exam:</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50266/for-anyone-who-cares-the-season-two-sannin-exam#post-134952</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ruinic</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99313</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Please add it to the wiki. I'm too lazy to do it myself. (As usual. &gt;.&gt;)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50266#post-134950</guid>
				<title>For anyone who cares... The Season Two sannin exam:</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50266/for-anyone-who-cares-the-season-two-sannin-exam#post-134950</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 09:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ruinic</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99313</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The Big Three<br /> Do you have what it takes to become Legendary?<br /> Attempt to become Sannin &gt;</p> <p>The Best</p> <p>Simply, to be the best, you must be The Best.</p> <p>I am today's Number 1 Player<br /> (If the mission has a requirement, be sure to have completed it before you click above, or you'll fail the mission!)</p> <p>The Best</p> <p>SUCCESS!<br /> You show the fundamental basics. Let us proceed.<br /> Continue Mission &gt;</p> <p>The Three Original Legends</p> <p>By hook or by crook, you must be recognized by the original three Sannin. Get them on your team!</p> <p>I have The Rack, J-Diddy, and SNAKEMAN in my Team<br /> (If the mission has a requirement, be sure to have completed it before you click above, or you'll fail the mission!)</p> <p>*(Didn't copy the success message for that part at the time, and using the Back button to look for it gives me some message about postdata. &gt;.&gt;)</p> <p>A Great Village</p> <p>You must be from a great Village - one recognized not for a single action, but for withstanding the test of time.</p> <p>My Village has the Epic Monument<br /> (If the mission has a requirement, be sure to have completed it before you click above, or you'll fail the mission!)</p> <p>A Great Village</p> <p>SUCCESS!<br /> Your village's monument only awaits your visage.<br /> Continue Mission &gt;</p> <p>Taijutsu</p> <p>Epic Battle</p> <p>There was an epic battle, long long ago, that you won. How do people remember it?</p> <p>Difficulty: 12 Successes: 12</p> <p>Succeed! That's right - with you kicking legendary butt.</p> <p>Ninjutsu</p> <p>Epic Knowledge</p> <p>You must have a deep understanding of all things Ninja - deep enough that you carry it in hte very way you exist..</p> <p>Difficulty: 12 Successes: 12</p> <p>Succeed! ..which is something you are well known for.</p> <p>Genjutsu</p> <p>Epic Wisdom</p> <p>Finally, are you the type of person to have the answers to everything</p> <p>Difficulty: 12 Successes: 12</p> <p>Succeed! Your words echo across nations.</p> <p>You are known far and wide as Sannin!<br /> You are Sannin!</p> <p>You now get 250 Stamina per day, get 15% extra Ryo on missions, and can partake in the Sealing of Demons!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>