<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Alyson&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986/alyson</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Alyson&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986#post-137910</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986/alyson#post-137910</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 22:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I don't see anything all that hard to read and I do get what your saying. Fortunately I have a while to really deal with it. Well, not THAT long but at least another month I think. I do have some plans for the end of her season :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986#post-137895</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986/alyson#post-137895</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 22:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rand</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hmmm, good point. I think maybe you should stick to BvS in this case (confusing explanation, sorry. Another try …) Maybe you should treat the loop as what it is: a new season. You could end season 1 with telling about the things you were hunting until the last day before the loop (f.e. if you hunted after your 45th ally, it's a friend you wanted to safe, if you needed the last item for the Letter of Marque, you found the last item to a fantastically strong item-set somewhere and took it with you to the new adventures awaiting you in season 2). And it's not as if you'd loose or forget all things after the loop, the items you loose you just loose, that's alright for any story, and the jutsu you forget you have not unlearned but you need to practice them when you don't have some important missions to hold your attention.</p> <p>…wow, too tired to think in English, so if there are loads of unintelligible things written, I'll correct them tomorrow</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986#post-137282</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986/alyson#post-137282</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 05:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thanks ^_^ I didn't even realize people actually came in here to read it. Guess I'm going to actually have to keep adding to it now as more stuff happens.</p> <p>What I don't know how to do is update it once I loop. How the heck do you explain losing everything, even your experience, without using everybody's favorite cliche Amnesia.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986#post-137114</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50986/alyson#post-137114</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 23:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Rand</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Haha, your page surely is something else. A great story you have written. One really starts to sympathize with your character :-)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>