<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Bloodline&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Bloodline&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:11:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-2019796</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-2019796</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 04:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>strauss</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Not sure where to best post it but it seems Heart of the Cards rolls separately for poker and individually for each game since I got free games at several different app costs already.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1690998</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1690998</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 00:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Choose Fate to follow the RNG, and choose Destiny to follow the Flash.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1690800</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1690800</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 20:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Stupid</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This will be a stupid question as my name suggests but which is the bloodline representing good and witch bad. I'm talking about destiny and fate. I expect that one will be evil and the other good in the future or am I totally wrong and they are the same please tell me.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1132339</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1132339</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 15:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kwigyo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>648934</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Palumatsu I have one thing to say to you&#8230; Knightmare Mark 86 parts. Especially the Shift to Drift ones. Do you really want to farm up +88 range and then smokebomb to the correct mission only to not get the item? PoG is a lifesaver. Just use common sense with it. If you plan on using it, don't eat stamina stuff til after. If it's too late for that, consider giving the regular droprate a few goes with the extra stamina.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1132336</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1132336</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 15:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hey, guys! What are u talking about? KnightFrame parts are VERY RARE, especially for s1! And they do not loop! U need all of them to complete BN!<br /> PoG EXIST for this goal!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1131752</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1131752</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Most people try to hurry up and loop in order to escape the limits lower seasons hold on you. Not only that, but BN is one of the harder areas of the game in sheer comparison to other parts, like Reaper and the Genin/chunin/jonin training levels. By the time you ever get to this, its nearly entirely redundant, because you'd have already collected all the loopables already that are on missions. although it does speed things up a bit for some, imo, i seriously dont think its worth it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1131747</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1131747</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>&#8230;I confess I have no idea what you're going on about. Where do AA missions (or ally drops) enter into this?</p> <p>Yes, of course, these are very few items for which it makes sense to bother using Power of Greass. And yet, those items exist. Are you really suggesting that because something is useful only rarely, therefore it's not useful at all?</p> <p>As befitting something that isn't needed much, you also get very few uses of it in a season. In fact, in Season 1, you can use it five times. For that matter, if you get it in Season 1, there are likely to be exactly five missions on which you will want to use it. It's almost as if it were designed that way&#8230;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1131736</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1131736</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 00:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>~.~ even then. let me hand you an example.<br /> Say an item drops 10% of the time on a mission. The best way to utilize Greass would be to push yourself to 10 stamina, jump to AA-rank missions, and then launch PoG. In R00t, this is a wise move, because while your farming bits and stuff, you've got a guaranteed drop elsewhere. ONLY drops. flavor text doesn't treat ally finds as drops. Now, for key words to get from field to field, this is one thing, however, very few fields have items that are needed for absolute progression (r00t key words, ally Chunks parts, etc). Most can be obtained through other means, however slowly, than to just sit there and PoG it. VERY few items are worth that much chaotic trouble. Not only that, but if you push the missions to the one you want, you have to let it sit there and collect dust while you spend the rest of your stamina that would otherwise be lost (<span style="text-decoration: line-through;">usefully</span>). It may seem like a good idea, but the item drop would have to be seriously low.</p> <p>then again, i dont know about any PW missions that drop that low, so whatever</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1131710</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1131710</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 23:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sam510</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>358542</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Palumatzu: you say that as if you'll generally use it when you have lots and lots of stamina. And as if there aren't ways of getting bonus stamina after it's all been used. And as if there aren't some specific permanent items with a low find rate. You might want to reexamine those assumptions. :-)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-1131610</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-1131610</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 21:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Palumatzu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>388167</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>that said, isnt it neverendingly inefficient? I mean, it'd be more efficient to grind for items needed and get ryo and AP instead of wasting all that lovely stamina for ONE item. no? Or am I miscalculating something?</p> <p>Or was this thrown in for the lazys?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-871327</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-871327</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>No, no. BurgerNinjas have an additional -Stamina penalty when you do them, a penalty which is negated by having the PoG bloodline.</p> <p>No matter what, using the actual Power of Greass to auto-get always takes all your stamina.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-870846</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-870846</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 19:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Silly Newb</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>After testing PoG on burger ninja missions, I did lose stamina. I used it while having 52 Stamina, and ended up with 1. :o Is this outdated info?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-870212</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-870212</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 17:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Silly Newb</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Power of Greass<br /> "# Lose no Stamina on BurgerNinja missions."</p> <p>Does this include Pizza Witch ones? They do share a lot of similarities after all (like freezer drops)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692#post-524920</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-50692/bloodline#post-524920</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 05:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Novaix</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>333449</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You do not get bloodlines fomr past connection, eighth trigram or the redeye equivalent. You get the looping jutsu flying thunder god technique, advanced whiteye or advanced redeye, respectively. You can not learn bloodline-specific jutsu, and you can choose from any of the 3 starting bloodlines (although choosing the same as your new jutsu would be foolish unless you were after a bloodline specific looping permanent, such as eye of the tiger/jazz hands/whiteye version)<br /> Therefore a) you should get bloodline specific permanents of the relavent type before getting this ability<br /> b) you should only choose TWO of these, because you will can choose the last one each time you loop again<br /> c) it does loop<br /> d) if you want to get all of them, choose the bloodline relavent jutsu/traits you like most<br /> Legacy's extra stamina/chakra<br /> Whiteye's better specific jutsu/extra levels<br /> Redeye's extra XP/AP and value meal (really the only good redeye only jutsu)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>