<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;If You Could Make A Bloodline...&quot; - ...what would it be?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-503414</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-503414</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 19:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Arcticmoon</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>WOW!!! A lot of detail on that mark'd one sounds awesome though. Anyway,<br /> This bloodline is based on Shaman King.<br /> Name: Power of spirit LV.1<br /> Ability: Plus 1 range, may summon Spirit summons, Minus 10% chakra costs, Can partake in Shaman missions<br /> Quest: Spirit caller (Requirements: Have W'ssup (An ally obtained on a B-level mission))<br /> 1: Call the spirits (Have the spirit scabbard (Obtained on a B-rank mission))<br /> Success: Where's the blade on this thing?<br /> Fail: That's a twig not a scabbard<br /> 2: Assemble your blade (Have the Spirit sheath (Obtained on a B-rank mission))<br /> Success: Doesn't a Blade have….. A blade???<br /> Fail: Try again<br /> 3: Channel the spirit (12 range, 10 successes Gen test)<br /> Success: You channel it perfectly<br /> Fail: Your accidentally channel Satan and he Bitch slaps you silly then destroys the world<br /> Epilogue: As you form your Spirit blade a angry Spirit caller walks up to you and punches you in the face, then joins your cause (You get Spirit sword(Plus 2 strength, plus 2 levels)/ Shouty joins you (Plus 2 tai range, plus 4 on Shaman missions/ the bloodline Power of spirit)<br /> W'ssup: Plus 1 range, Plus 2 on Shaman missions<br /> Show stopper (100 chakra cost, 20000 Xp) Plus 2 Nin range<br /> Coup de grace (100 chakra cost, 20000 Xp) Plus 2 Gen range<br /> Stagecrash (100 chakra cost, 20000 Xp) Plus 2 Tai range<br /> Shouty: Plus 1 Levels, Plus 3 on Shaman missions<br /> Spirit capture (100 Chakra, 50000 Xp) Capture Summons on certain missions<br /> Name: Shimegami beads<br /> Quest: Spirit summoner (Requirements W'ssup, Shouty, Tech (Obtained on a D-rank Shaman mission) and Quiff (Obtained on a C-rank Shaman mission)<br /> 1: Find 10 beads (14 Range, 4 success Gen test)<br /> Success: Thank god for google maps<br /> Fail: You find plenty of stuff but only 9 beads<br /> 2: Find 80 beads (14 range, 4 success Tai test)<br /> Success: Finding things is fun<br /> Fail: You find something but it isn't a bead. EEEWWWW!!!!<br /> 3: Find someone who can USE the beads (14 Range, 4 success Nin test)<br /> Success: Shouty punches you in the junk and swipes the beads, right in the junk (Now you know what Flipper feels like)<br /> Fail: You accidentally eat the beads. Loser.<br /> Epilogue: You feel less of a man but more of a Shaman (You get Shimegami beads (Plus 2 range on Shaman missions)/ You may now do B,A and S-rank Shaman missions)<br /> Tech: Plus 2 Gen strength, Plus 2 Gen levels on Shaman missions<br /> Spirit search (50 Chakra 200000 Xp) Plus 200% Ally/Item find chance on Shaman missions<br /> Quiff: Plus 4 Nin levels, Plus 4 Tai levels on Shaman missions<br /> Gel Jammer (120 Chakra 100000 Xp) Plus 3 Nin levels, Plus 2 Nin range on Shaman missions<br /> Name: Power of Spirit LV.2 (Plus 2 range, Minus 20% chakra costs, Spirit summons now stay with you until dismissed)<br /> Quest: Spirit Summoner (Requirements: Duel Ice (Obtain on a B-rank Shaman mission), Girly green (Obatain on a A-rank Shaman mission and Cupid (Obtain on a A-rank Shaman mission)<br /> Prologue: You feel ready to become Even more powerful<br /> 1: Some cocky Shaman gets all up in your face (15 Range, 5 success Gen test)<br /> Success: You slap him and his giant beast of death silly<br /> Fail: He kicks your ass. Royaly!!!<br /> 2: The bad guy's minnions try to take you down. Cane all of their asses (10 range, 500 success rolling Tai test)<br /> Success: 1 down PLENTY more to go<br /> Final success: Phew, that's the last of 'em<br /> Fail: You lost to LACKEYS!!!<br /> 3: Boss battle (20 Range, 10 Success Nin test (Automatic jutsu victory (Show stopper)<br /> Success: Nice work<br /> Automatic jutsu victory success: You stop his show<br /> Fail: PWNED!!!<br /> Epilogue: The boss escapes but he drops something behind (You get Oracle chime (A strange object)/ The power of spirit Lv.2 and W'ssup LV.2<br /> W'ssup LV.2 (PLus 2 range, Plus 5 on Shaman missions)<br /> Jutsu: Show stopper (100 chakra cost, 20000 Xp) Plus 2 Nin range<br /> Coup de grace (100 chakra cost, 20000 Xp) Plus 2 Gen range<br /> Stagecrash (100 chakra cost, 20000 Xp) Plus 2 Tai range<br /> Spirit strike (225 chakra cost, 30000 Xp) Plus 2 Nin strength, Plus 2 Nin range<br /> Duel Ice: Plus 2 Range<br /> Ice boarder (120 Chakra 100000 Xp) Plus 3 Gen levels, Plus 2 Gen range on Shaman missions<br /> Girly Green: Plus 2 levels, PLus 4 on Shaman missions<br /> Pixie dust (120 Chakra 100000 Xp) Plus 3 Tai levels, Plus 2 Tai range on Shaman missions<br /> Cupid: Plus 2 strength, PLus 2 levels on Shaman missions<br /> If you could be arsed reading all this and think it's a good idea then please message Arcticmoon because I have lots more ideas but am not sure if I can be bothered making any more.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-465835</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-465835</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 11:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zulikas69</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176854</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Bloodline "mark'd". This bloodline was thinked and named by sikcool. I am only the one, who write and created thingies about that bloodline.</p> <p>Bloodline "marke'd" is based on orochimaru curse seal from anime and manga "Naruto".</p> <p>This bloodline have 2 levels and few different modifications. first level of this bloodline you get from quest "Forest of death (the secont option)".</p> <p>Quest "Forest of death (the secont option)".<br /> Requirements- Season 3+, genin, finnished "Chunin Exam Part 1", All sanin theems (not active, just to have them).<br /> Step1- You enter forest and one of your teamate is acting strange. Gen. Dif.6 Suc.3.<br /> Succsess- you find out that he isn't your teamate and atack him emidiatly.<br /> Faill- "well maybe he is only exited. What the…" you whoke up in hospital.<br /> Step2-Fight him quickly and defeat. Tai. Dif.7 Suc.4.<br /> Succsess-He runs quickly from you.<br /> Faill-He beats you onehandedly, how lame.<br /> Step3- find your lost teamate. Nin. Dif.9 Suc.1.(Epic Dog Urination Technique auto succsess)<br /> Succsess- you find him right behind that bush.<br /> Faill- you search all forrest, but didnt find him, maybe behind that bush would work.<br /> Step4- Super strong wind comes to you. Tai. Dif.4 Suc.10.<br /> Succsess-You whithstand wind. It was aimed not to you but your teamates.<br /> Faill- you fly straight to mouth of giant snake. You meet Billy "whats up?"<br /> Step5-(from now on your team wont help) Strange ninja come to you. He looks in to your eyes. Gen. Dif.10 Suc.2.<br /> Succsess- you whithstand his genjutsu.<br /> Faill- You ended up in playng dead.<br /> Step6- Fight Strange ninja with your ultimate taijutsu. Tai. Dif.12 Suc.6 (Primary Lotus automatis succsess)<br /> Succsess- You allmoust beating him.<br /> Faill- he beats the crap out of you.<br /> Step7- Throw few kunais and shurikens at him. I have 10 kunais and 10 shurikens.(you will loose them)<br /> Succsess- You throw everything you have.<br /> Faill-To throw what? I dont have it.<br /> Step8- Finish that ninja with your ultimate ninjutsu. Nin. Dif.14 Suc.4. (Fire Style: Phoenix Flower Jutsu automatic succsess)<br /> Succsess- you burn him, and he only burns his face off.<br /> Faill- you totaly faill.<br /> "you are strong as I aspected from you." An ninja bites you, yack.<br /> You got bloodline Mark'd.</p> <p>Mark'd.<br /> +200 to chakra maximum.<br /> +200 daily chakra.</p> <p>you gain one specific jutsu "Marker art skillz" (here you can see trivia <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MGmTR4IDho0&amp;feature=channel_page">http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MGmTR4IDho0&amp;feature=channel_page</a>)<br /> Marker art skillz- 200chakra cost, -20stamina, no chakra loss from next 3 regular missions (or bingo rounds) (that means that you still need enought chakra to use jutsu, but you will fully regain it after mission) also you gain 1lv for 3 regular missions.</p> <p>Mark'd Lv2 have few different modifications.</p> <p>Mark'd Lv2 earth-<br /> +400 to chakra maximum.<br /> +200 daily chakra.<br /> you gain another bloodline jutsu "Mark of earth"<br /> Mark of earth- 500 chakra cost, -10stamina, +5 Taijutsu strenght, +8 Taijutsu levels for next 5 regular missions or bingo rounds.</p> <p>Mark'd Lv2 fire-<br /> +400to chakra maximum.<br /> +200 daily chakra.<br /> you gain another bloodline jutsu "Mark of Fire"<br /> Mark of fire- 500 chakra cost, -10stamina, +5 Ninjutsu strenght, +8 Ninjutsu levels for next 5 regular missions or bingo rounds.</p> <p>Mark'd Lv2 water-<br /> +400to chakra maximum.<br /> +200 daily chakra.<br /> you gain another bloodline jutsu "Mark of water"<br /> Mark of water- 500 chakra cost, -10stamina, +5 Genjutsu strenght, +8 Genjutsu levels for next 5 regular missions or bingo rounds.</p> <p>all Mark'd Lv2 are gaining throu quests.</p> <p>Quest "Long way for power, Earth/fire/water"<br /> Requirements- jounin, Season 3+, Sasuke lv3, Sticky, Tubby, Flute, The Twins, Bones, Not bingoed, snakeman.<br /> Step1- Some sound ninjas have come to fight you. Tai. Dif. 12 Suc. 10, Nin. Dif. 9 Suc. 8.<br /> Succsess- you show the who you are.<br /> Faill- you woke up in hospital<br /> Step2- They give you 1 day to sneak out from your village.<br /> I am not in village now.<br /> Step3- cover your trace. Gen. Dif. 15 Suc. 8.<br /> Succsess- few ninja teams have not tracked you.<br /> Faill- Ninja team has tracked you and beated crap out of you. ( you are bingoued for 24 hours)<br /> Step4- Sound ninjas tells you to get in the bucket. Whait the second… where is bucket? Who has forgoten that?<br /> I have billy bucket.<br /> Step5- Some Ninjas has tracked you. Tubby whats to fight them.<br /> I have Tubby Lv2<br /> Step5- Some Ninjas has tracked you again. Sticky whats to fight them.<br /> I have Sticky Lv2<br /> Step6- Some Ninjas has tracked you again. It is kinda boring. Twins whats to fight them.<br /> I have Twins Lv2<br /> Step7- Two Ninjas has tracked you again. But bones comes and takes you. Flute whats to fight One of them.<br /> I have Flute Lv2<br /> Step8- One ninja have tracked you, Finaly the last one! Another came in, Sh@*. Bones will fight him.<br /> I have Bones Lv2<br /> Step9- Is it time to go out? From now on timer will begin.<br /> I have been here for 24 hours.<br /> Step 10- Fight billy for freedom. Tai Dif. 16 Suc. 3.<br /> Succsess- You easily wound him badly.<br /> Faill-you lost the batlle and honor.<br /> Step 11- Billy transforms in to something powerfull. Tai. Dif. 20 Suc. 10, Nin. Dif. 18 Suc. 15.<br /> Succsess- You defeat him allmoust in equal fight.<br /> Faill- You lost the batlle and honor.<br /> Step 12 (earth)- you return to snakemans hideout and have to fight with Tubby for place in hideout. Tai. Dif. 18 Suc. 20.<br /> Succsess- you wonnn.<br /> Faill- You are kicked out.<br /> Step 12 (fire)- you return to snakemans hideout and have to fight with Sticky for place in hideout. Nin. Dif. 18 Suc. 20.<br /> Succsess- you wonnn.<br /> Faill- You are kicked out.<br /> Step 12 (water)- you return to snakemans hideout and have to fight with Flute for place in hideout. Gen. Dif. 18 Suc. 20.<br /> Succsess- you wonnn.<br /> Faill- You are kicked out.<br /> You gained Bloodline Mark'd Lv2 earth/water/fire.</p> <p>Quest "fullfill mark power (earth/fire/water)"<br /> Requirements- Mark'd Lv2, emosuke Lv3.<br /> Step1- you have to show how strong your mark is.<br /> I have bingoed 5 non bingoed ninjas today, without using note.<br /> Step2- Emosuke just laughts from you. Gen. Dif. 20 Suc. 20.<br /> Siccsess- you showed him, that you not afraid of his pityfull genjutsu.<br /> Faill- you show him, that you afraid of him.<br /> Step3- Emosuke atack you with his sword. Tai. Dif. 20 Suc. 20.<br /> Succsess- What a succsessfull block.<br /> Faill- he stabs you.<br /> Step4- emosuke is atcking you with lightning. Nin. Dif. 20 Suc. 20.<br /> Succsess- you grounded his lightning.<br /> Faill- You has been baked in lightning.<br /> Step5- kill snakeman and finaly be free. Tai. Dif.30 Suc.5.<br /> Step6- Destroy his body. Nin. Dif.30 Suc.5.<br /> Step7- Snakeman is in you, He is trying to take over your body. Gen Dif.30 Suc.5.<br /> you lost snakeman. You get Item "Brown marker"/"Red Marker"/"Blue marker"</p> <p>"Brown marker"- +10 daily stamina, +1 Taijutsu strenght, 1 stamina less cost jutsu, min. 0 stamina (this means that if jutsu cost some stamina, stamina cost is lowered by 1, Stacks wit other Markers) Item loops.</p> <p>"Red marker"- +10 daily stamina, +1 Ninjutsu strenght, 1 stamina less cost jutsu, min. 0 stamina (this means that if jutsu cost some stamina, stamina cost is lowered by 1, Stacks wit other Markers) Item loops.</p> <p>"Blue marker"- +10 daily stamina, +1 Genjutsu strenght, 1 stamina less cost jutsu, min. 0 stamina (this means that if jutsu cost some stamina, stamina cost is lowered by 1, Stacks wit other Markers) Item loops.</p> <p>Quest "Long way for power, Heaven mark"<br /> Requirements-"Blue marker","Red marker","Brown marker",Marke'd Lv1.<br /> Step1- 4 sound nijas whants to fight you, again… Okey lets skip all this.<br /> I have billy bucket.<br /> Step2- join rescue team. What the? what has hapend just now, what have you skiped? You havn't even left your villige. oh well.<br /> I have team of Billy Lv3, Emosuke Lv3 and K dog (where he came from?)<br /> Step3- Defeat snakemans army. Tai. Dif. 15 Suc. 30.<br /> Step4- Defeat snakeman with one jutsu. Nin. Dif. 20 Suc. 30.<br /> Step5- Defeat Snakeman within you and seal him away from you. Gen. Dif.35 Suc.10.<br /> You lost snakeman. You gained bloodline "Mark'd Lv2 heaven"</p> <p>Mark'd Lv2 heaven-<br /> This bloodline loops.<br /> +400to chakra maximum.<br /> +200 daily chakra.<br /> you gain another bloodline jutsu "Mark of Heaven"<br /> Mark of Heaven- 500 chakra cost, -10stamina, +5 strenght, +8 levels for next 5 regular missions or bingo rounds.</p> <p>Quest "Fullfill everything"<br /> Requirements-Mark'd Lv2 heaven, Haus.<br /> Step1- Show you power.<br /> I have bingoed 10 non bingoed ninjas today, without using note.<br /> Step2- you must to be the strongest.<br /> I am sanin.<br /> Step3- show the whole world that you are strongest.<br /> I am in top 10 daily rankings.<br /> Haus becomes to Hous Lv2, you got item (Marker Color of heaven)</p> <p>"Marker Color of heaven"- +20 daily stamina, +1 strenght, 2 stamina less cost jutsu, min. 0 stamina (this means that if jutsu cost some stamina, stamina cost is lowered by 2, Stacks wit other Markers) Item loops.</p> <p>Haus Lv2- +200% Wasteland Item / Ally find chance, +4 levels.<br /> Jutsu:<br /> Diagnosis - 250,000 XP. -5 Strength, +300% Item / Ally find chance - Food Pills needed : 2&nbsp;C<br /> Inner Monologue - 200,000 XP. +3 Range, -3 Strength : 3&nbsp;C<br /> Sanake within you- 500,000 Xp. +6 Levels, +6 Range, -6 Strengh : 4 Chakra, 5 Stamina</p> <p>Quest "New life of snake"<br /> Requirements- Haus, snakeman, Marker Color of heaven at least one in the villige.<br /> STep1- Defeat snakeman, he is eeeeevalllllll. Tai. Dif.25 Suc.25.<br /> Step2- Help haus to use snakemans body. Nin. Dif.25 Suc.25.<br /> Step3- Defeat snakeman withinyou. Gen. Dif.25 Suc.25.<br /> You lost snakeman. You got Haus Lv2.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-461478</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-461478</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 16:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sikcool</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>317334</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>bloodline named Mark`d based on snakemans curse seal -requires the legacy items from wasteland and mono and the sannin theme :) THATS WATH I CALL VS</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-453104</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-453104</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 20:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zulikas69</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176854</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>New bloodline, Yes I know That I am enjoyng in creating them (truly I hope that creators would take one of them :) )</p> <p>Blood (LV1)</p> <p>Gives you some daily stamina (From 20 to 50)<br /> first level of this bloodline loops.</p> <p>There is posibility to level up this bloodline in to two different bloodlines.</p> <p>Blood Lv2 Black<br /> Gives you 1 Nin. strenght and range.<br /> Gives you 3 Nin. levels.<br /> You can learn specific jutsu.<br /> You get one specific jutsu "Blood suck".<br /> Blood suck- 600 chakra, -5 levels, -2 strenght and range, +5 stamina from every teamate you curently have in your team. It can be used only one time for every teamate, teamates woun't help you for the rest of the day and another day.</p> <p>Blood LV2 Blue<br /> Gives you 1 Tai. strenght and range.<br /> Gives you 3 Tai. levels.<br /> You can learn specific jutsu.<br /> You get one specific jutsu "Animal I have become".<br /> Animal I have become- 200 chakra, -10 stamina, +4 Tai. Strenght and range, +10 Tai levels.</p> <p>Blood LV2 human<br /> Gives you 1 Gen. strenght and range.<br /> Gives you 300 to your max chakra.<br /> You can learn specific jutsu.<br /> You get one specific jutsu "Borrrrrring life"<br /> Borrrrrring life- 150 chakra, + 100% Mission Ap. and Jutsu Xp.</p> <p>this bloodline is based on anime Black blood brothers.</p> <p>Virgingirl- +2 levels in genjutsu, +30 stamina if you use "blood suck", when Virgingirl in your team (once per day) (this means that will get total 40 stamina from this allie (cos of virgin blood))<br /> Jutsu- Like a virgin- 900 chakra, +50 stamina, once per day. Required Blood LV2 Human.</p> <p>Blondiebly- -2 level, +100% allie find chance.<br /> Jutsu- Wake up - 50c, -500 frien points from your allies in your team, +200% Chance to find or level allie.</p> <p>Silverman- +2 Nin. and Tai. levels.<br /> Jutsu- Time of dying-170c. +8 Nin levels. Required Blood LV2 Black.</p> <p>Silverman Lv2- +4Nin. and Tai. levels.<br /> Jutsu- Time of dying-170c. +8 Nin. levels. Required Blood LV2 Black.<br /> Now or never- 120c, +7 Tai. levels, silver blade need. Required Blood LV2 Black.</p> <p>Pyromaniack- +3 Nin. strenght and range.<br /> Jutsu- whatch me "burn"- 250c, +15 Nin. levels. Required Blood LV2 Black.</p> <p>Buffman- +3 Tai. strenght and range.<br /> Jutsu- Mega punch- 300c, +15 Tai. levels. Required Blood LV2 Blue.<br /> Blue eye beauty- 200c, +3 Gen. strenght and range. Required Blood LV2 Blue.</p> <p>Witchgirl- +3 Gen. strenght and range.<br /> Jutsu- Lets start "Riot"- 320c, +15 Gen. levels.</p> <p>Lil tats- +6 Tai. Levels.<br /> Jutsu- On my own- 100c, Your team do not help you for this mission, +50% Xp. (and daily ranking).</p> <p>Pcyboy- +6 Nin. levels.<br /> Jutsu- It's all over- 100c, automatically lose a mission and regain stamina lost. Required Blood LV2 Black.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-446945</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-446945</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 21:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>The K</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>310765</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If I could make a bloodline I'd like to see something based off the Kaguya clan. I realize that the original three bloodlines deal with all three stats (Legacy for gen, Red Eye for nin, White eye for tai) but I would find it cool if maybe something that could happen with the Kaguya bloodline might be</p> <p>*Exclusive jutsus taught by bones<br /> *A bloodline jutsu that increases the chance of ally drops (since white eye doesn't do this)<br /> *When one wins 10 arena fights in one day they get Blood lust which gives them plus 2 arena fights in one day<br /> *15 arena wins in one day gives them Bone Warrior which gives them a +2 stamina boost when attacking any kaijuu (since the other give +5 when attacking a specific kaijuu, I figured since this bloodline doesn't deal with a specific stat it could apply to all kaijuu types but give the user less hp return per attack)<br /> *Upon Jonin ascension the ability to unlock a jutsu called "Spine Whip Jutsu" which increases the range by 2 and costs around 50 to 70 chakra (not too sure).</p> <p>I think anymore than that would be over powering it in comparison to the other bloodlines. I didn't put too much thought, just kind of came on and thought I'd say something about the Kaguya.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-446022</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-446022</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2009 15:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Enryu</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Knowledge of the Core<br /> - You can bend the rules of the world around you as you see fit, provided you have enough core for it<br /> - By spending a certain amount of core you can<br /> *Auto win a mission and get whatever is hidden on it (allies, items and events)<br /> *Increase JXP/AP/RXP/style/rep/storm MPH/friend points/kaiju damage/ryo bonus% for the day (each one is bought separatedly)<br /> *Get an extra life for fighting phases, only once per phase<br /> - +10% core<br /> - moon does not wane with time<br /> - can force one fight to go monocrome per day<br /> - +2 edge<br /> - +1 drain<br /> disclaimer: this ability was based on nothing at all, any resemblance with something you may have seen is mere coincidence</p> <p>Poke of Restoring<br /> - a hidden power has awakened inside you. You can acheive heightened concentration and manipulate a person's life energy<br /> - once per day you may use one special skill you may learn from your medical allies<br /> *Dr. Stylish: "Restoring Style: Slow-mo-fo" (halves difficulty)<br /> *Dr. Mark: "Restoring Style: You Are Fine Now" (unbingos one player of your choice, cannot be yourself)<br /> *Dr. Value: "Restoring Style: Godmode" (on the first round of bingo you will receive no damage, on the next, you will recover 10hp)<br /> *Dr. Fakename: "Restoring Style: Healing Rate Up" (any hp bonuses you get while bingoing are increased by 25%, lasts one battle)<br /> WARNING: if you try to use the same skill twice or two different skills on the same day you will be stamina-locked (stamina will be locked at 0 until next dayroll)<br /> - quest: Think Harder: "Stylish and Mark are discussing how to improve the Poke of Restoring…"<br /> *Requires Dr. Stylish, Dr. Mark and must have unbingoed at least 10 ninja<br /> *Must have their abilities<br /> *Must not be bingoed<br /> *Must not have used any ability of the Poke of Restoring<br /> *At the end you get the "Restoring Style: Stopwatch" (Used before entering a bingo. Opponent cannot attack for 3 turns. Unbingoable teams are innefective. Can run away from bingo with no adverse effects while active).<br /> -Missions:<br /> *Cure apendicitis<br /> *Make skin grafts<br /> *Remove glass shards<br /> *Remove glass shards FROM THE HEART<br /> *Reconstruct a bone<br /> *Solve a puzzle<br /> *Solve a HARDER puzzle<br /> *Disarm a bomb<br /> *Cure a mysterious infection<br /> *Remove shotgun pellets<br /> *Remove a rifle bullet<br /> *(rare)Cure an incurable disease<br /> *(rare)Remove a mortal parasite FROM THE HEART<br /> *(rare)Remove a mortal parasite FROM THE HEART, AGAIN<br /> *(rare)HEART PARASITE REMOVAL, ROUND THREE<br /> *Prevent an outbreak<br /> *Hone the Poke<br /> *Get out of depression<br /> *Operate on a vehicle<br /> *Suture lots of cuts<br /> *(rare)Make a transplant<br /> *(rare)Defeat a parasite mutation<br /> *Operate on a live show<br /> *(rare)Remove a remote killing machine<br /> *(rare)Operate ON THE BRAIN<br /> *Stop cardiac arrest<br /> disclaimer: this was loosely based on the videogame series Trauma Center, the original characters are copyrighted to Atlus Co.</p> <p>Hope you enjoy reading this, even if it will never be in the game</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-440249</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-440249</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 12:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Karnil</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>How about this Bloodline:</p> <p>"PopEye" or "Vim of a Sailor" [Of course PopEye is a pun with all your xxxEye bloodlines :P)<br /> - Obtain Sailor Missions</p> <p>-Jutsus: Anchor-arms (x strength bonus for Tai) [Item requirement is "Can of spinach"] Chakra cost 300<br /> Pipe smoke (x strength bonus for Nin) [Item requirement is "Tobacco"] Chakra cost 300<br /> Spin yarns (x strength bonus for Gen)[Item requirement is "sailor's yarn"] Chakra cost 300</p> <p>-Allies: "Popeye" ("the sailor man" may be added) [+2 Tai range]<br /> "Olivia" (She Popeyes girlfriend) [+2 Gen range]<br /> "Bluto" (He was the enemy of Popeye) [+2 Nin range]</p> <p>-Teams: Popeye + Olivia Bonus: + 5 Tai,Gen Lvls<br /> Popeye + Bluto Bonus: + 5 Tai,Nin Lvls<br /> Olivia + Bluto Bonus: + 5 Gen,Nin Lvls</p> <p>For those who didn't notice Popeye stands for Tai, Olivia for Gen and Bluto for Nin ;-)</p> <p>-The item requirements are <strong>no</strong> Alliedrops, they drop in specific "Sailor missions" but their droprate may be x0%<br /> x could be any number… no defined by me…</p> <p>-How to obtain the missions:<br /> Quest: (Requirements: Special Jonin, 2 Anchor Arms tattoo)</p> <p>(You get the "Anchor Arms tattoo" as Temporary tattoo that is in "Bubblegum" which would be common prize at the Pricewheel)</p> <p>Quest:</p> <blockquote> <p>You got a nice pair of Anchor Arms there bud' sais some old Sailor smoking his pipe.</p> <p>You sure are a good sailor righ'? Lets test that…</p> <p>-insert Tai,Gen,Nin Sailor Missions-</p> <p>Wow" You're pretty strong bud'</p> <p>I'll join ya</p> <p>-You obtain Popeye as your Allie<br /> -You obtain "false Vim of a Sailor" Bloodline<br /> -You obtain access to Sailor Missions : full source reference</p> </blockquote> <p>- Example Missions would be:<br /> - Set sails [Tai : 9 dif , 10 suc]<br /> - Bar fight [Nin : 9 dif , 10 suc]<br /> - Navigate [Gen: 9 dif , 10 suc]<br /> as i said only examples</p> <p>Well… and as a final prize you get a new Quest and get the real Bloodline</p> <p>Quest:</p> <blockquote> <p>get real Anchor Arms! (req: False vim of the sailor,100 Sailor Missions, All Allies, [maybe more])</p> <p>-Fool the Tattoo-shop owner that you're old enough: (Gen XXX) I'm too lazy to think about something that would be good XD<br /> -Darn he found out anyway… but… Money will change his mind… (10000 ryo)<br /> -Be a tough sailor and endure the pain (Tai XXX)<br /> -Show of the cool pair a Anchor Arms to all your friends (Nin XXX)</p> </blockquote> <p>Benefits:<br /> + 1 Strength<br /> + 5% Daily ranking (Because the arms look soooo cool)<br /> + 15% Alli find chance (Because everyone wants a sailor as your friend)</p> <p>—-</p> <p>Last thing to be said…</p> <p>It only a fun Bloodline, i know Popeye is not Anime/Manga… and the balancing… i don't care…</p> <p>I had fun making it ^^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-436493</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-436493</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 12:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zulikas69</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176854</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The Hope (okey, I know that this is my third post in this thread which contains new bloodline)</p> <p>This bloodline is lv4 trade.</p> <p>-You can give 2 more Juicy Apples to see who have imunitet to note.<br /> -In theme menu apears new theme slot "background theme" which contains all bingo style themes<br /> - -40 daily stamina (this includes the Level 1, Level2 and Level 3 penalty)</p> <p>The Hope- This is a permanent item.<br /> -You can give 2 more Juicy Apples to see who have imunitet to note.<br /> -In theme menu apears new theme slot "background theme" which contains all bingo style themes</p> <p>If you have chosen "Sick of Him! (Anonymous)" then new quest aperas "The new enemy (B nonymous)".</p> <p>B nonymoes- you get him 3 days after completing mission "Sick of Him! (Anonymous)"<br /> +3 Gen. strenght, -10 succsess to enemy during bingo.<br /> Trivia- It is based on "N" (also known as Near or Nate River) from anime death note. His name is made from Anonymous, just first letter has been changed from A to B (coz N was second L).</p> <p>"The new enemy (B nonymous)"<br /> Requirements- B nonymoes, The Tote, Right Lv2, Jonin Rank.<br /> Step1- Bee friend with right- I am hanging ou with right using friend points today.<br /> Step2- Say to Right that fight is not over yet. Gen. Dif.15 Suc.25.<br /> Succsess massage- "He is getting in my way, I will kill him"<br /> Failure massage- "I am god, I dont ceare abaut another ant in my way"<br /> Step3- Make a deal with B nonymous. Nin. Dif. 25 Suc.15.<br /> Succsess massage- He refuse to join you, but he will share his knowlege with you.<br /> Failure massage- He refuse to join you and he says that he will hunt you down. (you can not to take this mission until pass 24 hours)<br /> You unlocked quest "The end of the game (to Right)" and "The end of the game (to B nonymous)".</p> <p>Ghem- It joins you if you bingo someone with nonte page wile B nonymous and LisaLisa Lv2 in your team.<br /> If you have LisaLisa Lv2 and Ghem in your team, You can get note page after bingoing someone with note page (posibility 50%)<br /> Trivia- Ghem is based on Rem from anime Death note.</p> <p>"The end of the game (to Right)"<br /> Requirements- to have Ghem, finished "The new enemy (B nonymous)".<br /> Step1- Force Right and B nonymous to meet each other. Nin. Dif.25 Suc.20.<br /> Step2- I have bingoed 10 non bibgoed ninjas, hwo had bloodline of trade (Trade, Note, Tote, Hope), today.<br /> Step3- Face Right, and dont fear his writing on note page. I have imunitet to note page.<br /> You lost Right Lv2.<br /> You got THe Hope<br /> You got new theme "Ready to finish the Job"</p> <p>Theme "Ready to finish the Job"- Opening Theme, -50 stamina, You can tarde 5 juisy apples to see what kind of bloodlines have ninjas in one villige.</p> <p>"The end of the game (to B nonymous)"<br /> Requirements- to have Ghem, finished "The new enemy (B nonymous)".<br /> Step1- Force Right and B nonymous to meet each other. Gen. Dif.20 Suc.30.<br /> Step2- I have bingoed 10 non bibgoed villige leaders today.<br /> Step3- Face B nonymous, and dont fear his team of hitmen. I have 20 note pages.<br /> You lost B nonymous.<br /> You got THe Hope<br /> You got new theme "Ready to work as god"</p> <p>Theme "Ready to work as god"- Opening Theme, -50 stamina, to make bingo cost only 40 stamina.</p> <p>If you have chosen "Sick of Him! (Right)" then new quest aperas "The new enemy (C nonymous)".</p> <p>C nonymoes (alternative name "chocolateboy")- you get him 3 days after completing mission "Sick of Him! (Right)"<br /> +3 Nin. strenght, +5 succsess to enemy during tracking.<br /> Trivia- It is based on "M" (also know as Mihael Keehl or Mello) from anime death note. His name is made from Anonymous, just first letter has been changed from A to C (coz M was Third L).</p> <p>"The new enemy (C nonymous)"<br /> Requirements- C nonymoes, The Tote, Anonymous Lv2, Jonin Rank.<br /> Step1- Bee friend with right- I am hanging ou with Anonymous using friend points today.<br /> Step2- Say to Anonymous that fight is not over yet. Gen. Dif.15 Suc.25.<br /> Succsess massage- "So there is another one…"<br /> Failure massage- "I have done my job, I'm out of here."<br /> Step3- Make a contact with C nonymous. Nin. Dif. 25 Suc.15.<br /> Succsess massage- He has contacted with you erlear than you with him.<br /> Failure massage- Phone is colling, you answer and hear "Hi I am Mello". Your answer "… And I am queen of england, very funny guys", those pranksters. (you can not to take this mission until pass 24 hours)<br /> You unlocked quest "The end of the game (to Anonymous)" and "The end of the game (to C nonymous)".</p> <p>Sider- It joins you if you bingo someone with nonte page wile C nonymous and LisaLisa Lv2 in your team.<br /> If you have C nonymous and Ghem in your team, There is possibility (50%) that you can neautralise imunitet to note page of enemy in bingo.<br /> Trivia- Sider is based on Sidoh from anime Death note.</p> <p>"The end of the game (to C nonymous)"<br /> Requirements- to have Sider, finished "The new enemy (B nonymous)".<br /> Step1- C nonymous Whants 11 thousand of note pages. Explain him tha he needs only 10 Gen. Dif.20 Suc.30.<br /> Step2- Give him 10 note pages.<br /> Step3- Face C nonymous, and explain that those things dose not work for you. I have immunitet to note page.<br /> Step4- Defeat his gangs and defeat him. Tai. Dif.10 Suc.30.<br /> You lost C nonymous.<br /> You got THe Hope<br /> You got new theme "My job isn't done yet"- Battle theme, -50 stamina, If enemy in bingo have The Tote or The Hope bloodline, then you do double damage to him.</p> <p>"The end of the game (to Anonymous)"<br /> Requirements- to have Sider, finished "The new enemy (B nonymous)".<br /> Step1- Find C nonymous, and make a deal with him. Nin. Dif.20 Suc.30.<br /> Step2- Give him 10 note pages.<br /> Step3- Learn Anonymous real name. Gen. Dif.30 Suc.4.<br /> Step4- Write his anonymous name in to note page.<br /> You lost Anonymous.<br /> You got THe Hope<br /> You got new theme "I am to smart for you"- Battle theme, -50 stamina, +20 levels in bingo.</p> <p>These themes you get only after looping to new season.</p> <p>When you have all 4 these themes you unlock new quest The hopeless</p> <p>The Hopeless<br /> Requirements- To Hope, All 4 Hope themes, 50 Juicy apples, non bingoed, bingoed 20 non bingoed ninjas today, 1000 bingo style points.<br /> Step one- Monster a[ears before you "You… you are the one hwo is killing all those people. You are doing my job. Now I have no work, I am god of death, No! I am god to god of death, and I came here to destroy you, because my creatures have not work to do. Prepear to die… Snif snif… Are these apples???<br /> Step two- give him 100 juisy apples. (if you faill at any step of this quest, then you will be bingoed for 48 hours, This time can't be shortened)<br /> Step Three- Wow they are delicious, I have to clean the world from likes of you.<br /> Step four- I know I could leave you allone if you would do my job. (what the hell… He whanted to kill me, that I could not do his job, and now… well what ever).<br /> Step five- I have bingoed 20 ninjas, hwo had The Hope, today.<br /> Step six- "you have done good job, I will join you"<br /> Nut skull has joined you.</p> <p>Nut skull- If he is in your partu over night then +10 note pages -100 stamina.<br /> Trivia- Nut skull is based on King of Death (Shinigami King) from anime death note.</p> <p>Quest "I am sick of note pages"<br /> Requirements- Nut skull in your team, Sanin rank, 100 note pages.<br /> Step1- I have to plenty of note pages, I am sick of them, Nut skull help me.<br /> Step2- "I will but I need something in exschange, I whana 200 note pages." give him 200 note pages.<br /> Step3- "that's not all. I whana enough apples for all year." give him 365 juisy apples.<br /> Step4- "How much is this worth for you?" give him 500&nbsp;000 ryo.<br /> Step5- "I whana part of your life force" Give him 500 stamina.<br /> You got The Note book.</p> <p>Note book- You can use it like Note page, but this item wont go away.This is a permanent item. This item loops. This item not trade able.</p> <p>Quest "The final trade"<br /> Requirements- Nut skull , Sanin rank, The Hope.<br /> Step 1- Nut skull is offering you to become like him.<br /> Step 2- "But I don't know are you worth it"<br /> Step 3- "Bingo 30 people for me" I ahve bingoed with note pages (or note book) 30 or more non bingoed ninjas today.<br /> Step 4- "Now bingo 120 people for me, this time you can do that not over one day." From this time the counter will start, and count how much you have succsessfully bingoed.<br /> Step 5- "Well I still dont know…" there is no end to it, you will have to bribe him. Give him 200 juicy apples.<br /> You got new bloodline "Real trade"</p> <p>Real trade-This bloodline loops. From now from every bingo you get 2 trade points, trade points loops. They can be traded to few things:<br /> Revival aura- cost 200 trade points. this item is one time use- unbingo all ninjas in your villige.<br /> Trade for unbingoing 1 trade point will unbingo by one hour.<br /> Life potion- cost 50. this item is one time use- +100 life in bingos for all day.<br /> Death finger- Cost 150. Permanent item, loops, not trade able. +20 damage in bingo.<br /> Death eye- Cost 300. Permanent item, loops, not trade able. You can see already bingoed ninjas (just like The Trade, but you don't need juicy apples)<br /> Life ring- Cost 150. Permanent item, loops, not trade able. +50 life in bingo.<br /> Scythe of death- Cost 300. Permanent item, loops, not trade able. +2 Trade points after succsessfull bingo.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-433942</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-433942</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 11:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ryuzaki Kawaii XIIII</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>Reborn! Eye</strong>~</p> <p><strong>Definition</strong>: Intense Power to overcome absitively posolutely everything</p> <div class="code"> <pre> <code>You remembered that you were shot in the forehead by a mysterious arcabaleno baby and gave you immense speed, power and will power that your eyes, hands and forehead emit fire and you are left with just your *insert odd pattern*-boxers!</code> </pre></div> <p>The RebornEye bloodline grants the following abilities:</p> <ul> <li>Adds level, strength, range and successes depending on any mission requirement.</li> </ul> <div class="code"> <pre> <code>Your RebornEye burns...</code> </pre></div> <ul> <li>Maximum bonuses depends on rank: <ul> <li>+1 as a Genin</li> <li>+3 as a Chunin</li> <li>+4 as a Sp. Jonin</li> <li>+5 as a Jonin</li> <li>+7 as a Sannin</li> </ul> </li> </ul> <ul> <li>You can learn RebornEye-specific jutsu.</li> </ul> <ul> <li>You have a 5%/11%/17%/23%/29% chance to have a sudden refill of stamina when your stamina reaches 0</li> </ul> <div class="code"> <pre> <code>Your Death Desperation gives you a sudden adrenaline rush!</code> </pre></div> <p>(This Bloodline is based from Vongola Bloodlimit from the manga series Katekyo Hitman Reborn!)</p> <p>This Bloodline has 3 levels:</p> <p>1.Death Desperatio<br /> 2.Rebuke Calmness<br /> 3.Zero Point Breakthrough</p> <p>explanaton and added info sooner or later…<br /> look out for Tuna Boy!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-341780</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-341780</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 23:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zolem</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Augh, this site won't let me log in! Anyway, I saw the name Black Eye and came up with an idea.</p> <p>BLACKEYE<br /> Origin: While practicing Taijutsu at a young age you failed so hard you punched yourself in the face. EVer since you've been excelent at withstanding pain.</p> <p>Effects:<br /> - Bingo timer 1 hour shorter per rank.<br /> - 10 fewer stamina lost from monster attacks (min 10)<br /> - + 1 strength per rank above chunin when fighting Kaiju<br /> - Lose 10 fewer stamina in Wasteland missions (but not Outskirt)<br /> - + 1 strength unafected by Wasteland<br /> - Natural Enemy with White Eyes, you each deal double damage to each other in bingo attemps.</p> <p>Esentialy it's a bloodline dedicated to the idea of endurance. It's good if you plan on fighting Kaiju a lot or focusing on the Wasteland. It's also good for bingoing white eyes users in a Black vs White motif.</p> <p>Specific Jutsu:<br /> Endure - 60C: On Specific missions there are rare items that cannot be obtained in the mission without useing this Jutsu (you are alerted to what the mission are, just like with White Eyes). None of these items are exclusive to the Black eyes, but they have a low drop percentage otherwise. Ofr example a +4000xp award in a B Rank mission instead of an A Rank.</p> <p>Learnable from Lee/Gai (both teach it):<br /> Feel the Burn - 60C: +3 levels<br /> Burn the Feeling - 100C: +1 Range +1 Strength</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-340810</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-340810</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2008 12:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zulikas69</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176854</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Battle of bonds</p> <p>This bloodline will loop and even genin could use it.<br /> this bloodline would allow to do special bingo style missions (Fighting missions), everything would go just like normal bingo, but you shoud to bingo one of your allies. There would be and battle of the bonds quests (like normal quests but it would have a lot with battle of the bonds fights.</p> <p>for example- you have few allies, you choose billy, then you go to bingo style fighting meniu and you shoud to defeat billy, billy would use only his jutsu (and basic jutsus like "Projectile Weapons: Kunai",combo jutsu(s) and second generation jutsu(s) ), if you loose you bingo yourself, if you whin you would get special xp and unlock his combo and second generation jutsu(s) in jutsu meniu .</p> <p>Second generation jutsus- they would be usefull in normal missions but theyr would have brilliant effect in Fighting missions or bingo (these jutsu could be learned only by sp xp).<br /> for example billy lv3 would have "dodge in air jutsu"- halved damage witch will be taken from oponent. (requrement to know shadow clone jutsu)<br /> combo jutsus- they would be usefull only in Fighting missions and in bingo, this jutsu could be learned by normal xp, these jutsus woud requere to use some kind of jutsus before you use combo jutsu.<br /> for example billy lv1 - first use shadow clone and then rendan (barage).</p> <p>For example I will cratte few combo moves:</p> <p>Billy lv1: Up and down rendan- requires to activate Shadow Clone Jutsu before this jutsu, +3 levels and +1 strenght in taijutsu, +3 damage in bingo and battle of bonds fights, 100c. 50,000 sp xp. (trivia- Up and down rendan is based on naruto uzumaki barage)<br /> 10,000 fists in the air- requires to activate Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu before this jutsu, +5levels, +2 strenght and +1 range in taijutsu, +5 damage in bingo and battle of bonds fights, 200c. 12000 sp xp. (trivia- 10,000 fists in the air name is taken from submersed song, This jutsu is based on Uzumaki Naruto Two Thousand Combo)<br /> Life is for Porn - requires to activate Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu before this jutsu, +3levels, +2strenght in genjutsu, oponent is stuned for next atack, 250c. 90000 sp xp. (trivia- Life is for Porn name is something simmilar to "the internet is for porn" song, this jutsu is based on harem jutsu.)</p> <p>Billy lv3: dodge in air jutsu- equires to activate Shadow Clone Jutsu before this jutsu, halved damage witch will be taken from oponent this turn.</p> <p>there would be and some alies, wich you could get only throu thease Battle of bonds missions. For example:<br /> Firsts 3 sounds- firstly you should make quest "Exam that failed"<br /> quest "Exam that failed part one"- require emosuke, billy and pinky, step one- you are near the dorrs, and note is on them "only genins can go in" - opportunity1- I am genin; opportunity2- Use disguise jutsu (you have to know it) and loose 100 chakra +100 chakra per rank.<br /> Step two- you enter in to hall full of genin ninjas. dont gat to much atention to yourself. gen dif 3+2 per rank suc. 5+3 per rank +2 if you use jutsu, mission.<br /> Failure massage- you got to much atention an you loose 10*number of suces needed more to succsess.<br /> succsess massage- you havent got atention at all.<br /> Step three- teen looking ninja with glass steps to you "hello. are you new here? I am third time here cos I faill al the time. but I have my ninja cards which shows me the info about all ninjas in this hall. I can show them to you." he takes them out but suddenly he is beieng atacking by other ninja. teen looking ninja drops cards on the floor. you quicly take them, even nowone notice that.<br /> Step four- you sit in roundom place in the hall. you begin to read problems of exam but even first is to hard for you. Half hour hase pased and you wrote nothing. here komes the final question "do you whana pass this exam"- opportunity1- yes; opportunity2- hell yoes.<br /> Bot of them leads to succsess, succsess massage- then you have passed.<br /> you got nija cards (+1 levels, allows to see oponents statisticks(not jutsus) like level, strenght, range and succsess in battle of bonds before you atack it) you unlocked battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 2"<br /> end</p> <p>battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 2"- Step one- you enter to forest of death. Raundom ninja has tacked you.Tai. Dif.3 Suc.4.<br /> faillure massage- you loose, how lame<br /> succsess massage- you beat thae crap out of him, but he runs away.<br /> Step two- suddenly massive wind blows your allies away from you. creepy looking ninja comes to you. endure his genjutsu. Gen Dif.7 Suc1.(none of your allies is helping you)<br /> faillure massage- you fall for genjutsu, you wake up in hospital, how lame.<br /> succsess massage- you faill his genjutsu.<br /> Step three- wow giant snake, and it is attacking you, beat snake. then you shoud beat this snake in bingo style battle.(none of your allies is helping you)<br /> faillure massage- you has been beaten by snake, how lame.<br /> succsess massage- you beat snake, but hardly, how lame.<br /> Step four- your allies has retuned, now you can show him how strong you are. battle snakeman(but weaker version) in bingo style fight (teamates help)<br /> faillure massage- you lost versus child loving ninja, how grouse.<br /> succsess massage- you show him how strong you are, but still lost battle.<br /> You unlocked battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 3". end.</p> <p>battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 3"- requires Lil' Whitey and Bruce Jr. in your team.<br /> step one- you take care of your teamates in forest of death, when suddenly team of ninjas has ataced you. battle Hairy in bingo style fight (only Bruce Jr. help)<br /> faillure massage- you lost the battle.<br /> succsess massage- you beat him, but Bruce Jr. hase fainted.<br /> Step two- battle handhole in bingo style fight (only Lil' Whitey help).<br /> faillure massage- you lost the battle.<br /> succsess massage- you beat him.<br /> Step three- Only one left. look atheres eyes and forse here to give you her scrool. Gen Dif.5 Suc.3.<br /> faillure massage- you lost and you where forced to give your scrool to her.<br /> succsess massage- it was easier then to steal candy from the baby.<br /> you came to center fo the forest<br /> Hairy has joined you. you unlocked battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 4.1", "Exam that failed part 4.2", "Exam that failed part 4.3", "Exam that failed part 4.4"</p> <p>battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 41"- requires team-lil shamy.<br /> Step one- fight versus Ms. bell in bingo style fight.<br /> when you succseed Ms. bell joins you.</p> <p>battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 4,2"- requires team-bugman.<br /> Step one- fight versus handhole in bingo style fight.<br /> when you succseed handhole joins you.</p> <p>battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 4,3"- requires team-Master P.<br /> Step one- fight versus jelyman in bingo style fight.<br /> Jelyman will join you.</p> <p>battle of the bonds quest "Exam that failed part 4,4"- requires team-emosuke.<br /> Step one- fight versus leechman in bingo style fight.<br /> Leechman will join you.</p> <p>Hairy- +2Tai. strenght. Can be taken in to wasetland.<br /> Jutsu- Metal sound-70c, +2Gen. levels, -1 level to enemy in bingo style battles for rest of the fight.<br /> Trivia- Hairy is based on dosu from naruto.</p> <p>Handhole- +1Nin. strenght and +2Nin. levels. Can be taken in to wasetland.<br /> Jutsu- masive sound-230c, +4Nin. levels, neutralise enemys jutsu for this turn.<br /> Trivia- Handhole is based on Zaku from naruto.</p> <p>Ms. bell- +1Gen. strenght. Can be taken in to wasetland.<br /> Jutsu- Loose in shame- 600c, you can get an ally drop, mission event, item or even level ally in mission even if you faill on it.<br /> ring my bell- 200c, +2Gen. levels, you take only 50% of damage, but you do only 70% of damage to enemy.<br /> trivia- Ms. bell is based on Kin Tsuchi from naruto.</p> <p>Jelyman- +4Tai levels<br /> Jutsu- Jely bones- 200c, +2 tai levels, enemy can't atack you next turn but you do only 25% damage this turn.<br /> Trivia- jelyman is based on Misumi Tsurugi from naruto.</p> <p>Leechman- +2 levels, +15c every turn.<br /> Jutsu- Leech chakra- 100c, oponent loose 200c, you get 150c in bingo style fights.<br /> Trivia- Leechman is based on Yoroi Akado from Naruto.</p> <p>Some reaper allies:</p> <p>Baldy- +2 Tai. strenght +3 Tai. levels, it can be used in reaper missions..<br /> Jutsu- Self repair- 400c, +3 stamina, +5 Hp. in bingo style fights.<br /> Trivia- baldy is based on Ikkaku Madarame fom bleach.</p> <p>Spike hair (alternative name "Barbarian" or "Konan Barbarian")- +1 Tai. range +3 Tai. strenght +5 Tai. levels, it can be used in reaper missions.<br /> Jutsu- Release berserk- 600c, -50 stamina , +20 Tai. levels (for 2 turns or missions in a row), double damage in bingo style fights (only for one turn).<br /> Trivia- Spike hair is based on Kenpachi Zaraki from bleach.</p> <p>Lil pinky- +1 Nin. range +2 Nin. strenght, it can be used in reaper missions.<br /> Jutsu- Make a fun of him- 400c, +5 stamina.<br /> Trivia- Lil pinky is based on Yachiru from bleach.</p> <p>Beauty boy- +4 levels, it can be used in reaper missions.<br /> Jutsu- You are beutifull, no mater what they say-450c, 10 times mission ryo, silver petal need.<br /> Trivia- Beutifull boy is based on Yumichika from bleach.</p> <p>later I will post more inf.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-326237</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-326237</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 06:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This one isnt so much a bloodline, but a Blood Pact, sure.</p> <p>Vow of Poverty</p> <p>Cost - lose all your ryo, 2 of each ally drop, and treasure items at dayroll. unappraised items stay, and everything in your bucket is safe. Gambling in the party house costs an additional 10%</p> <p>Bonuses -</p> <p>Ally find chance is Tripled.<br /> Ally drop % is doubled.<br /> Gain an additional 20% ryo from regular missions (think of it as donations to the hobo)<br /> Collection Bonuses are doubled for non-village leaders</p> <p>Obtained through a special mission. I'll come up with more later.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-322690</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-322690</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 19:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Neko Hibiki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>199746</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd make the Shoujo-Ai bloodline.</p> <p>This bloodline is only effective with an all girl team though.</p> <p>Abilities : Get 1 stamina for each girl on your team back on a regular mission now.</p> <p>Drops : 1 sexy picture of all girl team.</p> <p>Jutsu : 10 chakra - Wow Hey Look At This (requires 1 sexy picture of all girl team) effect : Causes automatic win due to enemy passing out from a nosebleed.</p> <p>How to aquire : Special mission that opens when you have the Rack and Yuri as allies then.</p> <p>Requirements : Have the Rack, and Yuri as allies. Have 5 hot pictures of Terri and 5 hot pictures of Robogirl too. Must solve a complex matheatical puzzle also.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-306329</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-306329</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 03:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>lol honestly, the bloodline described by Ren Po Ken is the Rinnegan, also made fun of in naruto D20 forums as the "Win-a-gon"</p> <p>it learns any jutsu, you have 6 bodies, and you're practically invincible in the ninja realm. It's Pain's bloodline, purple eyes with multiple rings</p> <p>yes, he is overpowered. and honestly, why disrupt the balance?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-305027</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-305027</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Chong</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>234881</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Lol</strong></span></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-303682</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-303682</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 23:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>Blood Shot Eye With Dilated Pupils</strong><br /> How would it be obtained you may ask you must complete special mission Rehabs for Quitters and next season this blood line will be amongst the starting bloodlines.</p> <p>Get an extra 165 appitite per day<br /> -65% Ryo for Expenses *chough* those eyes dont get like that for free mow<br /> Summons Hallucination Based Monsters At random Which have lets say a 30% chance of turning on you (bad trip)<br /> Missions only cost 8 stamina because of the layed backness of this bloodline</p> <p>Arena card<br /> Harsh Hit if you win the turn with card activated counts a winning 2 turns but if u lose it counts a losing 2 turns</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Jutsus</span><br /> Wake&amp;Bake -2 levels -2 sucesses +5 to range… if this is first jutsu used that day gain + 60 stamina<br /> (Chakra Cost 450)<br /> Tore Up From the Floor Up +7 levels -3 Successes -260 Ryo +8 range +2 Strenght -35 stamina -2000 Jutsu XP<br /> (Chakra Cost 375)<br /> Roadie Drive around with your allies after the misson and gain a additonal 500 friend points per allie<br /> (chakra Cost 210)<br /> Get Fried +2 to Doujutsu levels<br /> (chakra Cost priceless naw just playing 300 )</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Eye of the Tiger</strong></span><br /> How is it obtained? by lasting 8 rounds with Apollocreed</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Jutsus</span><br /> Adrian's Revenge -6 levels, +5 range +2 Successes (chakra cost 255)<br /> -40 stamina +8 range<br /> Montage 100% ap/xp Gain</p> <p>Bonus allies<br /> Rocky +2 levels + allows you to summon *Itallian Stallion*<br /> Mic +4 to ninjitsu levels<br /> Mr.T +45% Ryo ( I pitty the foo who wif out da Ryo )<br /> +other random rocky allies</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>QueerEye (for the ninja Guy)</strong></span><br /> Bloodline coming soon to a ninja near <span style="text-decoration: underline;">you</span>!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-292594</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-292594</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 12:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BloodyANBU</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>128570</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>* summons stay as allys<br /> * +50% ryo<br /> * black eye jutsu available-allows user to have +5 lvls on all Tai Nin and Gen and +50%friend points for victory<br /> * more allys available such as Inuyasha Kagome Shesshomaru Shippo Sango and Koga. You must have both heck butterfly and swallowtail butterfly to attain<br /> * Also available are Agumon Gabumon Guilmon Veemon Armadillomon and Gaomon, all of them can be upgraded<br /> * all allies are permanent and can be used just as all other allies in game</p> </blockquote> <p>Black eye sounds a little too overpowered to me. I mean….. all your allies stay with you? You might want to cut that off. But if it has a HUGE amount of missions needed to get it, I guess I can't object. But the first power is only useful when you're in a powerful village, so it's not much of a use. And besides, summons are supposed to leave after a set period. It's too many allies as well. You might want to separate the Inuyasha ones into a different bloodline. Sorry, I didn't mean to sound mean.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-292123</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-292123</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 21:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i would make the black eye</p> <ul> <li>summons stay as allys</li> <li>+50% ryo</li> <li>black eye jutsu available-allows user to have +5 lvls on all Tai Nin and Gen and +50%friend points for victory</li> <li>more allys available such as Inuyash Kagome Sheshomaru Shippo Songo and Koga must have both heck butterfly and swallowtail butterfly to attain</li> <li>also available are Agumon Gabumon Guilmon Veemon Armadillomon and Gaomon, all can be upgraded</li> <li>all allys are permanent and can be used just as all other allys in game</li> </ul> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-239691</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-239691</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 23:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Katagara</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>183613</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>DOH, forgot to log in before posting that &gt;_&lt;<br /> Wanted to put this here so its not an anonymous poster XD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-239687</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-239687</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 23:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I personally would like to see Healing Touch make the game, but I doubt it would. If it were added, it'd have to be in the form of a mission chain that is triggered by buying a village upgrade, like Ringeye from Burgerninja, in this case it would be medical ninja facility. Here's how I think it would start.</p> <p>Down With the Sickness<br /> You feel strangely weak after your last mission, something must be wrong.<br /> Oh Crap</p> <p>You fall to your knees and feel yourself slipping away. You refuse to die like this! You do a quick monologue to deepen your character (This is what death scenes are for of course) and decide that your will survive this!!!<br /> Go Me!</p> <p>Tai Mission<br /> Fight it!<br /> Don't die, you're the main character!<br /> 12 Difficulty 19 Success</p> <p>Success! You fight the feeling, but you finally succumb to the feeling and pass out</p> <p>Failure! Its too strong and you pass out without even putting up a fight</p> <p>You awake in a white room facing 11DBHK<br /> "You are dead *Insert Player Name Here*, but you can get back."<br /> Ok, cool</p> <p>"Only those with the power of death itself can return from this place"<br /> I have 'True Blood of the Reaper'<br /> Success! He nods, "Good, good"</p> <p>Fail! He shakes his head and sends you back in shame</p> <p>"You have been killed by the Fail virus, but if you can defeat it here you can return to your body."<br /> O rly? Bring it on!</p> <p>Nin Mission<br /> The Cure<br /> Feel the virus inside you and destroy it<br /> 15 Difficulty 15 Success</p> <p>Success! You find it and destroy it, you're that full of win.</p> <p>Fail! You mistake your spleen for the virus and destroy it, ouch!</p> <p>"There, you are now completely free of fail. Now take all of the win in your body and condense it."<br /> Easy!</p> <p>Gen Mission<br /> The Cure Part 2<br /> Feel the Win!<br /> 16 Difficulty 14 Success</p> <p>Success! You feel the win flowing through your veins and send it all to your hands!</p> <p>Failure! You accidentally send your win to your head and give yourself a headache, ow!</p> <p>11DBHK chuckles and waves his hand. You awake in your village's Medical Ninja Facility with a nervous looking guy with glasses standing over you. "H-hey! This one's c-coming to!" An old looking guy in a lab coat comes up beside you and pats you on your shoulder. "Amazing, you're one of the first to actually survive the fail virus and be awake this soon, congratulations!" He hands you a Lab Coat. "If you have survived this, it means you must have the Healing Touch, a force of pure win that makes you immune to the Fail virus. Go home and get some sleep, tomorrow you will be working here with Dr. Style to help control this outbreak. See you then! The nervous looking doctor shakes your hand and says (With a lot of stuttering and gasping) that his name is Dr. Style and that he will be working with you.<br /> You got the bloodline Healing Touch! (You are immune to the Fail virus and can now participate in Medical Missions!)<br /> You got a Lab Coat! (+1 Range)<br /> Dr. Style Joins You!</p> <p>That's how I'd see the starting mission would be. In Medical missions you would lose 10 stamina after every mission due to how depressing your environment is ("Your depressing workplace bums your out, -10 stamina") and you could only use allies found there and The Rack and Haus. The Rack and Haus would each have justus that the bloodline give you like The Rack would have Medical Style: Hottie Recovery 300c Restores 5 stamina and +1 strength and Haus would have Medical Style: Breaking the Rules 500c +3 Range +2 Stam -100 Friend Points from your current team and Medical Style: Last Resort 600c Instant win 1 regular mission but disband your current team.<br /> Dr Style's stats would be +2 Strength, +2 Range on Medical Missions -25% AP, XP, and Jutsu Experience (He'd lose this part and improve the first 2 parts when he levels up, which marks his change from a screw-up to a doctor in the game) and would have basic medical jutsus like Medical Style: Incision 100c +2 strength, Medical Style: Bandage 200c +2 range, and Medical Style: Never Give Up 50c Fail current mission and get back 8 stam. (Full stam would be a little unfair)<br /> From there, the allies would include Dr. Old, Nursey, Shaky (A parody of Hanataro from Bleach) Dr. Kastle, and (Maybe) an addition of parodies of the shows Scrubs and House including John D, Icy, Mr. T, Dr. K, Dr. Hate, The Foreman, Cutter, and Sweepy.</p> <p>Other jutsus would be things like Medical Style: I Get to Cut You Open, Medical Style: Examination, Medical Style: Play by the Rules, Medical Style: Crushing Criticism, Medical Style: Clear!, Medical Style: Scalpel, etc. You could use Healing Touch once a day to instantly win a medical mission. The shop would offer the new permanent items Gloves (+3 levels) and Scalpel (+1 Tai Range)</p> <p>I've thought out some other parts of it, but I feel like I've been rambling for the past several paragraphs. 0_o Wow, That was a lot of typing, any1 have any input on this? It'd be awesome if this was put in ^_^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-239548</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-239548</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Giffica</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>169382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes well if you didn't know what doujutsu is then they are eye techniques. Such as the sharingan and byakugan. The reason legacy have the different version or whatever(I have no idea i have just read. if you know help me)if because legacy is based of naruto. He doesn't technically have a bloodline besides the uzumaki clan blood. Therefore its different for legacy. saying that i do expect masters to add Hijutsu to the game as well. It is jutsu that requires blood line such as haku's or The Kaguya clan(Bones/kimimaro). Also all of your ideas are basically null and void because unless they are based of of anime too bad. WHy do you think he has sharingan and byakugan? Also trade is Death Note and reaper is Bleach. This new one is Code Geass.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-239510</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-239510</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 19:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well "Ringeye" made it into the game. But I don't think it's anything like what's describe here.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-233459</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-233459</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zulikas69</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176854</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>m</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-233455</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-233455</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 17:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zulikas69</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176854</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This would be my bloodline.<br /> Flame eye-</p> <p>Description: you like to see fireplace on fire. you are looking at it so long tha your eyes begin to burn. (require 20 note page)<br /> This bloodline loops.</p> <p>Powers:<br /> Fire style jutsu cost half chakra. it only for ninjas jutsu not for reaper jutsu.<br /> reduce bingo timer by half.<br /> +30 daily stamina. Double stamina wich you get per mission.</p> <p>jutsu- Flamig eyes- +2 levels, +2 strenght versus monsters (50c and can not be reduced)<br /> when jonin- Flamig eyes- +2 strenght, more +2 srenght versus monsters (60c and can not be reduced)</p> <p>new allies:<br /> G. Sensey- joins you after certain B rank mission. +2 ninjutsu range.<br /> G. man- lv1- joins you after certain C rank mision. +2 ninjutsu strenght.<br /> Lv2- levels after certain A rank mission. +3 ninjutsu strenght, +1 taijutsu strenght<br /> VulcanMan: lv1- joins you after certain D rank mission. +1 ninjutsu level.<br /> lv2- levels after certain B rank mission. +1 ninjutsu level and +1 ninjutsu strenght.<br /> Lv3- levels after certain AA rank mission. +1 ninjutsu strenght, doubles all fire style jutsu efects used in regular mision, but chakra charge costs more 5 stamina.</p> <p>New Jutsu:<br /> G. Sensey:<br /> Hands on fire- +2 taijutsu strenght (120c)<br /> Feets on fire- +1 taijutsu range (80c)<br /> I am burning!!!- +1 taijutsu range, + 2 taijutsu strenght (180c)</p> <p>G. man- lv1:<br /> bandage enemy- +2 ninjutsu range (120c) (not fire style) require fire eye.<br /> fire bang- +2ninjutsu strenght (80c)<br /> lv2:<br /> Black fire ball- +3 ninjutsu strenght (150c) require fire eye.</p> <p>VulcanMan: lv1:<br /> Iner fire- +2 genjutsu strenght, when bingoing +1 genjutsu range (120c already reduced) require fire eye.<br /> Fire clone- +2 ninjutsu and taijutsu strenght (280c)<br /> lv2:<br /> Fire arow- +4 ninjutsu strenght (260c)<br /> Flame sword- +2 ninjutsu strenght and range (200c already reduced) require fire eye.<br /> lv3:<br /> Regeneration- +100 stamina, can only be done once per day (400c already reduced) require fire eye.</p> <p>Teams:<br /> G. Sensey, G. man Lv1- team basic fire. +1 ninjutsu range, +2 taijutsu strenght.<br /> VulcanMan Lv3, G. man Lv2- Team eternity flame. After charging chakra +2 stamina, +4 ninjutsu range.</p> <p>I hope that bloodline is not over pwered.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-219267</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-219267</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2008 02:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>csmokey</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>126366</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hockey Mask in Shape of Skull(Hollow Mask)</p> <p>Strength +3<br /> Range +2<br /> Level +5<br /> Stamina<br /> It has a side effect of losing half your stamina to activate it</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-157122</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-157122</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 20:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I wanted to add that these Operate skills will use either an item to work (scalpel) or they can only be used 5 times a day.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-156794</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-156794</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 00:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>PotPie</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>121123</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The get away from the light seems kinda rigged for some reason. +10 range for -3 str and only 150 chakra?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-156007</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-156007</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 17:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Seyon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>89540</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>Healing Touch Bloodline</strong><br /> Could possibly be introduced way after pirates and drift racing. Available as a starting bloodline S3+.</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Description</span><br /> Bingo's are no longer as big a threat as they used to be, the new hot topic is Guilt. Guilt can only be obtained after bingoing someone a lower level than you or by using a note page to bingo them. Guilt will start draining stamina away from you each day, 1 stamina on day 1, 2 on day 2 etc… It can be removed with a special potion recipe ???. Someone with the healing touch can operate on someone with Guilt to remove it and give back the stamina lost as well as give that stamina to the operator. Guilt will cause the person who has it to be unable to bingo, spar with friends, go on special missions, are do anything related to NWW or Attacking/spying on villages. (I.E. only stamina use is regular missions.) I'm assuming that once BvS gets 10,000+ players, bingos are gonna start going insane. You can only receive guilt in S2+.</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Bonuses other than Healing Touch Ability</span></p> <ul> <li>Immune to GUILT</li> <li>+2 stamina per level each day</li> <li>Ninja Art Hottie Regeneration only takes away chakra use for the same day used.</li> <li>Can gain certain ninja medical abilitie jutsu, I.E. Kabuto's hands, healing others for stamina.</li> <li>Our style: Item gained after healing 10 guilts, may reduce bingo timer by one half of remaining duration. (DS Stylus reference)</li> <li>May spend 100 stamina and work in Village's Ninja Medical Facility for 5,000 Ryo, once per day.</li> <li>10 ryo bonus for failing training missions, 20 for d rank, 30 for c rank, 40 for b rank, 50 for a rank, 100 for s rank.</li> <li>Having 3 people with this bloodline unlocks new monster attack on village. Omega Guilt, 2,600 health, can only be defeated by a village leader using the healing touch on it. Village upgrade: Hinting Nurses, reduces the rate that guilt will grow in a sick ninja. Personal Upgrade: Cold Shoulder, no longer receive guilt from using note pages.</li> </ul> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">New Allies</span><br /> Dr. Style: joins you after jonin ascension. When in your party, you can perform the healing touch twice a day. +1 Strength<br /> Dr. Kastle: joins after you cure 1 guilt. +1 range, +1 strength.</p> <p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">New Jutsu</span><br /> Dr. Kastle:<br /> Operate: Don't touch the sides! +2 ninjutsu strength, +5 ninjutsu levels. (100c)<br /> Operate: What's this thing? +2 genjutsu strength, +5 genjutsu levels. (100c)<br /> Operate: Live dangit, live! +2 taijutsu strength, +5 taijutsu levels. (100c)<br /> Operate: Call it… +25 successes vs monster, cannot use jutsu the rest of the day. (0c)</p> <p>Dr. Style:<br /> Operate: I aint giving up. +10 stamina if you fail the mission, (50c), cause smokebombs are nice but they run out.<br /> Operate: Go away from the light. +10 range, -3 strength. (150c) It's risky to use motivation speech on a dying person.</p> <p>Feel free to add more…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-153050</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-153050</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 21:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Medin</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>118923</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>… so I'm easily amused, and I came up with this. (Warning: no real attempts to balance this have been made, although I think it should be possible.)</p> <p><strong>Ally</strong>: <strong>Francis</strong></p> <ul> <li>Acquired in Season 2+ on the C-Rank mission <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/mission:impersonate-a-star">Impersonate a Star</a>.</li> <li>Francis can take <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Idolmaster:_Xenoglossia">Idol missions</a>.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Effect</strong>: +2 Gen Levels</p> <p><strong>Notable Teams</strong>:</p> <ul> <li>Francis + Dino + S.D.: <em>insert bonuses here</em></li> </ul> <p><strong>Jutsu</strong>:</p> <ul> <li>Croon (BlueEye Jutsu, Idol Jutsu) (Chunin minimum): +2 Success (30&nbsp;C)</li> <li>My Blue Heaven (Idol Jutsu) (Sp. Jonin minimum): +4 Gen Strength (75&nbsp;C)</li> <li>MacHeath (Idol Jutsu) (no minimum): +2 Tai Success, +2 Tai Strength, +2 Tai Range, lose friend points instead of gaining them for this mission (100&nbsp;C) <ul> <li>Note: if friend points matter more for Idol missions, this should give +1/+3 Idol, not be limited to Tai, lose <em>triple</em> friend points, and cost 60&nbsp;C.</li> </ul> </li> <li>My Way (Idol Jutsu) (Chuunin minimum): Substitutes your highest-level stat (<em>after</em> all bonuses) for the actual stat being tested during a regular mission (mission rank * 25&nbsp;C)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Drops</strong>:</p> <ul> <li>Gold Record (rare, like Emo Rock CDs; used in Idol missions or sell for 500 Ryo)</li> </ul> <p><strong>Other</strong>:</p> <ul> <li>Looping with Francis yields the theme <em>???</em>.</li> <li>Becomes Francis Lv. 2 after a specific Season 2 Idol Special Mission, which also grants the permanent item <em>The Voice</em>.</li> <li><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/monster:evangelions">Evangelions</a> take an extra <em>n</em> damage per attack if you have Francis in your team (<em>2*n</em> for Francis Lvl. 2) as he flies them to the moon.</li> </ul> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-140569</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-140569</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 02:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mark1</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>97210</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>hmmmm lemme give this a shot</p> <p>Snake eye<br /> you get snakeman stuck in your eye</p> <p>Auto win all your mission<br /> get 10000% AP/Ryo/daily ranking<br /> get all the themes</p> <p>Yay my bloodline wins</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-140286</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-140286</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 19:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually Starcrier, it was originaly STAMINA, not chakra that the Jutsu cost. It actually made the Jutsu a little TO painful to use, since any player who was in a warring village would never get to play since it cost 50 stamina per use of the power. Switching it to an un-tradeable rare actually made the jutsu easier to use compared to what it used to be. Yes, though, I do agree if it had been Chakra it would have been way to overpowered.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-140065</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-140065</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 14:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Why does it need to be as powerful as the initial bloodlines? It's not an initial bloodline! It's acquired through missions, so it's power should probably be around the same as the other mission-acquired bloodlines.</p> </blockquote> <p>You're right, I kinda lost focus there.</p> <blockquote> <p>Chakra Scalpels - +2 successes - uses up a Scalpel (one of Pontoon's mission drops) : 30&nbsp;C - Adds a new option to the village menu called "Operate!" Once per day, by spending 30 stamina and a scalpel, you can reduce a fellow villager's bingo timer by 6 hours (9 hours if your village has a Medical Ninja Facility).</p> </blockquote> <p>Nice, though I would have called it Speedline Surgery since Chakra Scalpels are Kabuto's and The Rack's speciality. Actually, that gives me another idea:</p> <p>Medical Nins Bonus! - Regenerates 2 HP per round of a Bingo Attempt. Negates the Rack's Weakness. Like Girl Power, it would be a three man team that draws from a pool of people (The Rack, Yuri, Stalkergirl [She makes her own medicine], Stalkergirl Lvl 2, Pinky Lvl 2 [but not Lvl 1], Pontoon [Personally, I'm fond of calling him Euchre], Tumor, Hiruluk, Kureha, and Tony Chopper). The last 3 are One Piece characters who I hope will make the cut. They're practically the only characters I like in the series. What's with anime lately having awesome supporting and minor characters, but main characters I want to beat to death with my shoes? Naruto? One Piece? Pokemon? I don't root for the hero, I root for the villains. I offer them my shoes to beat the hero to death with.</p> <p>But I digress.</p> <blockquote> <p>The halve bloodline jutsu cost is pretty cool, but why would he let you use Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu for free? (I assume that's actually your intention, since giving back 125 chakra could be abused if the player's village has a Chakra Training Center or Jutsu Enhancement Tower) His "Six Paths of Pain" technique doesn't use shadow clones.</p> </blockquote> <p>No it doesn't, but I thought it would be a nice way to simulate it without making it an inherent +3 Lvls to the character. This way, you have to give up your jutsu to get the +3 Levels if you want to have another ally. By the way, for his innate bonus of halving bloodline justu cost, I meant only the initial three bloodlines. I don't want people thinking that all Reaper and Trade jutsu would be half cost as well. Also, I meant Chakra cost, so you still would need to pay full Stamina and item costs.</p> <blockquote> <p>Mega Chameleon - +2 Gen Range, +2 Gen Strength, +15 successes on the first round of combat during a bingo attempt, doubles the difficulty of tracking you for other ninjas.</p> </blockquote> <p>Personally, I don't believe that there really should be 40+ Difficulties for tracking ninja within ten levels of you. I would dump that last bit and add can be used for spying (probably attacking as well). I would also tone down the Auto successes of the initial bingo attempt. Probably to 10.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139933</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139933</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 08:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Starcrier</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>108481</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>that blue eye bloodline isnt too bad i think now that sutasafaia changed it instead of using a chakra cost for the healing jutsu( which is WAY overpowered i say) it needs a rare item to be used. Also doubling the chance instead of giving a +5% chance of getting an ally really balances the bloodline</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139843</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139843</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 02:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Altered Nova</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>81815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Depends on what you are comparing it to. If you're comparing it to The Trade or Reaper Blood, then yes it is overpowered. If you're comparing it to WhiteEye or the other initial bloodlines, not so much. Let's look at RedEye vs. WhiteEye vs. RingEye:</p> </blockquote> <p>Why does it need to be as powerful as the initial bloodlines? It's not an initial bloodline! It's acquired through missions, so it's power should probably be around the same as the other mission-acquired bloodlines.</p> <p>Mostly though, I'm just not seeing the point of a bloodline that's basically a fusion of two existing ones. Especially one that comes with a jutsu like this:</p> <blockquote> <p>Ringeye: Innate Jutsu, 100 Chakra, Effects of Lvl 1 WhiteEye or RedEye as appropriate.</p> </blockquote> <p>This bloodline weakens the Redeye and Whiteye bloodlines significantly by giving their abilities to ninja that chose a different bloodline. Frankly, if this bloodline existed, I'd expect most player that know about it to always choose Legacy when making new characters or looping, because they could get a watered down version of the Redeye and Whiteye by acquiring this bloodline, essentially giving them all three basic bloodlines.</p> <p>The fact that you have to be a Jonin helps a lot, but it still seems unbalanced, and unnecessary. I would prefer a version that only comes with the elemental jutsu discount, a very powerful ally, and a few awesome jutsu and summons. It would stand out more because it would be unique, and it would simply feel "cooler", in my opinion.</p> <blockquote> <p>Since Blackjack is primarily a surgeon, the Hand of God bloodline is basically your genetic ability to cut a straight line of an exact depth and length.</p> </blockquote> <p>That actually makes sense, and gives me an idea. Perhaps Pontoon (I'm going with the British name for Blackjack, unless someone else can think of something better) can teach you a surgery jutsu!</p> <ul> <li>Chakra Scalpels - +2 successes - uses up a Scalpel (one of Pontoon's mission drops) : 30&nbsp;C - Adds a new option to the village menu called "Operate!" Once per day, by spending 30 stamina and a scalpel, you can reduce a fellow villager's bingo timer by 6 hours (9 hours if your village has a <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:medical-ninja-facility">Medical Ninja Facility</a>).</li> </ul> <blockquote> <p>As part of a group, Hurt would give you back 125 Chakra each time you used Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu. On his own (Six Hurtin's coming your Way Bonus) he would halve the cost of Bloodline-Only jutsu (Any Bloodline).</p> </blockquote> <p>The halve bloodline jutsu cost is pretty cool, but why would he let you use Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu for free? (I assume that's actually your intention, since giving back 125 chakra could be abused if the player's village has a <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:chakra-training-center">Chakra Training Center</a> or <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/upgrade:jutsu-enhancement-tower">Jutsu Enhancement Tower</a>) His "Six Paths of Pain" technique doesn't use shadow clones.</p> <p>I got an idea for Hurt's Giant Chameleon summon too. It's invisibility trick makes it hard to find you, giving you a "sneak attack" bonus when you bingo someone else, and making it much harder to find you for other players that are trying to bingo you.</p> <ul> <li>Mega Chameleon - +2 Gen Range, +2 Gen Strength, +15 successes on the first round of combat during a bingo attempt, doubles the difficulty of tracking you for other ninjas.</li> </ul> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139796</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139796</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 01:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have modified mine a bit after reading through everything, to re-balance a bit. Granted I never saw mine as particularly powerful, but now it's just a bit more useful. Changed what the requirement was for the Jutsu, since having to use 50 stam per shot would make players NEVER take the BlueEye…you know…since villages would get pissed at you for not un-bingoing them, and then you would get no stam for the day. Also, since all Note Pages are rare and you cannot trade them, you would not be able to give them all to the BlueEye</p> <p>BlueEye</p> <p>Description: A doctor tried to take your temperature as a child and slipped, sticking the thermometer into your eye. You've been interested in medicine ever since!</p> <p>Powers:<br /> 2 stamina discount on regular missions and in chakra recharging<br /> 10 stamina discount on special missions<br /> Double chance of finding and leveling allies</p> <p>Jutsu: Healing Arts Jutsu<br /> Cost: 0 Chakra, Requires a Note Page: Un-Bingo a member of your village</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139710</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139710</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 21:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>argent</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99364</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Once you become a special jonin if you are already not a reaper you auto become one</p> </blockquote> <p>Wait… the bloodline gives you a bloodline?</p> <p>The second ability requires a village to be useful. The first ability requires a extremely powerful village to be useful. The 7%+ chance of autowin needs clarification: does it advance like a RedEye's bonus XP? Or are you just not certain what level to set it at? How would it stack with Billy's autowin?</p> <blockquote> <p>Allies level on 1st try of a leveling mission</p> </blockquote> <p>Alright… this is a high level bloodline ability for RedEyes or a hard to acquire theme. Both require a substantial outlay of money to make possible unless you are very, very lucky. And I'm going to assume you mean that they level if you succeed in the mission.</p> <blockquote> <p>Jutsu costs are deducted by half in season 2.</p> </blockquote> <p>So wait… in season 2, you get the high level ability of <em>another</em> bloodline?</p> <p>Yeah. This is a mite too strong. And it sounds like you're presenting this as an initial bloodline…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139704</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139704</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 21:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Getting to auto-reaper? Your kidding right? A higher chance of auto-win than Billy, getting all your allies to level right off the bat, permanent summons, and half off all your jutsu costs? That sounds waaaay to strong.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139652</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139652</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 20:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That sound like a really nice bloodline actually too nice I think you would have to put some drawbacks on the bloodline like less stamina and more jutsu cost. I think it would be 10 less stamina per rank and 10% more jutsu cost. I would also add some more stuff to it that is more practical for beginning players because right now the 7% auto-win is the only one for beginner players.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139625</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139625</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Teh Kaz</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>101519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The Thunder Eye</p> <ul> <li>Summons stay in youre party</li> </ul> <ul> <li>bingo duritation is decreased by half</li> </ul> <ul> <li>Once you become a special jonin if you are already not a reaper you auto become one</li> </ul> <ul> <li>7%+ chance of auto- win</li> </ul> <ul> <li>Allies level on 1st try of a leveling mission</li> </ul> <p>when doing the jonnin exam the last mission part for it for Thunder eye is.<br /> 10/10 ninjutsu<br /> Defeat the Thunder God</p> <p>once it is defeated you obtain Kiroke(Kirachi from naruto)<br /> Jutsu costs are deducted by half in season 2.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-139489</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-139489</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 15:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>That RingEye bloodline sounds WAY overpowered… seriously, it practically obsoletes both WhitEye and RedEye. I realize you're trying to be accurate to the source material (in Naruto, the Rin'negan actually does obsolete both of those bloodlines), but that particular absurdly powerful bloodline is one that probably shouldn't ever make it into the game.</p> </blockquote> <p>Depends on what you are comparing it to. If you're comparing it to The Trade or Reaper Blood, then yes it is overpowered. If you're comparing it to WhiteEye or the other initial bloodlines, not so much. Let's look at RedEye vs. WhiteEye vs. RingEye:</p> <table class="wiki-content-table"> <tr> <th></th> <th>RedEye</th> <th>WhiteEye</th> <th>RingEye</th> <th>Winner</th> </tr> <tr> <td>Extra XP/AP</td> <td>+7%/Rank</td> <td>None</td> <td>+3.5%/Rank</td> <td>RedEye</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Extra Levels on Missions</td> <td>None</td> <td>+1/Rank</td> <td>+.5/Rank</td> <td>WhiteEye</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Innate Jutsu</td> <td>RedEye</td> <td>WhiteEye</td> <td>RingEye</td> <td>RingEye</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Jutsu Levels at Jonin?</td> <td>+1 Strength</td> <td>+2 Levels</td> <td>No</td> <td>RedEye/WhiteEye Tie</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Bingo Insight?</td> <td>RedEye Level</td> <td>None</td> <td>1/2 RedEye Level</td> <td>RedEye</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Bloodline Only Jutsu?</td> <td>Yes</td> <td>Yes</td> <td>No</td> <td>RedEye/WhiteEye Tie</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Elemental Cost Reduction?</td> <td>No (but can get certain ones cheaper)</td> <td>No</td> <td>Yes</td> <td>RingEye</td> </tr> <tr> <td>Additional Ingredients?</td> <td>No</td> <td>+1</td> <td>No</td> <td>WhiteEye</td> </tr> </table> <p>I didn't include Legacy because it's nothing like any other initial bloodline. It looks balanced against the other initial bloodlines, or is because it stacks with White/Red Eye and Legacy that you say it's overpowered? Remember, you can't get it until Jonin.</p> <blockquote> <p>The Hand of God Bloodline is pretty sweet too, but I'd give the players the ability to remove themselves from the advertising board if they don't want to sell their services for a while, and blacklist certain villages or players that they don't want to help. Also, they could set a maximum daily limit to the number of times other people could buy their services, if they don't want to find themselves at less than 100 stamina every time they log in. Also can we really call it a bloodline? Technically, it's a profession, not some genetic ability. But then again, I don't think The Trade quites makes sense that way either.</p> </blockquote> <p>Since Blackjack is primarely a surgeon, the Hand of God bloodline is basically your genetic ability to cut a straight line of an exact depth and length. Some people can (with practice) others never will, no matter how hard they try. The rest of it is practicing your innate talents, just like all the other bloodlines. And no, the trade doesn't make any sense this way, but we're looking for logical connections in a parody game, which probably tells you something about us.</p> <p>Your other suggestions are good ones.</p> <blockquote> <p>You'd have to set up a hell of a special mission line for this Bloodline though. It's not exactly easy to become a world-famous mercenary doctor!</p> </blockquote> <p>Yes. Yes I would. I would probably want to watch the rest of the BJ TV series first, then try to blend elements from both the OAV series and the TV series. Besides, how can you not love a medical X-Files?</p> <p>Tumor is actually a reference to Pinoko, as she started life as a Teratogenous Cystoma.</p> <blockquote> <p>Also, what kind of bonus do you think Hurt would give you, and would he team with anyone?</p> </blockquote> <blockquote> <p>Like Billy, Hurt would be his own team.</p> </blockquote> <p>That pretty much sums up my opinion on the matter. As part of a group, Hurt would give you back 125 Chakra each time you used Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu. On his own (Six Hurtin's coming your Way Bonus) he would halve the cost of Bloodline-Only jutsu (Any Bloodline).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-138635</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-138635</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 23:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sutasafaia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90006</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I would also make one called GreenEye, although it would have a different effect than the one already made.</p> <p>Description: A doctor tried to take your temperature as a child and slipped, sticking it into your eye. You've been interested in medicine ever since!</p> <p>Powers:<br /> 2 stamina discount on regular missions and in chakra recharging<br /> 10 stamina discount on special missions<br /> 5% increased chance of finding and leveling allies</p> <p>Jutsu: Healing Arts Jutsu<br /> Cost: 50 Stamina, Un-Bingo a member of your village</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-138623</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-138623</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 22:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>argent</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99364</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Like Billy, Hurt would be his own team.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-138582</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-138582</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 21:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Altered Nova</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>81815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That RingEye bloodline sounds WAY overpowered… seriously, it practically obsoletes both WhitEye and RedEye. I realize you're trying to be accurate to the source material (in Naruto, the Rin'negan actually does obsolete both of those bloodlines), but that particular absurdly powerful bloodline is one that probably shouldn't ever make it into the game.</p> <p>I'd either weaken the bloodline by limiting it to it's other effect - mastery of all six elements (giving a large chakra discount to all elemental jutsu known) and giving it some powerful unique bloodline jutsu. Either that, or make this bloodline limited to season 3+.</p> <p>Some possible unique jutsu (assuming you capture Hurt to use as an ally after gaining the bloodline):</p> <ul> <li>The Six Paths of Hurt - +6 levels, +6 strength, +6 range, +6 successes : 600&nbsp;C. This is Based on Pein's "The Six Path's of Pain" technique, in which he can summon up to 5 clones to battle by his side. These clones are unique in that they aren't formed from chakra, they are literal genetic clones of Pain's former allies, grown in a lab, and they all share one mind with him. He can control them flawlessly, they all share eyesight, and they are apparently immortal, as the only way to defeat Pain is presumably to kill him and every clone simultaneously.</li> <li>Illusionary Dragon Nine Consuming Seals - +10 range vs. Monsters, 400&nbsp;C. If used against the Demon of the Sand or the Nine-Tailed Fox, there is a small chance (increasing with the number of times used) that you will obtain the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:spirit-of-the-demon-of-the-sand">Spirit of the Demon of the Sand</a> or the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:spirit-of-the-nine-tailed-fox">Spirit of the Nine-Tailed Fox</a> upon the monster's defeat, even if you're not the Kage. This is obviously based on the jutsu Pein used to extract the bijuu from their hosts and seal them into that large statue.</li> <li>Summons - Pein has used at least six different summons in the manga, so you could allow the player to learn several of them from him. I'd probably use that Giant Chameleon one, it was pretty cool cause it could turn invisible. Not sure how that would work mechanically though.</li> </ul> <p>The Hand of God Bloodline is pretty sweet too, but I'd give the players the ability to remove themselves from the advertising board if they don't want to sell their services for a while, and blacklist certain villages or players that they don't want to help. Also, they could set a maximum daily limit to the number of times other people could buy their services, if they don't want to find themselves at less than 100 stamina every time they log in. Also can we really call it a bloodline? Technically, it's a profession, not some genetic ability. But then again, I don't think The Trade quites makes sense that way either.</p> <p>You'd have to set up a hell of a special mission line for this Bloodline though. It's not exactly easy to become a world-famous mercenary doctor!</p> <p>Is Tumor supposed to be Blackjack? I would figure you'd give a card related name, like Poker or Pontoon. I'd make his bonus be if you are bingo'd while he's in your party, recovery time is halved. What kind of jutsu (if any) would he teach you though?</p> <p>Also, what kind of bonus do you think Hurt would give you, and would he team with anyone?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-138357</guid>
				<title>Re: If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-138357</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2008 15:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>RingEye<br /> This is not a selectable bloodline, you would have to earn it like the Reaper Bloodline.</p> <p>After going Ronin for 30 days as a Jonin and having completed 30&nbsp;S-Rank missions, you are allowed to join the Akasuki in a special mission. This will be a big multipart mission with many sub-missions, one of which will be capture (bingo) someone who has either one of the Kaiju themes or an item that gives you a theme (may change this to only someone with one or both themes. Garra was a season 2 character when he was captured after all.). The ability to bingo would be granted from the Special Mission theme, and only those with the theme/spirits would be available.</p> <p>The bingo is not a normal bingo either. While the victim would not loose their theme or item, Red Water would not reduce bingo time, and they couldn't use Cure Right Wounds. When you complete this mission, you would get Extracted Spirit (of whichever one you get). Another factor, for seventy two hours, the victim's village will have the ability to bingo you despite the fact that you're not in a village (A special Ronin 'village' would appear in their bingo screen) Also the use of note pages in both the first bingo and retaliatory bingos would be forbidden.</p> <p>This Extracted Spirit is given to the Akasuki leader, Hurt, in the next and penultimate special mission of this section. You would then have to beat up Hurt in the final special mission and pluck his eye out and put in your socket.</p> <p>What the RingEyeactually does:</p> <ul> <li>+3.5% AP/XP per Rank (cumulative with Redeye). Does not round.</li> <li>+.5 Levels per rank on regular missions (round up, cumulative with WhiteEye)</li> <li>Ringeye: Innate Jutsu, 100 Chakra, Effects of Lvl 1 WhiteEye or RedEye as appropriate.</li> <li>RingEye does not level (so you will not get +1 Str and/or +2 Lvl from using</li> <li>You would receive the occasional insight when bingoing like a Redeye does (but it's only half as likely to occur).</li> <li>RingEye does not give you access to WhiteEye or Redeye only jutsu (but if you all ready were a White/Red Eye, you don't loose them).</li> <li>Jutsu with an Elemental effect (Fire Style: Whatever, Blizzard Jutsu, The Shocker, probably others) will cost half chakra. Reaper jutsu would not be affected even if the name or description implied an element (like Archer Style: Fire and Flame jutsu).</li> </ul> <p>This is a reference to Pain or Tobi (I forget which) from Naruto.</p> <p>Another Bloodline I would make<br /> Hands of God</p> <ul> <li>In exchange for 100 Stamina, you would unbingo someone.</li> <li>There would be a board advertising your services, with a list of fees (most likely two fees, as you would probably want to give people in your village a discount) in Ryo. You set your own fee, with a minimum of 10,000 Ryo.</li> <li>Once a patient clicks on your name in the board, the fee would be deducted, you would loose 100 Stamina, and the patient would be unbingoed.</li> <li>Once your stamina dips below 100, your name is removed from the board until next dayroll. Your name will not be returned earlier, even if you raise your stamina level above 100.</li> <li>A Kage can allow someone to draw on Village Ryo rather than their own. This would be done via a permission.</li> </ul> <p>You would also get an ally with this bloodline, Tumor (may form a team with Sicko) who would reduce the Stamina loss for unbingoing a patient to 75.</p> <p>This bloodline is a Blackjack reference, rather than a Trauma Center reference.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256#post-137937</guid>
				<title>If You Could Make A Bloodline...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-51256/if-you-could-make-a-bloodline#post-137937</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 23:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think I'd make GreenEyes.</p> <ul> <li>+7% ryo per rank (like how RedEyes get +7% XP per rank).</li> <li>The GreenEye Jutsu would let you reroll one die per rank, maybe. I'm not sure exactly about how to do this one.</li> <li>GreenEye-specific jutsu available from MC Stripeypants, Billy, Cato, The Rack, and other wealthy/merchant/lucky/unlucky ninja. Would require the use of Sham Rocks for more powerful jutsu.</li> <li>Slightly higher luck on the Prize Wheel and on the Slots.</li> </ul> <p>…think that would cover it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>