<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>The bug?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271/the-bug</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;The bug?&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:10:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271#post-148623</guid>
				<title>Re: The bug?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271/the-bug#post-148623</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Something went screwy with the second science machine specifically (the one that will give your village an additional +50 Stamina). Basically when you're in a village that has the Science upgrade the formula for computing your daily stamina changes</p> <p>from: Whatever it was before<br /> to: Whatever it was before+Science Bonus</p> <p>Science Bonus will be either 50 or 0 depending on whether or not you manage to trigger it.</p> <p>Now here's that part that was bugged: Instead of doing addition, it instead did concatenation. So instead of 300+0 or 300+50 giving you 300 or 350 respectively, you instead got 3000 or 30050.</p> <p>Some people went nuts. Some people (*waves*) didn't even notice until after it had been fixed despite being online at the time and instead bug reported the bonus stamina that was deliberately given out as compensation for the confusion.</p> <p>Concatenation, by the way, is what javascript does by default. Which is dandy when you're working with text, but sucks when you're making an online game (or a calculator for an online game, or trying to add 2+2).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271#post-147790</guid>
				<title>Re: The bug?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271/the-bug#post-147790</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 04:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Here's the scoop.</p> <p>If you were in a village that had science! activated yesterday, you got roughly 10x's the stamina you would have gotten. If you used this stamina, you got nothing. If you didn't use this stamina, you got purple specs which give +1 tai strength. If you didn't get any stamina from the bug, you didn't get anything.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271#post-147691</guid>
				<title>The bug?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54271/the-bug#post-147691</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 00:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mark1</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>97210</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So I logged on today and I saw the big announcement about everyone getting super stamina and people who didn't use it get a super item…. So then what is this all about I didn't notice anything when did this accure?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>