<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Looking for a Quartermaster</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467/looking-for-a-quartermaster</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Looking for a Quartermaster&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:04:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467#post-148411</guid>
				<title>Re: Looking for a Quartermaster</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467/looking-for-a-quartermaster#post-148411</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Works for me! naito's got the job!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467#post-148409</guid>
				<title>Re: Looking for a Quartermaster</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467/looking-for-a-quartermaster#post-148409</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i am on a lot each day and i will stay in the village. if you will have me i will take the job</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467#post-148375</guid>
				<title>Looking for a Quartermaster</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-54467/looking-for-a-quartermaster#post-148375</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Here's the skinny: I don't have the time or desire to micromanage the storehouse. However, I don't think it's a good idea to give everyone full access to the storehouse; we have really high turnover and that'd just be asking to have our storehouse ganked. Is there anyone who's been in the village for a long time, who plans on staying, who would be willing to be the Village quartermaster?</p> <p>In effect, I'd give you the ability to change people's attributes in the village. You'd be able to set who can take permanent items and who can just take everything in the storehouse. And also, who can't take anything at all. (Technically, you'd have the ability to change who can attack and who can spy, but I'd very much prefer you not play with those settings).</p> <p>Your job? Watch for requests for permanent items (or for other item swaps) and reset people's permissions to be able to do what they need to do. These requests may come either in the village chat log or in the forums here. So, you'd just have to watch for both. Checking once a day is sufficient, in my opinion.</p> <p>I should also say, I currently like the 5 item per day limit. When someone dumps a large number of items that are in high demand (see Silver Petals or Tasty Burgers), I don't think the first person who sees them should be able to take all of them. I'd prefer they be distributed widely amongst those who need them, and I think 5 a day is a fair way to do that. So, this position should <em>not</em> be used to take more than you (or your friends) would normally be able to take. But it can be used to facilitate trades (for example, if someone wants to give 50 petals specifically to another person).</p> <p>Would anyone be willing to do this job?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>