<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Make A Village</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989/make-a-village</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Make A Village&quot; - A create village wiki page</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989#post-153391</guid>
				<title>Re: Make A Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989/make-a-village#post-153391</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Omnifox</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>83749</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thx Boss.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989#post-153382</guid>
				<title>Re: Make A Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989/make-a-village#post-153382</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Now at <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/make-a-village">Make a Village</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989#post-153375</guid>
				<title>Make A Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55989/make-a-village#post-153375</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 17:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Omnifox</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>83749</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you can here is the link A create village wiki page</p> <p>If you can't get in there then here is the text:</p> <p>Village Creation<br /> Okay, time to start a new village.</p> <p>Villages cost 50,000 Ryo to start. That money will be the start of your Village Bank.</p> <p>You need to come up with a village name, and also how your village description looks.</p> <p>For example:<br /> Village Forest - the Village Hidden in Trees.<br /> Village Pants - the Village Hidden in my Pants.<br /> Village Whirlpool - the Village Hidden in the Sea.<br /> Village Infinity - the Village Hidden in Forever.</p> <p>Your description is important - it must be descriptive of your village.</p> <p>Please note that you may need to put a 'the', like in 'The Village Hidden in the Snow' - it isn't automatically there)</p> <p>People will see this when you do things, so it should be indicative of your village. Do NOT do something sneaky, like 'Sand Village - the Village Hidden in the Waves'. Your village will be deleted if you do.</p> <p>No punctuation or multiple spaces - keep it simple. Capitalization is important - if you don't want your village to look like a bunch of fools, make sure things look nice. You won't be able to change them.</p> <p>Look at the list of Villages and players already out there - don't try to copy a name, call yourself 'mist' when someone else has 'Mist', or name yourself 'M1ST' village and crap like that. We'll delete you.<br /> When you start your village, your village will be placed near a natural resource - one of three. This is the resource you will use to bribe Clients and create specific upgrades. To get ones you don't have, you'll have to hit other villages.</p> <p>Ready? Okay then. Name your Village!</p> <p>Village "Your Name" - the Village Hidden in "Your Description".</p> <p>Create Village (50,000 Ryo) &gt;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>