<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Question about Themes/Looping</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813/question-about-themes-looping</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Question about Themes/Looping&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:22:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813#post-152967</guid>
				<title>Re: Question about Themes/Looping</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813/question-about-themes-looping#post-152967</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 18:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Alright, thanks.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813#post-152962</guid>
				<title>Re: Question about Themes/Looping</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813/question-about-themes-looping#post-152962</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 18:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You get the themes that you earned in previous seasons. So, I started S2 with: The Flash, Teacher's Pet, Battle of Champions, Warstruck, Drunken Fist, Money for Nothing, All Together Now, Out on Top, and Seasons Don't Fear. Had all of them the very first day. But yes, I do believe that you have to wait until you loop again to get a new theme that you unlock in S2.</p> <p>There's an exception to this: Floating on Air is instantly gained.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813#post-152960</guid>
				<title>Question about Themes/Looping</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-55813/question-about-themes-looping#post-152960</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2008 18:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Alright, I have a pretty simple question for anyone who's looped:</p> <p>When you loop, do you get themes that you "earned" in the previous season? For example, if I have more than 45 allies in Season 1, then when I loop, will I get the All Together theme, or will I have to reacquire my allies in Season 2? The same thing with Battle Champions, Drunken Fist, The Road to Womanhood, and any other that you get by gaining something that you lose when you loop.</p> <p>The looping guide seems to suggest that by "unlocking" a theme in Season 1, you'll get it when you loop, but the description of the themes seems to imply the opposite.</p> <p>Also, if you do get such themes by "unlocking" them in Season 1, does that mean that themes unlocked in Season 2 don't become yours until Season 3? Like, if I would not get Bruce Lvl. 2 this Season, but got him in Season 2, would I get the theme immediately, or would I have to wait until I loop again to get the theme?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>