<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Long Term Planning</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397/long-term-planning</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Long Term Planning&quot; - Post-Epic Wiki!</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:03:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397#post-156786</guid>
				<title>Re: Long Term Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397/long-term-planning#post-156786</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2008 00:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Omnifox</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>83749</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>lol if you will still have my 2 cents I would suggest bumping the quiet glade up. It helps you alot. If you get the right monster you will be more or less be hunting for ingreds for free, which will be great if you achieve your Science plan.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397#post-155084</guid>
				<title>Re: Long Term Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397/long-term-planning#post-155084</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 06:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Kravick</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>96795</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm glad to have you as Kage, Uzuki. Putting thought and reason behind upgrades makes us all the better for it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397#post-154002</guid>
				<title>Re: Long Term Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397/long-term-planning#post-154002</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 18:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Schon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>88446</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As a village we have been kicking butt! And this is due to everyone in the village participating. We have a great resource in this wiki and it has really helped to bring us together as a village. I'm proud to be a member.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397#post-153968</guid>
				<title>Long Term Planning</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56397/long-term-planning#post-153968</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>First, I want to start off by saying that this village has been amazing. It's taken us less than two months from when the Village was first created to being an Epic village with 50 members. I'm not sure that any Village in the game can compare with that! You're all incredible and I'm really proud of you all.</p> <p>Now that we've gone Epic, the dynamics of our upgrades will change a bit. We're actually starting to run low on useful upgrades that we can purchase (though, to be sure, there are still quite a few as well!). We're moving into the territory where we're going to be using Science! much more often and focusing quite a bit of our efforts on monsters. With that in mind, I think I should share my thoughts with the rest of you as to how we should proceed.</p> <p>From here on, I intend to invest in Science! every day until our machine gets up to 100% reliability. (I've actually been doing this for over a week now, so it shouldn't be a huge surprise). Once it gets to 100% reliability, the intention is to unleash one day and tinker the next, such that we have a chance at rare ingredients every other day. This will also increase our production of basic resources for summoning purposes. Once we kill the Mad Scientists, we'll step this up even further and tinker and activate every single day.</p> <p>The other thing I would like to do is increase the rate at which we summon monsters. Up to this point, I've kind of expected everyone to throw everything that they have at the kaiju, because I was unsure if we'd be able to kill them. After we destroyed Storm Riders in a little over two days, I'm fairly confident that monsters will die with minimal effort on our part. So, I would like to summon monsters more often, but that doesn't mean I expect the village to spend all their time attacking monsters. For the most part, you can attack the monsters as much (or as little) as you want. So long as the monsters aren't destroying any of our upgrades, I don't particularly care how fast they die. But, keeping a constant stream of monsters does two things for us: (1) it gets us cheap, upkeep free upgrades, and (2) it gives the villagers powerful items that aren't available in any other way.</p> <p>In terms of purchasable upgrades, I think the most important one we need right now is the Elemental Harmony. Our upkeep is just too high right now. After that, I'd consider the following relatively high priorities: Sneaky Tricks, and Ninja Cooks. Moderate priorities in my mind are Tools of the Trade, Hard Corps, Ninja Dog Kennel, Ninja Ambassadors, Ancient Teachings and Quiet Glade. Everything else (that I can think of at least), seems low priority to me.</p> <p>So those are my thoughts! Again, keep up the good work guys, I'm glad to have you as my fellow villagers!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>