<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>new genin ascension</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56377/new-genin-ascension</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;new genin ascension&quot; - the genin exam is no more... (sigh)</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:22:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56377#post-153924</guid>
				<title>new genin ascension</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56377/new-genin-ascension#post-153924</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Geff</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>101148</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>here is what comes now when you make a character:</p> <p>** If you refer someone, you get +100 Stamina for the day</p> <p>You walk up to the Genin Exam, ready to go. Flipper, the Genin Exam Proctor, waves at you. "Hey there, <strong>name</strong>, are you ready for a long and involved tutorial?"</p> <p>You punch him in the junk. Right in the junk.</p> <p>*koff* *koff* "Agh, what the crap! ackk.. *koff* okay, okay, here's the short version:</p> <p>You start with 150 Stamina a day, which you use to start Missions and Special Missions, Collect Resources for our Village, and so on.</p> <p>Bonus Stamina is easy to get! There're two bonus codes on your Main page, posting a sig banner will get you Stamina when people click it, not to mention awesome Invite Bonuses!</p> <p>Your Abilities (Gen, Nin, and Tai) let you attempt to get Successes on Missions.</p> <p>Jutsu, Teammates, and Items get you bonuses to Levels (more attempts), Strength (better attempts), and Range (higher possible attempts).</p> <p>Get enough Successes to Defeat a Mission! Get Items, Allies, Jutsu XP, Ability AP, Ryo, and more!</p> <p>Is the Mission too hard? Use Jutsu! Jutsu cost Chakra and Items. Use Stamina to Charge Chakra, and hit the Store to buy more Items.</p> <p>Special Missions advance the plot, rank you up, and unlock tons of awesome things, from Reapers to Dance Contests!</p> <p>You can drink one Potion a day from your Main page! Get Stamina, items, bonuses, and more!</p> <p>Villages are a bunch of Ninja that can get Village Bonuses, fight other players in the Ninja World War, fight Monsters, get Summons, invade other Villages, and more.</p> <p>The How to Play covers everything, so you should read it sooner or later.</p> <p>…agh.."<br /> He was going to say more, but he collapsed. Oh well. You grab him by the collar and drag him off to do some Missions.</p> <p>You learned the Projectile Weapons: Kunai Jutsu!<br /> You got 15000 Jutsu XP!<br /> You got 250 Ryo!<br /> You got 2 Kunai!<br /> You got +50 Stamina!<br /> You got 1 Bitter Medicine!<br /> You got the ally Flipper! (+1 Levels for Attributes under 3!)<br /> Flipper joined your team!</p> <p>You are now Genin!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>