<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Explanation</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56143/explanation</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Explanation&quot; - New Friend points system.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56143#post-153665</guid>
				<title>Re: Explanation</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56143/explanation#post-153665</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 07:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Read again. And possibly look at the current friend rankings.</p> <p>All allies who, at <strong>this morning's dayroll</strong>, had been acquired by at least 10 players, AND where the top player had 5000+ friend points, are hanging out with all 10 people on their top 10 list today.</p> <p>The only ally who has been acquired by 10 people, but doesn't meet the second condition, is Mister Tea. All other allies, save for LisaLisa and the new ones that have only 1-3 people on their list, meet both conditions.</p> <p>As for the rest of your post…hanging out will go back to normal tomorrow. The major changes will be Top 10 list instead of Top 3, and an ally can hang out with more than 2 people as explained at the end of the news line. And yes, a number of people will probably get Nadeshiko tomorrow.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56143#post-153662</guid>
				<title>Explanation</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-56143/explanation#post-153662</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 07:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>New Friend Franking System: The new friend ranking system shows the top 10, and allows one person to hang out with an Ally per day - two if the top friend points are over 5000, and then +1 for every 25000 points the top friend has (so an ally with 75000 points would have the top five players hanging out. one for free, +2 at 5K, 3 at 25, 4 at 50, and 5 at 75.).</p> <p><strong>To flush out some of the allies, all of them that have at least 10 players who have obtained them and are over 5000 top points will all be hanging out with their whole top 10 today.</strong></p> <p>What does that mean?</p> <p>Ninja have to posses at least 10 allies?</p> <p>Of those you have: should have friend level over 5000 or get today over 5000 friend points?</p> <p>Will this help with <strong>Nadeshiko</strong>?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>