<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Monsters</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57147/monsters</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Monsters&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:03:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57147#post-155604</guid>
				<title>Re: Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57147/monsters#post-155604</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yeah, actually. I've had some of that lingering in my head for a bit now, and I hadn't really been able to organize my thoughts properly about it. How's this for a compromise:</p> <p>(1) All enticed monsters will be enticed at some random time after 12 noon server time from now on.<br /> (2) I'll give warning at least 24 hours in advance of a summon.<br /> (3) People will try and save stamina to kill a monster late in the day on summoning days if it's possible that they can play later in the day.</p> <p>Up to this point, I've tended to summon early in the day because people are more likely to have stamina and because certain monsters get stronger or regenerate some health after a day has passed. For these strengthening and regenerating monsters, we want to kill them in as few days as possible, and that means making it available early in the day so people don't use their stamina on other things while there's a dangerous kaiju hanging around. Truthfully? I'm not really scared of this anymore. So summoning later in the day is fine with me (so long as people keep an eye out for Nine Tails, Sand Demon, or the 20k monsters and treat them accordingly).</p> <p>For those who can only play early morning, you've still got an advantage on some kaiju. Every day there's a 10% chance of getting a random kaiju right at the day roll (our Cockroach today was a random one, we didn't summon it). You guys will get first dibs at those. So, to be fair to the other guys, we'll do our summoning later in the day.</p> <p>But one final note: The kaiju we got today were really wimpy (the roach only had 1,400HP. A Sannin could actually solo that on a good day. The Pokermans were about twice that, but still &lt; 3000 HP). Wimpy kaiju aren't going to last very long regardless of when they show up. It's just a bit of luck when it comes to those. Even if you don't manage to get an item from a kaiju, you still get the benefits of the upgrade (which, in many cases is actually more important than the item).</p> <p>But yeah, I'll see what I can do for ya Lear, you've got a very good point.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57147#post-155596</guid>
				<title>Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57147/monsters#post-155596</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 20:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay, so we're becoming a pretty powerful village, and with the exception of the 20,000 HP monsters, our village can take down a monster increadibly fast. Too fast actually. Today we fought two monsters. The first one was dead by around 8:30 and the second was summoned immediately after and died around 10:45, which creates a problem for me, and I'm sure others as well, because I can't possibly get on any earlier than 1:00. Some days not until 3:00. As a result, I don't get any chance to attack the monster. Ordinarily, this wouldn't be a problem, but almost every single monster we've fought has arrived in the morning, and it's incredibly frustrating when, time after time, I find that the monster was killed 3 or 4 hours before I could get on. For all the monsters our village has fought so far, I've only ever actually been able to attack two, the very first one, and the Storm Riders we fought recently.</p> <p>So, I'm asking if perhaps, Uzuki could summon a monster in the afternoon occasionally? Otherwise, I'm not going to see another monster until I get out of school in another month. And I'm sure it's not just me. I can't imagine I'm the only one who can't get on at 8:00 in the morning. Especially if you had already fought a monster that morning. It's extremely irritating to find that not only was one monster killed before I could get on, but a second one as wel because you were compelled to summon the second monster immediately following the first for, presumably, the same people to fight. It seems to me that if you'd already fought one in the morning, it would make sense to wait until the afternoon to allow some other people to fight it. You know, spread it out a little bit because I, and anyone else who can't get on so early, would like at least a chance at a monster item every now and then.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>