<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Sannin JXP theory</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277/sannin-jxp-theory</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Sannin JXP theory&quot; - tell me if im even close</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:22:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277#post-156010</guid>
				<title>Re: Sannin JXP theory</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277/sannin-jxp-theory#post-156010</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is jediwaldo (im at work) and the damn site won't let me log on -.-</p> <p>Yeah if you want to put it up that is fine. The spreadsheet I plan on redoing incorporating redeye bloodline(the xp bonus), and whiteeye bloodline (zero bonus). Especially since Legacy gets that extra bit of stamina.</p> <p>There are a few things I want to add to it. Since to get obsessive insight you need Anon I figured to prep correctly the night before one needs to have LisaLisa in your party in your party the night before so you get her bonus to make up for the 10-20 stamina loss from the Trade. (or a glowing mood ring if you couple hanging out bonuses).</p> <p>Plus, since I did this early this morning it might take some time to fix some of my errors issues. I can also reformulate for generic bloodline, I can also set it up for requried and recommended items/things to get done.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277#post-155936</guid>
				<title>Re: Sannin JXP theory</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277/sannin-jxp-theory#post-155936</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 14:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Nice work.</p> <p>Could someone put this in Experience Guide on BvS Wiki Page if jediwaldo agrees.</p> <p>It nice help for Sannin run or Jonin Ascension (Season 2+).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277#post-155920</guid>
				<title>Sannin JXP theory</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-57277/sannin-jxp-theory#post-155920</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 13:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jediwaldo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>104443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I decided to make a spreadsheet with technical goings of a season 1 legacy player and the play by play on how to get Sannin.<br /> <a href="http://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=pZt5r007Dmu9pZMIFn-v8Yg&amp;output=html">http://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=pZt5r007Dmu9pZMIFn-v8Yg&amp;output=html</a><br /> I hope its helpful. I plan on using this (slightly modified) to get my sannin. My village has the Sand Demon Monument (+1 stamina back per mission), Fox Monument (+1 back per charge), and soon to be Spartan Battleground (50% chakra costs, obsession insight will cost 1/2 :D)</p> <p>Also, here is the list of what is recommended by people to achieve Sannin.<br /> <a href="http://docs.google.com/Doc?id=dgsms2qg_0dgsd7sfr">http://docs.google.com/Doc?id=dgsms2qg_0dgsd7sfr</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>