<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Hanging Out Question.</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204/hanging-out-question</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Hanging Out Question.&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:23:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204#post-159029</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging Out Question.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204/hanging-out-question#post-159029</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 05:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Wow Bruce JR. ? Make Out Mood enhancer would be awesome but I don't have it, or Bankai, yet.<br /> So save up on Ryo til I got enough for maybe three parties. Or in that case wait till tomorrow.Go on B-rank missions till I get J-Diddy with Bruce Jr. and TicTac. Use The Ninja-Mas Spirit, and do the best I can to get the Love Love Paradise.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204#post-159025</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging Out Question.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204/hanging-out-question#post-159025</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 05:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I was typing up a response as well, but Uzuki beat me to the punch. However, a few added notes:</p> <p>Using Make-Out Mood Enhancer with Bruce Jr. as the only member of your team would work as well, but those are quite difficult to come by.<br /> You can also get Friend Points at the Party House in the Party Room. All-Out Bashes, yielding 10k Friend Points for 20k Ryo the first two times each day, gives the most friend points for each ryo spent.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204#post-159022</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging Out Question.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204/hanging-out-question#post-159022</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 04:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you hang out with an ally, your friend points get reset to zero. Nothing else that I can recall reduces friendship points, so you can do it across as many days as you need. Each day that you don't hang out with an ally, your friendship points stay. Whenever you get relatively near the top of the friend rankings, you'll hang out with that ally automatically (you don't get to choose when it happens). Silver Elixir does nothing to friend points, Silver Potion does, but it's not worth using.</p> <p>Best way to get friend points is to party with J-Diddy, TicTac, and whoever you want to hang with (your case, Bruce Jr., not Sr.). Then run missions while using the Ninja-Mas Spirit (taught by the HoClaus). If you're in season 2, use Battle of Champions theme. If you've gotten lucky, you'll have Love Love Paradise. Then just run missions. Any missions will do, but preferably ones that you can pass regularly. After a couple days, you should be hanging with Bruce Jr.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204#post-159020</guid>
				<title>Hanging Out Question.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58204/hanging-out-question#post-159020</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 04:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I want to get the note. So to do so I want to get the theme "Floating on Air" I need to hang out with Bruce Sr.<br /> I have a few questions. Do you have to get it all in a single day? Can you stack multple days? and what does a Silver Elixer do to friendship? Or does it do anything? I'm new to hanging out XD</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>