<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>The Other Side</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647/the-other-side</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;The Other Side&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:32:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647#post-160638</guid>
				<title>Re: The Other Side</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647/the-other-side#post-160638</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 15:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You need to be Jonin to be that far in the mission, so he shouldn't have to worry about range too much, aside from the low success mission (where Timmy2, Sword Jutsu, +NWW item gets you by). But, yeah. Fletch's jutsus are probably the strongest jutsu available for those missions.</p> <p>Truthfully, by that point in S1, I just Shorty's Kido for each mission, and ran a party of Tats, Fletch, and Timmy2. That seemed sufficient at the time.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647#post-160606</guid>
				<title>Re: The Other Side</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647/the-other-side#post-160606</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 14:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It would have been more appropriate to post this in the Missions section than here in the General section.</p> <p>That aside, permanent items are always a good help in completing missions. You'll probably bring Tats and Fletch along for +2 Range/Strength, and perhaps bring Timmy Lvl 2 for the +2 Successes. Combined with Shikai and Sword of the Reaper, you'll be at +1 Level, +4 Stength, +2 Range/Success with this set-up…not counting other permanent items you may have, or your rank if you're Sp. Jonin or Jonin.</p> <p>If you aren't Sp. Jonin (Nin) or Jonin, you'll need to use Kido:Slayer for the second part for the range ( you should have 13 with Fletch and the Ninja Dog item ). If you don't have enough levels or permanent items to feel confident on the first and fourth checks, you could probably just use Kido…if you'd barely be making it with that, you might want to look into Fletch's jutsu ( which give +4 Strength in one stat but require his ally drop ), or Strawberry's and Robogirl's jutsu ( which give +4 Levels in one stat )</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647#post-160574</guid>
				<title>The Other Side</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58647/the-other-side#post-160574</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 13:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well I'm getting Shikai today and I'm three allies and alot of silver petals away from the "Adventures in the Otherside"<br /> mission. And I'm just wondering…how do you complete The first, second, and fourth part of the mission?</p> <p>The third has low succeses, and the last one has low strength. So I'm set there.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>