<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Hanging-Out Guide.&quot; - anyone interested??</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:20:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-407078</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-407078</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 11:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sta</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>… ignore my post, please.</p> <p>I still think there should be a hanging-out guide, but I suddenly see that I'm hanging out with all three my allies. :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-407077</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-407077</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 11:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kor</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>after the recode all 10 first spot are Hanging-out</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-407076</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-407076</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Sta</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi,</p> <p>I've got only 5189 friend points with chunks and now I'm hanging out with him, while the highest has 8991. I'm fourth in the list with friend points, how is that possible?</p> <p>I'm trying to time it to do the eye of the storm quest.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-352567</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-352567</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 06:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>LBD</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is why we need a guide</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-349826</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-349826</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 02:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MM007</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thank you very much. That was the point of confusion with me. I always interpreted it as "you hang out with the ally you have the most friendship points with".</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-349807</guid>
				<title>Re: MM007</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-349807</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 01:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous Poster</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>no buttons are needed to hang out. when you have enough during dayroll, it happens automatically.<br /> you can check the current friend points @<br /> <a href="http://www.animecubed.com/billy/friends.shtml">http://www.animecubed.com/billy/friends.shtml</a><br /> the bolded names are the people who are hanging out today…<br /> at a quick glance, you need ~95k friend points to hang out with stalkergirl.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-349801</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-349801</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 01:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MM007</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Some think hanging out is easy, and some hard…but I don't know how. I'm an S1 Chunin by the way.</p> <p>I have over 23K Friendship Points with Stalkergirl, 21K with Bugman, and 17K with Red Rover; but have no idea how to actually set it to hang out with any of them. What buttons do I have to click to make this work?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-313374</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-313374</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 01:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm not sure what the hanging out guide would say?</p> <p>Once you are hanging out with an ally, you: learn their jutsu at half JXP cost and can use it for half chakra cost during normal missions. You can also pass special missions that require you to be hanging out with an ally.</p> <p>To hang out with an ally, you need to be listed in bold on the current friend point rankings for the day, or use an ability that provides an instant hang out (floating on air, make out mood enhancer, tsuki-ball, mysterious powers).</p> <p>That's the entire guide, isn't it?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-313212</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-313212</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 22:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>portwizard</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>181794</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thats just sad its so simple you get points from doing missions with an ally only points with the allies that are in your team at day roll the person that has the most points with an ally gets to hang out with them, yet there are other ways to hang out via FOA or MOME</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-313174</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-313174</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2008 21:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I only today found out proper how hanging out works. and i'm nearly looping to S3. This certainly warrants a guide.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-221244</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-221244</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 01:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Anyone you have the proper friend points with. They don't need to be in your team. (If they needed to be in your team, Nadeshiko would be really difficult).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-221242</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-221242</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 01:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've got a question about hanging out. I've never seen this answered anywhere I've looked.</p> <p>Can you only hang out with allies if they are in your party at the end of the day? Or can you hang out with anybody if you have the appropriate number of friend points? I'd assume you don't need them to be in your team, because of the requirement to get Nadeshiko…but…it's never been stated. If I can hang out with anybody I have the appropriate number of friendship points with I'm pretty sure I can hang out with four or five, maybe even six, of my allies after a couple of parties at the party house.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-194882</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-194882</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 10:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm fairly certain the base amount of friend points per mission is 25 with a 3-man team and 40 with a 2-man team…I haven't used only 1 ally in a month or two. Type of mission and mission difficulty have no bearing on the friend point gain, except for the missions that have +xxx friend points hidden.</p> <p>The max that can be earned from any mission using a 3-man team is 1600 friend points with the set-up Uzuki described. A-rank and AA-rank missions have a mission with 4000 friends hidden, as well.</p> <p>Also, since hanging out was recently changed to minimum of 3000 friend points, I'll swing by to update that on the Allies page…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-194583</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-194583</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 03:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I don't know about a guide, but something I've noticed is that the Wiki never mentions how many friend points you get per mission (at least no where that I could find). Perhaps that should be added somewhere. I'd add it myself, but I honestly don't know. =_= Nor do I know where it should go. I'd assume all missions of the same rank give the same amount. Do all missions in general give the same amount? I'd test it, but I'm out of stamina for today, and will likely be out of stamina for a couple of days before I could run around testing it (next two days = fighting EvilTaxi, day after that = Jonin run).</p> <p>I think there is some extra information that could be added (in fact, I'll add some now), but I don't think there's enough to warrent a full guide.</p> <p>Edit: Added a little bit of info. Removed statement that some abilities and summons require you to hang out with someone because a.) abilities is vague, could really mean anything b.) summons is incorrect; you need 300 friend points and to hang out with someone you need a lot more than 300, regardless who you chose (in fact, you need a minimum of 1,000 friend points anyway, regardless of what other people have).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-193761</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-193761</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 16:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>A hanging out guide would be great. I keep comming back to this page every once in a while.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-176466</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-176466</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2008 18:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/allies#Friendship">Allies::Friendship</a> isn't sufficient?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-173382</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-173382</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 15:21:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think that's more than enough to warrant a guide. The average BvS player probably doesn't understand the mechanics of hanging out, and considering a lot of the higher special missions require you to hang out, having a guide to link to would be helpful. I know I personally had to search for "hanging out" because I'm doing Robogirl lvl 2 and I haven't had to hang out before and there's no page about it.</p> <p>Plus the guide could list all the missions/theme/allies that require hanging out to finish/get/acquire.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-161541</guid>
				<title>Re: Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-161541</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm not sure hanging out really needs a guide, there's not a whole lot to it. Hanging out allows you to learn a person's jutsu for half the JXP cost and use it that day for zero chakra cost. It also lets you pass certain missions that require you be hanging out with an ally. There's four ways to hang out with an ally:</p> <p>First, you can have high friend points with that ally. (If the highest friend point holder has &lt; 5000, 1 person gets to hang. 5,000-24,999 two people, 25,000-49,999 three people, and +1 for every 25k after that). You get friend points every time you run a mission. To maximize friend points, you simple stack friend point bonuses (J-Diddy is 4x, TicTac is 2x, Battle of Champions theme is 2x, Ninja-Mas Spirit jutsu is 2x, and the item LoveLove Paradise is 2x), and then run missions until you're near the top.</p> <p>Second way to do it is with a <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:make-out-mood-enhancer">Make-out Mood Enhancer</a>. You set it up so there's only one person in your party, then drink the potion, and you're hanging out. You can get up to 2 this way.</p> <p>Third is with <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/theme:floating-on-air">Floating on Air</a>. Set your opening theme to Floating, then you'll be hanging out with all three allies in your party from overnight. You can get up to 3 this way.</p> <p>Fourth is the Mysterious Power Bloodline. If you refer 50 people, you can hang out with 1 ally per day for free if you're not currently hanging out with anyone. Max you can hang out with this way is 1.</p> <p>That's it, that's all the guide would have.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904#post-161389</guid>
				<title>Hanging-Out Guide.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58904/hanging-out-guide#post-161389</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 08:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Can we provide a hanging out guide??Since we all have those guides out there,maybe we can add this up. This can definitely help new or old players alike who would want to know how they can hang out with an ally. Maybe we can include the benefits of hanging out and all other stuff about it. Just a suggestion.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>