<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Winning in the arena?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Winning in the arena?&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160678</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160678</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 16:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Schon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>88446</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Advice #3 is something that I hadn't considered. Adding another yomi layer.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160662</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160662</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 16:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jkeezer</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>115701</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'll give this piece of advice as well. My old strategy, the one I don't use anymore, started off with using Tai as my first move.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160661</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160661</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 16:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jkeezer</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>115701</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Advice 1:<br /> The first round is the only completely random round and even then, it isn't. Anything after the first round is 3-Parts Strategy, 2-Parts Chance.</p> <p>Advice 2:<br /> A "no power" player can win against a "three power" player. I've lost before with all three powers to someone with none. But if you don't think out your moves carefully, you won't likely pull it off.</p> <p>Advice 3:<br /> You cannot defeat the Red Eye power (well you can but don't bother trying). If you know your enemy is going to use Red Eye this round, force them to use the stat that gives you the most benefit.</p> <p>Advice 4:<br /> Play 4 fights everyday without exception. Practice makes the game a whole lot easier.</p> <p>I have 171.5 Wins on 210 Fights.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160230</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160230</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 01:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You can, however, play the odds. It's possible to say "If I play Gen, I have a 33% chance of winning, 33% chance of tying, 33% chance of losing, but if I play Tai, I have a 50% chance of winning, 50% chance of tying, and zero % chance of losing" etc. Knowing such odds would let you make smarter decisions, but wouldn't tell you what you ought to play.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160189</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160189</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 00:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I doubt a 'guide' for winning would really be worth attempting…after all, only 50% of the players are winners, nothing will be able to change that.</p> <p>When it comes down to it, it's a mixture of 'chance' and 'how many times do I think ahead of my opponent?' For example, a scenario that might be common: P1 has G:2&nbsp;N:1&nbsp;T:0 and P2 has G:1&nbsp;N:1&nbsp;T:1. Depending on how P1 has played so far, the following things will be going through P2's head: "Is he going to use a Gen, which he has two of, meaning I use Nin? Will he expect that and play Nin instead, meaning I should play Tai?"</p> <p>The possible outcomes from that situation would effectively be one of the following, in the format of ( P1's card ) / ( P2's card ) with the winner of the exchange at the end of the line:</p> <p>Gen/Gen, Gen/Tai, Nin/Nin : P1 with +1<br /> Gen/Gen, Gen/Nin, Nin/Tai : P2 with +2<br /> Gen/Nin, Gen/Tai, Nin/Gen : P1 with +1</p> <p>Of course, that's just the overall result. If the match is still going by that point, either P2 is 1 point ahead or 2 points behind, unless bloodline abilities were involved, which would seriously complicate things. However, think for a moment: P1 is also strategizing his/her win, too, with the same thoughts going through their head as was mentioned going through P2's earlier. In this case, if P1 was two points ahead, and just needed one more, he/she may play differently than if the opposite case were true.</p> <p>Basically, what I'm trying to say is that because it's a Human that's the opponent and not a computer, trying to come up with a guide for winning seems like a fruitless endevour. While you could make suggestions, since you can't accurately put in a guide how to watch for different play styles, doing more is making poor use of your energy.</p> <p>I think I might support a very short section on how to recognize an unavoidable tie situation, and tell people to not 'stall' when there's nothing to do to change the fact…kind of gets annoying when one pops up, and suddenly I have to wait 20-30 seconds for the next round…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160178</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160178</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 23:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Any Wiki arena guide should involve lots of math, which is something I don't really have the time to do at the moment.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160170</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160170</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 23:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Harry Dresden</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>100189</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>(basicly the same as Mark)<br /> The way I win in the arena well lol i guess i should say draw lol.. I loose rarely (mostly when they have a bloodline special) other times i either draw or win lol. I play by luck basicly. I look at the opponets stack (like if they are all even 3&nbsp;3&nbsp;3 and such) then i play off the strongest one some will use the one they have the most of. But thats not always true, i play the one that kills the one they have the fewest of. And mostly win or draw. and so on. I would like to make a little guide on it if Uzuki will let me.</p> <p>Only heres the catch lol the catch is guessing there next move. You want to second guess your opponent which is not easy unless you have a truely powerful mind. The trick for me is well a secret lol…….But mostly I just watch. I play the card that they last played sometimes or play the card that can be defeated by the card they last played. Its quite confuseing. Uzuki if you want I can make a guide page for winning in the arena lol of course Your results "WILL" vary lol.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160140</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160140</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 21:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It was sort of revealed by McMasters that 50% of players open with the same card the other day. I imagine a lot of people have made a guess at what that card is, and have altered their playstyle since then.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-160132</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-160132</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Kaja Rainbow</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>92734</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Mark1, I tried that, but I seem to get a lot of people who play differently than what you said there.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-159550</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-159550</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 20:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mark1</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>97210</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well this is the stradigy I use- use Taijutsu twice then a ninjutsu (with luck you'll be one or two ahead) and then look at their stats most of the time they will look simular to this 2G 1N 3T or 2G 2N 2T…. if its 2-1-3 then go with gen because they will most likly not want to use their last nin and the worst you can get is a tie with this logic. now you have 2G 2N 1T and say they use gen so they now look like 1-1-3 the obvious one is use gen to counter their T and then you win with this stradigy I've never lost only tied and won except when they used super powers</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-159409</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-159409</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 16:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Also, try playing outside the dark hours… that's when the monochrome players are in the arena. They are all season two and the chance is high that they have a bloodline power (or even two!).</p> <p>On the other hand you get more points there if you win… take the risk?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-159266</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-159266</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 13:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>gurlag</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>121439</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is something I noticed, though it doesn't always work.</p> <p>Watch the timer closely. Everytime a round ends, it resets to 60. Once a round ends, see if the message "Waiting for You…" is immediately there (should be around 55-60 secs in the timer). If it is, play a card that beats whatever your opponent used in the previous round (he used Tai in round 4, the above situation appears, then you should use Gen in round 5). It's probable that your opponent clicked Attack twice (which happens, at least to me), and thus, he played a card twice (once in the current round and another for the next one). This only works if you opponent actually has 2 or more of whatever card he used.</p> <p>But like I said, this doesn't always work, so don't rely on it too much.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-158986</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-158986</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>A number of reputation points is a very good supplement to what you can't get of what Uzuki mentioned. I managed to get my first bloodline item with about 7k and about 1500 reputation points total a few days ago.</p> <p>Another helpful tip is to not try going 'all the way' on a day where after 2000 ryo, you only have say, 2-3 wins ( I decided when I had 3.5 wins from 4 matches, lucky start ). There is a fair ammount of luck to it, but starting out with an advantage is better than hoping you'll get what you need with the more expensive options.</p> <p>Also, while there are a lot of people with Bloodline powers by this time, most of the people I run into still don't have any. Given 4 or so matches a day, I would guess that I've only been running into one, maybe two people with the powers every other day.</p> <p>As for techniques…whatever you come up with that really works. The first 3-4 rounds of the match are usually very random depending on who you're facing, and the rest, you end up quite limited in what you can do.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-158977</guid>
				<title>Re: Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-158977</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 02:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>There's lots of different ways to approach it, but to be honest, things are a lot harder than when I first started. Lots more people are out there with Bloodline powers. I've heard with zero powers, you'll probably only have a 40% chance of winning in most cases.</p> <p>Personally, I play randomly if there's no strong position. When I say randomly, I mean really randomly. I use the random number generator at <a href="http://random.org/">http://random.org/</a> Sometimes you'll lose in 3 rounds if you get unlucky. Usually it'll go on for a few rounds. The game doesn't really get interesting until you get to rounds 5-9, where each side is limited much more in what they can do.</p> <p>But I've had a Legacy power for a while, and I just got my RedEye power as well. Powers make a huge difference.</p> <p>Ideally, you should start figuring out how to get your first bloodline power (and that requires getting 10 wins). 20k ryo, 2 emergency rations (and a hollow leg to use them) is a good start. You'll probably need a stack of reputation points to go the rest.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190#post-158944</guid>
				<title>Winning in the arena?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58190/winning-in-the-arena#post-158944</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 00:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hey folks, I'm trying to slowly get points for the arena items, but I don't really have a knack for arena matches. My win ratio is horrible. I'm actually pretty good at rock-paper-scissors in real life it seems there are different strategies involved.<br /> How do you guys win matches? Pick randomly?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>