<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Kinda Awakard.</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391/kinda-awakard</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Kinda Awakard.&quot; - A tiny question.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391#post-159705</guid>
				<title>Re: Kinda Awakard.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391/kinda-awakard#post-159705</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 06:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Myusha</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>124295</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Aww, that sucks. So four players out and I'm in? XD GET OUT PEOPLE XD jking. Anyway I'll wait till you get your four gone(good luck for your base upkeep). Soon I'll get Shikai, to stop any depression I may feel right now XD.<br /> Thank for the quick response and I'm willing to wait. I'll ask every month or so, or you could private message me.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391#post-159701</guid>
				<title>Re: Kinda Awakard.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391/kinda-awakard#post-159701</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 05:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>We'd love to have you aboard if we had room, but unfortunately we literally sit at maximum capacity on most days. We've got a full 50 players right now, none of which are non-playing. We've also got three more sitting in the queue at this very moment :( If you're willing to be patient to wait until some space opens up, I can let you in. But until some people stop playing, there just isn't room :(</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391#post-159700</guid>
				<title>Kinda Awakard.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-58391/kinda-awakard#post-159700</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 05:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Myusha</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>124295</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm from the Viking Village. But right now I'm Jounin and I want to try and take on Sannin eventually, and the useful theme 'Floating on Air' will take forever to obtain seeing as NRF hasn't even been purchased yet. Wiki seems far ahead then them, and overall a little better. So could I join Uzuki-Sama?</p> <p>I'll always owe the Viking Village but I feel like they're to slow.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>