<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>the trade?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;the trade?&quot; - why?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:32:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595#post-164612</guid>
				<title>Re: the trade?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade#post-164612</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 08:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>alright thx :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595#post-164435</guid>
				<title>Re: the trade?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade#post-164435</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 22:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You can have 3 themes active at a time: one opening, one battle, and one ending. You set your themes on one day, and they become active on the next. So if you set "All Together Now" today, it'll be active tomorrow.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595#post-164399</guid>
				<title>Re: the trade?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade#post-164399</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 21:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>mh… allright i guess i'm gonna do it then… thx :)</p> <p>ahhh but one thing about themes… let's say i'll get .. i dunno 10 themes. are they all "active" permanently? or is it somewhat like teams? i mean something like you can change it once everyday after that it's stam penalty? if it is like that.. how many themes can you have active at once? 1?</p> <p>this is Thark btw ;)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595#post-163419</guid>
				<title>Re: the trade?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade#post-163419</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Once you've made the Trade 2 (ie, the Note), you get all sorts of benefits. The biggest one is probably Note Rush (+20% AP/XP/Ryo for the day if you bingo someone). But the jutsu you can learn are great. Anon's obsessive insight is fantastic for #1 runs, and Right's jutsu is great for trying to push off looping while farming cash. LisaLisa also has a jutsu that lets you change your party without paying a stamina cost.</p> <p>In addition, bingo'ing can also help with invasions.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595#post-163393</guid>
				<title>Re: the trade?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade#post-163393</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 13:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you're not planning on bingoing anyone then the Trade has less value, but in season 2 it gains a lot of utility beyond that. Firstly, you'll probably need it to meet the three bloodlines required for the Jonin exam. You'll also need it to get access to the Monochrome reaper missions, which require you to be immune to the Note. And finally you can use it to get a theme which makes you immune to the note and at gain at least one of three powerful jutsu. In season one, though, it's mainly for bingos.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595#post-163329</guid>
				<title>the trade?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-59595/the-trade#post-163329</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2008 11:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Thark</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>97204</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>hey,</p> <p>this is prolly a pretty stupid question but,</p> <p>why would i wanna do the trade? i mean i don't really like bingoin someone cuz it pisses me off when someone does that to me :(. but anyway of what use would that be to loose 30 stam everyday (or better 20 cuz i'm season1). does the trade loop btw? (reaper doesn't but i'm not sure about trade?!). is bingoing just for the fun of pissing people off? i really don't get it yet i believe… problem is i'm about to hit the the lvl cap (well in the closer future not like tomorrow or something). and i wanna try to save some money, potions, hairpins and i don't wanna do something unnecessary and stuff to prepair myself for my sanninrun.</p> <p>so would you guys tell me to do the trade (i don't have 1 style point yet) or tell my not to?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>