<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:55:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-173635</guid>
				<title>Re: The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-173635</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 19:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It took me a few days, but I was hanging out with Bruce Jr., J-Diddy and Tic Tac all together. The friend points required for them are all around 120k, so I just did some grinding through D-ranks until I got them all to that level, then used ~20k ryo in the party house to hang out with some random character that had under 10k points (was Annie at the time, now looks like Z-Dog might be a better idea) It was totally unintentional (until the end) because I was just trying to get the sham rock mission, and realized that I would be hanging out with all three at once… and figured it would be a cinch to get one more through party bonuses.</p> <p>If someone in your village has the HoClaus, GET THE NINJA-MAS SPIRIT. With that, J-Diddy, Tic Tac (and Love Love if you have it) every single mission you run will get you 800 friends points. Doing it this way took me (I think) about 4 days.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-170380</guid>
				<title>Re: The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-170380</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 02:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://www.animecubed.com/billy/friends.shtml">http://www.animecubed.com/billy/friends.shtml</a></p> <p>On that link you can see the current friend points for everyone. Bold are currently hanging out with that ally. You need to be able to hang out with 4 of them on the same day, so you'll probably want to do J-Diddy+2 others until you hit a certain threshold, then swap to do J-Diddy+2 others and hit that threshold as well.</p> <p>Allies with very few people listed, or with friend points below 10k are the usual targets.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-170338</guid>
				<title>Re: The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-170338</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 00:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What if you want to get Nadeshiko just by any means and you don't have the theme or the item? What'd be the easiest way? The wiki entry was a little vague on alternatives. How do you determine their hang out threshold and all?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-168031</guid>
				<title>Re: The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-168031</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 02:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Incidentally, the +100 stamina from the Silver Hairpin is the day AFTER you hang out with Shorty…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-165785</guid>
				<title>Re: The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-165785</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 17:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Silver Hairpin only gives stamina if you hang out via friend points, not from mome or floating. Any allies with expensive jutsu that you'll need are good candidates for hanging out for Nadeshiko. I went with Right, Anon, Hyuk, and Shorty, and learned all their jutsu on that day.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-165579</guid>
				<title>Re: The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-165579</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 10:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Shorty Lvl. 2 is good idea for 100 stamina from Silver Hairpin and cheaper Kido: Nightfall(-30 Stamina, +3 Tai Strength, +10 Tai Range) to get Billy lvl3. And if you don't have lvl2 you need all jutsus of lvl 1 to get Bankai.</p> <p>Miss Kitty has 800k xp justsu Kido: I Can Has Cheezburger. (Ten times the chance of finding Items / Ninja)</p> <p>Mister Tea for Lucha Libre Style: Pity the Fool. (Double chance of leveling allies)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402#post-165553</guid>
				<title>The Trade Lvl 2 and Nadeshiko</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60402/the-trade-lvl-2-and-nadeshiko#post-165553</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 09:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So I finally got the floating on air and a mood enhancer and would like to hang out with Right, Annonymus, and two others to go for the Trade lvl 2 and get Nadeshiko the next day.</p> <p>Is there anything I should keep in mind? Which two other allies should I hang out with (for cheaper jutsus, for example). Did anyone ever do it this way and has some advice? Thanks!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>