<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Friend levels and Floating theme</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60265/friend-levels-and-floating-theme</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Friend levels and Floating theme&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:32:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60265#post-165172</guid>
				<title>Re: Friend levels and Floating theme</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60265/friend-levels-and-floating-theme#post-165172</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 11:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Floating on Air will remove points and you will hang out only with 3 allies.</p> <p>Make-Out Mood Enhancer is only way to have 4 allies with this theme.</p> <p>An here is mini guide to get Nadeshiko:</p> <p>It's easy with Love Love Paradise, J-Diddy, TicTac, The Ninja-Mas Spirit to hang with 4 or 5 allies.</p> <p>One mission will give you 800 points per ally.</p> <p>10 misions = 100stamina = 8k points</p> <p>8k friend points is enought to hang with for Big Bo, Big Ro, Big Shammy, Z-Dog or others low level allies from <a href="http://www.animecubed.com/billy/friends.shtml">http://www.animecubed.com/billy/friends.shtml</a></p> <p>You make team of: chosen ally with J-Diddy and TicTac.</p> <p>Make 10 or more missions.</p> <p>Make next team(30 stamina for a change for second and next change of the day. So it's good idea to day before leave for a night chosen team.) and make next 10 missions.</p> <p>500 stamina is low limit I would go with but with ramen and potions and bonuses and Hairpin Pieces its easy to get 700 for that.</p> <p>More stamina you have more friend points you can receive from missions.</p> <p>Don't forget at the end of stamina to use Ninja Art: Hottie Regeneration to get 100 stamina but with that you can not use The Ninja-Mas Spirit jutsu so you will get from the 100 stamina around 4000 points only.</p> <p>Also instead of doing it all at one day you can day before build you friend levels of chosen allies to 4000(they will not be Hanging Out at this level) and next day will end with 12 k points with 10 missions per ally.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60265#post-165160</guid>
				<title>Friend levels and Floating theme</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60265/friend-levels-and-floating-theme#post-165160</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 10:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Liliandra</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91651</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Quick question,</p> <p>If you have sufficient friend levels to hang out with X the next day, and set your team to w, Y and Z while turning on the theme, will it erase X's points before it counts for hanging out bonus? (Having trouble getting a Make-Out Mood Enhancer and on the loop countdown, hoping to grab Nadishiko before then. :/ )</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>