<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>On Ronin Missions</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;On Ronin Missions&quot; - ...how do we want to handle them?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:03:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132#post-165435</guid>
				<title>Re: On Ronin Missions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions#post-165435</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 22:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Moare</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>79546</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sounds like a fair deal to me</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132#post-165370</guid>
				<title>Re: On Ronin Missions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions#post-165370</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 18:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Arkantos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98147</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Agreed… first scout them out… also, I think the importance of trying these missions is more what you can GET from the missions… if it something minor and not really a MUST… then perhaps the village can organise things better…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132#post-165062</guid>
				<title>Re: On Ronin Missions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions#post-165062</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 03:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I probably should have mentioned that the rumor is, the difficulty level is around ordinary S1 Jonin level. So yeah, there's no point in Sp. Jonin or lower doing it. I think it was originally suggested, this is the kind of thing you'd do when you're out getting SNAKEMAN (which can only be done at Jonin anyway).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132#post-165014</guid>
				<title>Re: On Ronin Missions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions#post-165014</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 23:56:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I concur, but would like to propose the idea that, instead of a first come, first serve system, I think that a few high level Jonins and Sannins should "scout them out" so to speak, so that we know the difficulty of them and such. That way, we don't send Chunin's and Sp. Jonin's out there to get mauled by a mission with a difficulty way above their ability.</p> <p>After that, I think you should set some requirements as to how high leveled someone should be for leaving for Ronin missions (so that those who are clearly too weak don't take up a slot instead of someone who could use it).</p> <p>For those who meet the requirement, then it should be first come, first serve. I just think we should take steps to make sure that the lower leveled aren't wasting time on a mission that they can't complete, while the higher leveled are waiting to try it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132#post-164867</guid>
				<title>Re: On Ronin Missions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions#post-164867</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 18:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This is not time sensitive as was sannin run error so allowing 3-4 nins at the time to leave would be good idea.</p> <p>Four spots are not reseeded with new people till and when one of them comes back we allow next to leave for a ronin.</p> <p>It's a good idea to make this quota of 'on the ronin' seats.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132#post-164788</guid>
				<title>On Ronin Missions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-60132/on-ronin-missions#post-164788</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 15:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So, there's currently a rumor going around that the Ronin missions are going to be coming out soon. Very little is known about these, other than the fact that you can only do them when you're <em>not</em> in a Village. From what's currently been suggested, Ronin will take approximately 5 days outside of your Village, and you'll only really need to do it once (after the first time, everything significant should loop, is my understanding). I imagine all (or at least most) of you will want to do these missions at least once. However, we also don't want the Village to completely fall apart for 5 days while everyone leaves the Village to go do the Ronin missions.</p> <p>So, I was thinking…maybe we should setup a system where only 3 or 4 people at a time could be officially out for Ronin missions? That is, 3 or 4 people could leave for Ronin and we'd save a spot for them to come back. Anyone, of course, is free to leave whenever they want, but if you don't get the official okay, we wouldn't save a spot for you to return (though, if there is one, you'd be welcome to return, of course). This way, the Village could maintain it's 45+ people necessary for purchasing upgrades, and we can slowly move people through the Ronin missions so they can get the benefits. My thought was we'd have a waiting list (first come, first serve) for people to go Ronin, and we just go through the list as quickly as we can.</p> <p>However, I'm open to discussion on this, if anyone has any ideas as to how to handle this better? (Keeping in mind that we don't really know how it's all going to work out yet).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>