<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Ekisata Uzuki&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546/ekisata-uzuki</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Ekisata Uzuki&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546#post-170405</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546/ekisata-uzuki#post-170405</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 02:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Harry Dresden</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>100189</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>lol you should throw me in your story lol…..also here something that might help u out with explain the blood line im just making this up as i go along.</p> <p>One day while on his missions Uzuki meets a strange old man carrying what appeared to be a very large rock, Uzuki being kind hearted (fill that in what ever way u wish) runs over to help the old man, the old man casually says, "No my dear son you don't need to help me its just a bit farther up ahead then I'll be done." Uzuki would not take no for an answer, "No one of your wisdom (nice wya of saying age lol) should be carrying something like this, where is your son? or grandson? Should they not be helping you with all of this?" The old man sighs and sets the rock down, "Son? Grandson? Well….they both died in a raid a few years back trying to make sure I got out ok….." Uzuki curses him self for bringing it up, and the old man sees his expression. "Its ok you did not know, but……" sigh "Oh well I guess you can help if you are so willing." Uzuki reaches down and picks up the rock which amazingly seems to weigh 400 pounds, he glances at the old man with a shocked expression on his face. "No good deed goes unpunished……" And before Uzuki can do anything the rock suddenly turns liquid and seeps into Uzuki's skin. "What have you done to me?!" Uzuki shouts at the old man, "Like I said no good deed goes unpunished……this is your reward……..I grant you what so many have seeked yet so few have attained, use this power well my friend and may we one day meet again…….." The old man snaps his fingers and instantly is transformed into a man looking roughly just over 25 in a greyish used duster (jacket type thing) and black hair with a hat tilted down some. "An old friend gave me that to hold onto till I found someone who deserved it……I saw how well you treated others and the friends you made and well…..it seemed only right to give it to you….." Uzuki stares dumbfounded then comes back to his senses, "Who are you?" Uzuki ask, "I am <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/player:dresden">Dresden</a> Co-Kage of <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/village:tardis">Tardis</a> Village……Remember what I said use the power wisely for it shall bring you many new friends and help you greatly when you need someone to hang out with." Uzuki gets up off the ground and dust himself off and glances back at Dresden, "Thank you very much…that was…….strange to say the least but this new power will come in handy……Well good day my friend, may we meet again." Uzuki says to Dresden, "Yes we shall meet again some day……" a bolt of lighting strikes down from the sky and strikes Dresden then before Uzuki can glance back Dresden is gone.</p> <p>Might be useful? lol……….of course u could edit it if u wish lol…….was gunna say the only way u did not detect who I was was because your kind heart or w/e clouded your mind so u forgot to try and detect anything strange about the old man.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546#post-169739</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546/ekisata-uzuki#post-169739</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 02:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Unless something has changed, I'm the third non-banned person to have it. (two have been banned for cheating to get it, two others have it legitimately last I heard).</p> <p>I'm not actually sure how I'm going to explain it yet…I had kind of given up on ever getting it, so it was a bit of a surprise!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546#post-169320</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61546/ekisata-uzuki#post-169320</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 16:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Altered Nova</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>81815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Mysterious power?! Congrats Uzuki! How many players in the game even have that bloodline? Maybe you can fill out the paragraph about it on the bloodlines page.</p> <p>[Edit] Oh, and how are you going to explain it into your profile?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>