<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;On Duplicate Monster Drops&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:03:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-169392</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-169392</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 18:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Great post Lear.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-169389</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-169389</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 18:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's too complicated, and it encourages people to plant spys arbitrarily.</p> <p>Also, it makes it way too easy to fall very far behind. Lets say a storm riders attacks while I'm unable to attack it any more than twice, or perhaps even at all. So, lets say that 10 people each get 14 attacks at it, and I only got 4. That means that 10 people each got 10 more attacks, or 20 more points, putting me pretty far behind. If they keep attacking, I can be reasonably sure that I won't get any of the next 10 drops, which would discourage more than encourage in my opinion. Plus, new people to the village will always start in last, which would discourage them from trying since they're already in 50th place for the next monster drop. Yes, it does guarantee that everyone will eventually get one as long as they keep doing stuff, but so does the current system really. We haven't been fighting a lot of monsters for a very long time. As long as there aren't a bunch of jerks that keep trying to get items they already have, then you can pretty much guarantee you'll get a drop eventually as long as you're fighting monsters.</p> <p>The reason why? Look at it like this:</p> <p>Lets say a monster attacks this thread, and we all fight to defend the thread. The number of attacks are thus:</p> <p>naito: 9<br /> Schon: 7<br /> Gogolu: 6<br /> Ananvil: 4<br /> Uzuki: 4<br /> Jupiah: 3<br /> Lear: 3</p> <p>So, Uzuki gets the drop because he's the thread starter and Schon gets one because the random number generator likes him best.</p> <p>A few days later, the same monster attacks. And we attack as thus:</p> <p>naito: 10<br /> Gogolu: 7<br /> Ananvil: 6<br /> Jupaih: 5<br /> Lear: 4<br /> Uzuki: 3<br /> Schon: 1</p> <p>So this time, naito gets the random drop, and Uzuki gives the drop to Gogolu.</p> <p>Another attack:</p> <p>Ananvil: 14<br /> Jupiah: 12<br /> Lear: 11<br /> naito: 3<br /> Uzuki: 3<br /> Gogolu: 1<br /> Schon: 0</p> <p>Here, Jupiah gets the random drop, but Ananvil still gets one from Uzuki. At this point, there's only 1 without a drop, and I can be fairly certain to get it the next time.</p> <p>Given, this is small scale; I'm using 7 villagers, not 50, but also remember, not everyone in our village seriously attacks a monster with the intent of getting the drop, so the real pool will be less than 50.</p> <p>Also, keep in mind that, with the exception of the Sand Demon and the Nine-tailed Fox, each time we defeat a monster, 2 items are given out, so even with a pool of 50, after fighting a monster 25 times, everyone should have the drop.</p> <p>The system that's in place now does work, and it should balance out in the end. It might not seem like it now because it hasn't been very long, but give it some time, and it should.</p> <p>Also, Jupiah, I don't think he wants to put that much effort into tracking everything people do, and donating ryo for points basically means you can buy drops.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-169336</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-169336</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Altered Nova</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>81815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I hope a system like this gets implemented. I've spent so freakin' much stamina attacking monsters and never got anything to show for it, so I stopped attacking them all out and only hit each one 2-5 times now, in the vain hope I'll get lucky. I'd be far more willing to fight them if I know I'm guaranteed to actually get something for it (even if not immediately). I just wish the was retroactive, I'd probably already have a billion points. XD</p> <p>Idea: Give players points for donating items to the storehouse, and ryo and contracts to the village. Maybe 1 point per 1000 ryo value given to the village?</p> <p>Every day, the player with the most points can trade in 20 points for any monster item in the storehouse. If that player passes, the 2nd place player can buy it or pass it to 3rd, and so on. Alternatively, players can bid on it, and the one willing to spend the most points (minimum 10) gets the item.</p> <p>[Edit] Also, you can give out points as a reward for players that are especially helpful to other players in the village. If someone uses an alt to help someone get anonymous, or volunteers an alt as a target to help a villager get Right, donates a billy bucket or hamburgers for someone trying to get Emosuke Lvl. 3 or a Hollow Leg, or just plain gives good, helpful advice to a new player, etc.</p> <p>Basically, reward people for getting involved in village affairs. Encourage player participation!</p> <p>Also, you could give points to villagers that volunteer to help edit the wiki. (hint, hint, wink, wink) ;)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-169146</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-169146</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 13:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ananvil</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>83686</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I agree with Gogulu.</p> <p>Especially with the spying, certain players will have significant advantages (namely, those of us with Stealth Suits and Permanent drops that add for spying; I'm one of them, but it still seems like a strong get stronger model.)</p> <p>Also, not all of us are allowed to invade…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-168990</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-168990</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 08:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's too complicated.</p> <p>You would have to note every move of 50 nins for a village.</p> <p>With 'most attacks system = duplicate item' you have clear situations. It's easy to follow and don't change fun game into the chore of bureaucracy.</p> <p>If you want a monster drop? Attack a monster policy is sound and simple. If 20k monster attack you may as Kage rule attack obligatory. If nin has 2 similar drops he/she can trade it or sell it or even donate to village. It's their right.</p> <p>Also with attacks you are angering other villages which is not needed.</p> <p>Patrolling and collecting is mandatory so I don't see reason to award points for something you have to do anyway.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-168871</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-168871</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 04:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Schon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>88446</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I can see it now, spies in every village lol. I like the idea though.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-168822</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-168822</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 02:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Patrolling and collecting is a little harder for me to keep track of via scripts, since it doesn't show up in the chatlog. I'll see if I can figure out a way to do it though.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-168821</guid>
				<title>Re: On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-168821</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 02:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I like this idea. Perhaps also award two points for a week of patrolling or collecting.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392#post-168806</guid>
				<title>On Duplicate Monster Drops</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-61392/on-duplicate-monster-drops#post-168806</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 01:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So, I was thinking about a new system which is a little less arbitrary than our current system when dealing out duplicate monster drops. Here's what I was thinking…</p> <p>Whenever you successfully plant a spy, you get +3 points<br /> Whenever you successfully invade, you get +5 points<br /> Whenever you attack a monster, you get +2 points</p> <p>You keep your points until you get a monster drop. Whenever there's a duplicate monster drop that I can give out, whoever has the highest points currently gets first choice at it. They can pass to the next person, until eventually someone takes it. The points awarded as roughly the amount of stamina spent helping the village.</p> <p>Doing it this way would (1) reward people who help the village out the most get more monster drops, rather than the guy who just happened to get lucky on this particular summon, and (2) spread the monster drops out a little more evenly, (3) encourage people to wack at monsters even if they don't want that particular drop.</p> <p>I've got a script that can parse the combat log for these events and award points based on them. Effectively, I can parse the chatlog for the events, then delete them, then post the updated numbers to the forums so everyone knows where everyone else stands at any given time.</p> <p>Thoughts?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>