<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Distillation</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548/distillation</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Distillation&quot; - some details</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:55:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548#post-196848</guid>
				<title>Re: Distillation</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548/distillation#post-196848</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 07:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>DrunkMonkGar</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145960</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sorry, but I don't know how to make this neat and clean.</p> <p>Distillation<br /> Haus pokes around his lab. "Hey, want to help me with some stuffs?" (Why does 'stuffs' have an 's'?)</p> <p>(Requirements: Wasteland Disease, 20+ Outskirts Missions completed)<br /> Sure &gt;</p> <p>Revenge</p> <p>Haus is tinkering with something in an unused corner of his lab. "There's a lot more to this junk from the Wasteland than meets the eye. Think you can handle it?"</p> <p>Continue Special Mission</p> <p>Ninjutsu</p> <p>Blueprints</p> <p>Haus pokes around his lab, and comes up with a blueprint. "Help me figure this out, would ya?"</p> <p>Difficulty: 16 Successes: 4</p> <p>Success! "Excellent."</p> <p>Continue Mission &gt;</p> <p>Practice makes Perfect</p> <p>"There's some new things you can do with potions, buddy, but I don't want to teach some big loser. I'm going to sit here, and watch you put things together, until I'm satisfied.</p> <p>(Do ten or more successful creations in the Potions area. Don't quit this mission, or it will reset your count.)</p> <p>(Successful mixes you've completed so far: 0)</p> <p>I have completed 10 Mixed Items<br /> (If the mission has a requirement, be sure to have completed it before you click above, or you'll fail the mission!)</p> <p>SUCCESS!<br /> "Good enough. Now, check this out…"</p> <p>Continue Mission &gt;</p> <p>"Good, good. See, I've found that you can actually break things down for ingredients, even worthless things, and then those ingredients can be used for new and Awesome stuffs. I'd suggest building yourself some Wasteland gear, you are going to need it."</p> <p>You got: Basic Blueprints!</p> <p>Basic Blueprints description: A strange recipe…<br /> Permanent Item.</p> <p>I think any type of potion works for the mixing part.</p> <p>Edit: Additional distillation info: Cracked Vial distills into 3 Acid Vials. Burnt Scroll distills into 2 Blackened Dust. Crumbling Minerals distills into 3 Wasteland Dust. Tangled Metal distills into 3 Metal Scraps. Ceramic Plating distills into 1 Ceramic Tile.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548#post-196451</guid>
				<title>Re: Distillation -&gt; UPDATE</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548/distillation#post-196451</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 20:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i recall something a requirement -&gt; you have to use the potion making-function in sum 10 times</p> <p>@forumstaff: would you merge this post with my first one of this topic, please? i could'nt edit it</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548#post-196417</guid>
				<title>Distillation</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67548/distillation#post-196417</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2008 20:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>sorry i can't remember all details of this special mission, but if you solve this you get the permanent item "Basic Blueprints". additional you unlock a new function in the potion menu -&gt;</p> <p><strong>Reduction Laboratory</strong><br /> Haus motions you over to an unused area of the workshop. "Let's see what you've picked up, maybe we can distill something useful.."</p> <p>i hope this is useful</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>