<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>On Monsters</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;On Monsters&quot; - ...man they&#039;re nasty now...</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:44:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-200316</guid>
				<title>Re: On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-200316</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Genin would make 6 dmg and chunnin 12 dmg max.</p> <p>What will that do?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-200031</guid>
				<title>Re: On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-200031</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2008 12:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Arkantos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>98147</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hmmm I think Genin and Chuunin SURELY should participate… except for collecting they could attack it ones a day (or twice) because we just RAID the resources we need…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-198405</guid>
				<title>Re: On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-198405</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 09:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think it is bad idea.</p> <p>But if you think about implementing it then:</p> <p>I think that genin and chunin should not attack monsters unless they are 20k kind.</p> <p>With as little stamina as they have every bit helps.</p> <p>To make this work you would also have to summon kaiju right after killing first and kill kaiju right after it hits 0.</p> <p>Why? Because people that come to play at time when monster can not be hit(or there is no monster at this moment) should not wait for you so they do this chore in fear of kage retribution.</p> <p>Rule that is now in place(must attack big monsters) is good. We don't have to get all monsters right away. There is no time limit.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-198024</guid>
				<title>Re: On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-198024</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 00:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Swan21</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>93166</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Once a day is nothing, as naito said, sparing 10-20 stamina for one attack at least is very much doable by everyone in the village.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-197914</guid>
				<title>Re: On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-197914</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 23:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fax</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>90931</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm riding the backs of monsters for this season, so this doesn't really affect me. I'm in the middle of the specjo exam right now, though, and have to level three allies.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-197845</guid>
				<title>Re: On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-197845</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 22:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think this is a very good idea. We give enough stamina bonuses that people can spare at least 10-20 stamina to attack a Kaiju. It is also in each persons best interest to attack to get the drop and also to keep are upgrades from being destroyed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840#post-197835</guid>
				<title>On Monsters</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-67840/on-monsters#post-197835</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 22:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Does anyone object to a rule that everyone in the village has to attack at least once a day if there's currently a kaiju alive? Failure to do so could result in the loss of access to upgrades / storehouse.</p> <p>Kaiju are seriously nasty now. The Fox Demon is reported to have 30,000 health (in addition to it's regenerating and increasing in strength). I imagine the Sand Demon is the same. Expect the Storm Riders and other 20k monsters to have 30,000 at this point. I don't think we can toy around with them like we used to.</p> <p>However, I still think we need to be killing monsters regularly (including enticement monsters). We still don't have Super Robots, which are Enticement only, and their upgrade gives 20% off arena reputation items, which is huge. We really need to keep enticing until we get that upgrade, at the very least.</p> <p>However, I'm not willing to summon them if they're going to start being a real threat to our upgrades. So, the alternative to having a rule that says "You must attack once a day." is to just stop summoning monsters. I'd rather not do this, but if you guys are really uncomfortable with the "You have to attack once a day" rule, then going without summons might be the best way to go.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>