<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Bleach</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Bleach&quot; - Your Shikai?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:14:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847#post-386322</guid>
				<title>Re: Bleach</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach#post-386322</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 08:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>winston</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>fang of the dragon.</p> <p>unreleased is a regular katana, nothing special.</p> <p>shikai- a kusari-gama, released with the call to "sharpen". the chain can be controlled by my reiatsu and extends quite a bit( not sure how far, never needed more than a few yards). when holding it by the handle i can compress my reiatsu through it to the blade at very high pressure, allowing the blade to cut nearly anything. this attack is called "bite".</p> <p>bankai- released with the call "devour" the kusari-gama is largely unchanged except for gaining red and gold color to it, the major chainge is in the fact that the reiatsu emanating from my body is compressed into a suit of winged, super dense, red and gold armor. the armor isn't impenetrable, and can only hold up as long as my reiatsu holds out, but it's an incredible defense. i can use burst of compressed reiatsu to speed my movements, but that mostly only negates the drag that the armor causes, and in a pinch, i can use compressed bursts through my finger tips much like the "bite" attack. Upon the helm of the suit, there is a set of horns which increase my sensitivity to reiatsu, allowing me to somewhat anticipate the moves of my opponents( this skill is indispensable since most other bankai level fighters are quite a bit faster than me), and allows me to limit the flow of reiatsu in parts of the armor where it isn't needed.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847#post-347593</guid>
				<title>Re: Bleach</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach#post-347593</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 05:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ahiok</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>168993</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Zanpakuto's name<br /> kaze'ryu (wind dragon)</p> <p>Shikai<br /> release command: Suraisu (slice)<br /> When in shikai form my blade is slightly longer and my speed and strength is increased slightly. Another effect of my shikai is that my blade doesn't have to hit to cause damage because the wind from my swings cuts through almost anything.</p> <p>Bankai<br /> bankai name: Hoeru kazeryu (lit howl wind dragon)<br /> once again my blade lengthens and i am able to move even faster making no noise at all. my bankai allows many special attacks one of which is being able to shoot air arrows from my blade that are stronger then a normal suraisu kaze and i am able to shoot many during a swing of my sword. in my bankai's last attack kaze'ryu is formed from the wind i control as a giant sky blue dragon that is invulnerable from conventional attacks seeing as its made of wind. kazeryu is able to shoot the arrows as well as appear behind you and grab you so i can attack.</p> <p>abilities:<br /> suraisu kaze: shoots a blast of reiatsu that can cut anything and uses little reiatsu when it has a focus weapon such as my blade. When i do not have blade it is weaker and requires more reiatsu. This ability is used automatically whenever i swing my blade.<br /> kaze shihail: as the name implies i can control the wind around me and use it to push people along with slow them down to allow for openings.<br /> inazuma:by using the air control i create friction making a static charge allowing me to send lightning at my enemies.<br /> kiemasu: i can merge with the wind this technique is mainly used to avoid attacks but is also untraceable so could be used to cause confusion in my opponent.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847#post-340306</guid>
				<title>Re: Bleach</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach#post-340306</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 13:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RazyVan</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>146953</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Shikai:Awaken,Zangetsu!<br /> Sends a blast of reiatsu in a 360 degree radius which can easily kill.<br /> The blade disappears,but can be drawn directly out of the user's body with no pain or physical difficulty.</p> <p>Appearance:Long pole.At each end a balde starts.Two in total for the whole weapon.They go in a sort of Z-shaped,but more like italic Z-shaped blades.One will point upwards,te other downwards.<br /> Lightning can be produced in a field using reiatsu and/or chakra.Strengthens speed,agility,strength and sight.</p> <p>Bankai:<br /> Destroys the blade.The user is then given the ability to manipulate and create lightning,which could also be made into kinetic,sound,magnetic etc. energy form electrical energy(sort of like in Futurama,when the professor uses de-fossilisation to make a toaster into a racoon).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847#post-340091</guid>
				<title>Re: Bleach</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach#post-340091</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 04:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ninjajohn100</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>115224</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>In unreleased form it would be a regular katana. The handle would be with black thread on one side and white on the other. The cross guard would have the Yin Yang symbol printed on it. The shikai would be released with either the command "Judge from the heavens, tentousama" which would make it a english style longsword with a shield, or with "Bring damnation from below, mashin" which would turn it into a giant hammer. The bankai would give 2 katana's. One would be perfect white and the other perfect black (similar to rukia's and ichigo's).The difference is that the one of the guards would be the Yin part of the Yin Yang symbol, and the other the Yang. There ability's would be to lock the opponent in place (kinda frozen but not with ice or weight). Then i could finish them off.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847#post-236411</guid>
				<title>Re: Bleach</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach#post-236411</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 04:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Shikai Fire/Phoenix ability,leaves an unbelieveable feeling of heat, a black bladed katana, with a japanese fire symbol marked from parts of the sword. Bankai ( lightning surronds me ), revealing a grim reaper like form with black markings on my face. The blade completely red with a spark of blue, and too active enough for anyone to even see the blade. Gives a high level speed, so fast, you're already on the ground. Then turns into a HUGE blade to finish it off.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847#post-203054</guid>
				<title>Bleach</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-68847/bleach#post-203054</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Genji</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>148257</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Bleach thread started.<br /> HAPPY FACE!</p> <p>talk about episodes, moments and events in bleach you like/dislike.<br /> if you had a shikai and/or bankai what would you want/what would suit your style?</p> <p>I'll start.</p> <p>Shikai<br /> Lightning affinity, more than likely giving a speed increase. a silver bladed katana, with a oval shaped crossguard</p> <p>Bankai<br /> substantial power increase, medium speed increase. a red-hued blade that is double sided towards the top quarter of the blade. blade appearance is a Dadao<br /> (for those of you who dont know, its a 2-handed chinese greatsword. tristan wields one in the 2004 version of king arthur)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>