<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;The Land of Baw&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;The Land of Baw&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:22:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-354931</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-354931</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 03:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Izuna</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>94909</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>personally, I haven't even bothered to unlock the training sash. Still, is fun when I do beat <em>tribloods</em>.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-325370</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-325370</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 13:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You can buy as many anticoagulant as you can everyday. I know some people who use them everyday.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-325078</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-325078</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 04:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>another thing i forgot to mention you can buy a Anticoagulant during the DH in the shop to negate all powers for a match. This way there are no powers and you can still work towards your moon. that is if you run into a mono battle your first match. not sure if you can buy more than one a day or use more than one a day.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-325009</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-325009</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2008 02:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Question: Why would you waste rations on DH? And if you are trying to get your power, don't get it during DH. More often than not, tri-blooded people are always there. Like I said, fight in LH, everyone is in the same ground. Yes, you can't increase your moon but you can get your power during that time and eventually have enough power to at least win a few fights. And don't call us tribloods cheap because we accumulated those powers. We worked to get those powers. It's not like it was handed on us when we started playing. We went through 3 seasons, some 4 to get those. It is definitely not cheap.</p> <p>And yes, like Yoshirou, I will also baw with my alt simply because I don't bother playing arena with him. If you are to hurt to do land of baw, don't. It's not like Ascension is required for non-Kages.</p> <p>Well, you bawwed about it. And that's the impression I got from it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-324710</guid>
				<title>The Land of Baw</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-324710</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 20:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>4 powers? are you talking about the whiteye power as 2 powers? I myself have all 4 powers. I know that the arena is hard when you only got one power. But arena is luck for a great part so i have even loss to a no power before. The more you play in the arena the more experience you will get on what move each tri-blood, quad-blood as i guess you would call it would make. I am doing the land of baw with my alt as i am too lazy to do the arena with 2 characters. but his first season i was able to get 15 wins in the arena and 7 of those being in the dark hour. It is anyone's choice of what they want to do with their character, but i prefer to do the arena as it has some great rewards like duelist eye/aura. We may now all be as good as lafiel or vysaga but it is possible for anyone to win any match. Also no offense to Nymphonomicon but i think McMasters is awesome just because he has put so much effort into making ALL of bvs and not just the arena. He also made anime versus and the whole animecubed website. At any rate it is up to the person to what he/she wants to do. Also, FYI the Land of Baw mission is hillarious. So good luck to people working on getting their powers.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-324691</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-324691</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 19:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nymphonomicon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91001</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I did fight for it, I fought in 20 Dark Hour matches in a single day and only got 5 wins. I've wasted countless Rations only to be spat upon and told I'm not good enough. I tried for two weeks to increase my moon and I lost it every day. I'm not afraid of those power-stacking punks, I've even beaten one or two of them on a rare occasion, but I do find it ridiculously cheap of them to accumulate so many powers and then I'm expected to battle them with only my wimpy, little Training Sash… and it's not just "Tri-bloods" that are giving me grief, the majority of players I lose to have at least 4 Arena powers.</p> <p>Don't tell me to be polite when you're repeatedly stereotyping me as some shivering, little coward who's scared of the big, bad Arena Experts. I don't need lessons in decency from a hypocrite.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-324394</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-324394</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 12:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you don't like to be mocked, don't baw. It's that easy. Fight for your moon like a man. If you don't have any powers, go get one. Anyone can get 10/15 wins in a day with the right preparation. Even if you tie every match that you play, you will eventually reach your goal. Go ask people in your village to throw one for you. If you don't like to take your chances and so afraid to fight those mighty tri-bloods, play in the Light Hour. Those are four chances for you to play in arena without the fear of fighting someone who is better than you. Do this in 3 seasons and you will get your so-called permanent powers. If you still suck being tri-blood and all, then there is nothing we can do about that. Just baw and GTFO of the Arena forever.</p> <p>And it's very rude to call the game creator of the game you are currently playing like that. At least have the decency to be polite.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-324393</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-324393</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 12:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Mari Scarlet</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>140284</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>There are four light hours in a day where no powers exist, and you won't believe how many nobloods and monobloods are around in non-DH times. Heck, even in DH, half of the people I meet are monoblood.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507#post-323593</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71507/the-land-of-baw#post-323593</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 17:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nymphonomicon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91001</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd just like to state for the record that McMasters is a massive douche for mocking people that think the Arena is too hard.<br /> I don't know what reality he lives in, but the Arena is ridiculously hard, especially if you don't have any permanent powers- seeing as 8 out of every 10 people you meet there has accumulated at least all three of the Bloodline powers.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>