<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Avatar Advice</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Avatar Advice&quot; - For Uzuki!</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:44:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-240666</guid>
				<title>Re: Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-240666</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 20:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It looks alright but It doesnt look as cool as the last one mainly because this is just a face shot. It doesn't show a cool pose with some weapon, but its your choice.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-212142</guid>
				<title>Re: Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-212142</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 23:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Now for something completely new!</p> <img src="http://bvswiki.com/local--files/player:uzuki/Uzuki-S3-p6.png" alt="Uzuki-S3-p6.png" class="image" /> <p>The pose wasn't translating well on Jin, so I thought I'd give Jessie a shot.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-212119</guid>
				<title>Re: Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-212119</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 22:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm not sure if I'm making it better, but how's this:</p> <img src="http://bvswiki.com/local--files/player:uzuki/Uzuki-S3-p4.png" alt="Uzuki-S3-p4.png" class="image" /> <p>(Part of the issue is that the original image isn't cropping so well…his pose is hard to make out when it's cropped around the waist. Here's a version of the original image)</p> <img src="http://fc02.deviantart.com/fs11/i/2006/254/b/a/Xenosaga__Jin_Uzuki_by_reitschule.jpg" alt="Xenosaga__Jin_Uzuki_by_reitschule.jpg" class="image" />
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-211823</guid>
				<title>Re: Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-211823</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 15:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I like it, but I think it could be improved by altering the background a little. The cherry blossom motif is fine in my opinion, but I'm confused a little confused by the angle that's presented. I see what looks like the top of a tree. That top of the tree seems to be at a somewhat even hight with the swordsman, maybe just a little higher. The shot of the tree also seems to be fairly level (as in, not angled upward), although that may just be an illusion due to the fact that I'm only seeing a small portion of the tree. Anyway, with what I can see, it looks to me like the swordsman is falling from the tree, presumably intentionally, but if that's the case, he's not fallen very far, and he's at a somewhat odd angle for "controlled" falling. (It looks to me like he's going to fall flat on his face.) The shot of the swordsman makes me want to see this as an angled up shot, which conflicts with the shot of the tree. It seems to want to create two different angles at the same time (if that makes any sense at all).</p> <p>Anyway, I like the intention, but background just doesn't seem to match the foreground quite right. I don't mean the cherry blossoms were a bad idea. (In fact, I like that.) I just think that perhaps a different shot of a cherry blossom tree would make it look a little better.</p> <p>Although, what do I know? I'm not an art major; I'm not even very good at photoshop, and I've had my avatar as that default ninja picture since I started playing. Take my advice with caution because, quite frankly, I'm not entirely sure I know what I'm talking about.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-211804</guid>
				<title>Re: Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-211804</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 15:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Going with a new Uzuki, I just haven't decided how it's all going to work out. I wasn't expecting S2 Uzuki to meet the Flash :) (ala, Eye of the Storm).</p> <p>With respect to the background: Don't like the cherry blossom motif? Or it's just those cherry blossoms?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-211772</guid>
				<title>Re: Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-211772</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 14:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nue</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>89950</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>it's good, but i reckon it'd be better with a different background. but i can't give you any advice on what different background that would be…</p> <p>so does that mean a new backstory for this new 'Uzuki' or will this just be an older version of the season 2 one?</p> <p>by the way, as well, i (Captain) will be away for this week till about monday as some family issues have come up and i'll be isolated a little. but nevertheless, i'll be back and playing again.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348#post-211408</guid>
				<title>Avatar Advice</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-71348/avatar-advice#post-211408</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 02:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's S3, and I want to keep my tradition of changing my avatar every season. What do you guys think of:</p> <img src="http://bvswiki.com/local--files/player:uzuki/Uzuki-S3-p1.png" alt="Uzuki-S3-p1.png" class="image" /> <p>(I'm not the original artist here, so you don't have to spare my feelings. All I did was take the original picture, crop it, put it on a backdrop of cherry blossoms, and then scaled it to the proper size. I'm not really wedded to this, I'm just testing the waters.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>