<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Revenge</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700/revenge</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Revenge&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:48:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700#post-216811</guid>
				<title>Re: Revenge</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700/revenge#post-216811</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 07:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lokumun</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112075</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes, Ryn, it's basically all up to luck S1. :) If you can get all the S1 range items like everyone else has said, then it won't be too hard. Otherwise just get to the mission and use Welcome to Goodburger. It's a low chance, but there's not much else you can do. That's how I got it :) (first try too, with only a 14-some% chance of getting it. I luff you, RNG :P)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700#post-215399</guid>
				<title>Re: Revenge</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700/revenge#post-215399</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 07:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><span style="text-decoration: line-through;">If you're a Special Jonin (Genjutsu) or a Jonin, you only need to get +1 Range from an item. Then, just get 500 Chakra, a Tasty Burger, and you can use Lil Bo's Jutsu 'Welcome to Good Burger.' You'll just barely hit the range, and will need to get very lucky to get enough successes, but you can do it.</span></p> <p>I'd say 'ninja'd', but I was beaten to it a while ago…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700#post-215302</guid>
				<title>Re: Revenge</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700/revenge#post-215302</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 04:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you're season 2+, then doing Monochrome first might be a good idea. The Monochrome items would be a huge help to this.</p> <p>Hall Pass- +1 gen range<br /> Awesome Pants- +1 range<br /> Dark Band- +1 range</p> <p>Combine those three with Jonin, and you already have 15 gen range.</p> <p>Combine that with your sword jutsu, and Letter of Marque/NWW item that gives +1 gen success. That'll give you 3 of the 4 successes you need.</p> <p>Getting one success, even without strength shouldn't be too hard. If you have 15 levels, then that'd give you nearly a 2/3 chance of passing it.</p> <p>If you're not season 2+, and you're still having trouble, spend some time in the arena. If you can average 500 points/day, then you should be able to buy the Duelist's Aura in 10 days.</p> <hr /> <p>I'll be honest, if you're having trouble passing Revenge, then you're going to have a hell of a time on the actual outskirts missions. They start off easy enough, but before long, you're going up against 18d14s and 17d15s and such. The wasteland allies help, but the missions are still moderately difficult for me, and I have a range of 22 in gen, 20 in nin, and 19 in tai sans team/jutsu.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700#post-215206</guid>
				<title>Re: Revenge</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700/revenge#post-215206</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 00:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Cyanide</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>119460</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>To my knowledge there is no way to nullify the chakra cost - if you have a Plug Suit and the Letter of Marque/Ring of Wisdom it is possible to combine with your sword jutsu and provide the four successes required, however the most common method of passing it is to get your range up to 13 - base 12 at jonin or sp. jonin (gen) and a gen range item: K-Dog's Headband, Counterfeit Permit, Chakra Armor, Letter of Marque, etc - and use the Welcome to Good Burger jutsu for the remaining range. Then it is up to luck ^_^ The other way is to simply make the range with a combination of items, use your sword jutsu and hope for the best.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700#post-215197</guid>
				<title>Revenge</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-72700/revenge#post-215197</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 23:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Chidon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>86059</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm trying to get Wasteland Disease but everytime I try, I can't get pass the 15d4s part of it. If I used a Wateland Rebreather would it nullify the 10x charkra cost for jutsu? Is there any other way to pass it?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>