<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>soul candy mission</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-73924/soul-candy-mission</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;soul candy mission&quot; - what failed msg</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:48:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-73924#post-218886</guid>
				<title>soul candy mission</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-73924/soul-candy-mission#post-218886</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 04:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hijinks Ensue<br /> Robogirl and TicTac have a SNEAKY PLAN!</p> <p>Crazy Plan!<br /> Robogirl and TicTac have an awesome idea, and are already dressed for it. "Let's sneak in on the Soul Reapers and play a prank!"</p> <p>Genjutsu<br /> Sneak In<br /> Robogirl and TicTac sneak into a bathhouse, and look back at you - "Follow us!"<br /> .<br /> Difficulty: 10 Successes: 3</p> <p>(WARNING: Only Reaper and Innate abilities may be used here!)</p> <p>Succeed!<br /> "You shimmy through a steam vent and get inside!"<br /> Ninjutsu</p> <p>THERE IS NO FAIL STATEMENT. THEN DONT HAVE TO USE ANY JUTSU HERE.</p> <p>Disguise Yourself<br /> Robogirl and TicTac are now disguised as soap and a towel - "C'mon, hurry up!"<br /> .<br /> Difficulty: 10 Successes: 3</p> <p>(WARNING: Only Reaper and Innate abilities may be used here!)</p> <p>Succeed!<br /> "You pretend to be a bottle of shampoo - and it works!"</p> <p>THERE IS NO FAIL STATEMENT. THEN DONT HAVE TO USE ANY JUTSU HERE.</p> <p>Taijutsu<br /> Pranktime<br /> Here we go - the two of them have dressed as a giant cardboard robot, and are going to bust into the bathhouse and take 'robopictures'. (whatever, just wind them up already.)<br /> .<br /> Difficulty: 11 Successes: 2</p> <p>(WARNING: Only Reaper and Innate abilities may be used here!)</p> <p>Succeed!<br /> "You wind them up, and send them on their crazy way." &lt;=== better use kido: iron maiden jutsu</p> <p>Fail.<br /> "You can't quite get the winder working, and the cardboard melts from the steam. Way to go. Back you go"</p> <p>Taijutsu<br /> GTFO<br /> They come busting out of the bathhouse. "RUN RUN RUN!" they say! Then, everyone ELSE comes out of the bathhouse, and looks at YOU!<br /> .<br /> Difficulty: 6 Successes: 9</p> <p>(WARNING: Only Reaper and Innate abilities may be used here!)</p> <p>Succeed!<br /> "You get the crap out of there before they set you on fire!"</p> <p>THERE IS NO FAIL STATEMENT. THEN DONT HAVE TO USE ANY JUTSU HERE.</p> <p>SUCCESS MESSAGE</p> <p>ALTERNATE - 1 :<br /> Robogirl gives you the thumbs up, and begins putting the pictures on the internet. TicTac, however, gives you a stinkeye. "I don't know if I like you enough to let you in on our scheme.."</p> <p>Current TicTac friend level: &gt;100!</p> <p>He gives you the once-over, and smiles. "You are alright, kid. Here, take this!" He throws you a piece of Soul Candy. "This'll take care of your body while you are doing missions, so they won't be as stressful on you."</p> <p>You may now do Reaper Missions without losing additional stamina!</p> <p>ANOTHER MESSAGE APPEARS. DAMN…<br /> ALTERNATE - 2 :</p> <p>Robogirl gives you the thumbs up, and begins putting the pictures on the internet. TicTac, however, gives you a stinkeye. "I don't know if I like you enough to let you in on our scheme.."</p> <p>Current TicTac friend level: 0.. &lt;=== THIS IS UR FAILED THIS MISSION ( gone with tictac only for 2 success reaper mission )</p> <p>He sniffs. "Eh, you are a loser. Never mind."</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>