<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Emo Teaparty</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-73528/emo-teaparty</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Emo Teaparty&quot; - A cute little suggestion...</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:48:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-73528#post-217503</guid>
				<title>Emo Teaparty</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-73528/emo-teaparty#post-217503</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 05:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>AneiDoru</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>140007</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://z3.invisionfree.com/Random_Village/index.php?showtopic=1573&amp;st=0#entry2425462">http://z3.invisionfree.com/Random_Village/index.php?showtopic=1573&amp;st=0#entry2425462</a><br /> It would be nice for you to <strong>vote before replying, and reply</strong>, so I can see if this idea sucks or not.</p> <p>It all starts with Emosuke having a 4th drop (I know, kinda uncouth, but just bear with me here)<br /> <em>Emosuke bumps into something and drops a cookie from his emo bookbag!</em><br /> You got Emo Cookie!<br /> "Such a sad…Sad pastry…"</p> <p>One emo drops 3 emo cookies you unlock the special mission 'emo teaparty'<br /> (you need 6 emo cookies and an easy to get potion base to complete it)</p> <p>Emo Teaparty<br /> "Emosuke looks lonely, why not join him?"<br /> Join in&gt;</p> <p>Emosuke sets up a little table cloaked in black with all sorts of black utensils (the forks look dangerous o_o.) "I sure could use something to use these teacups with." Emosuke mumbles<br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Hand him a Potion Base</span></p> <p>He snatches the drink from your hand and pours it into the very emo looking glasses. "Oh darn, i allmost forgot the snacks." He pondered.<br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Give him 6 Emo Cookies</span></p> <p>His emo eyes light up as he snatched up the cookies from your hands.<br /> <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Continue</span></p> <p>Tai 10d 8s "Tough It Out!"<br /> Tough out a depressing and scary teaparty…<br /> Success! "You even finish your plate!"<br /> FAIL "You hurt yourself on everything and run out of the room crying!"</p> <p>Emosuke looked very contended as he cleaned up everything from the (sad two person) teaparty. He smiled and picked up something from his cluttered bed "I think you are finally understanding what being emo is all about" he smiles and hands you a poorly decorated beanie.</p> <p>You got Emo Beanie! "Not very fashionable…" +2 Tai Strength</p> <p>You can now learn Way of the Emo (+5 tai success, +2 strength, 50000 JXP, 125c) in the 'Learn a Jutsu' menu!</p> <p>This is one of the few ideas that I have actually shared, though all replies are welcome it'd be nice if "YOU SUCK!!!" wasn't the answer, if you are going to say HELL NO a less admirable reply would be "this will NEVER happen", or at least tell me why first. &gt;_&gt;</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>