<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Impartial survey</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Impartial survey&quot; - Please give feedback</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:48:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220824</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220824</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 14:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>one thing that amuses me is that everyone instantly assumes every suggestion is a bad suggestion.</p> </blockquote> <p>If 95% of everything is crap, and I haven't found an exception yet, then it's a fair assumption that 95% of suggestions are crap.</p> <blockquote> <p>one thing i suggested was to make it a rule against theiving from a village and put in this safeguard "Make an option that allows a leader to REPORT a theft of items, and a mod look through the facts and make a judgement based on village logs".</p> </blockquote> <p>Do you know how many 'Someonz stoled my stuffs' messages McMasters gets in a day, on the average? Neither do I, but if it's more than one, then that's too many for your suggestion to be feasible. It's a question of resources. McMasters could say, "Okay, EvilTaxi, I can have you look at the extensive backlog of theft reports or I could put you to work on meaningful stuff like rebalancing the NWW, or ending Ren Po Ken or something." , but we both know what would get picked.</p> <blockquote> <p>His reply to that suggestion "Its the leaders fault for allowing a member the right to take items".</p> </blockquote> <p>He's right. Who's fault was it that Naruto stole the sealed scroll? Mizuki. Who's fault was it that an Academy Student washout like Naruto was <em>able</em> to steal the scroll? Sarutobi.</p> <blockquote> <p>Taking items for starters is the basis for the storehouse. Even allowing just 3 items a day they could take the best and leave. My suggestion was simply to make it possible for someone to report the theft and for it to be recified. is that a good or bad suggestion. Theiving from honest people is not a way to play a game, its a way to be an ass.</p> </blockquote> <p>Unless you regularly keep a stock of three or more Golden Potions in your village's storehouse, the theft was not worth complaining about. If you Kage restricts access to perms to a few trusted villagers and keeps the # of items a day low then he's doing his job to regulate theft to an acceptable level. By complaining about something so minor, you are venturing deep into the land of diminishing returns.</p> <p>The only exception I can think of is if permissions either got hacked or bugged and then the person stole a bunch of stuff. Then you would have a legitimate complaint and McMasters would do something about it. He's done it before when hackers deleted villages, I'm sure he would do something suitably potent in that case.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220352</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220352</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 20:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Jadian has mostly covered everything, but I've got a few things to say as well.</p> <blockquote> <p>yes thats right, a proxy. asnyone who legitimatly wanted to cheat the system would use one. so putting these stupid things in place would change nothing.</p> </blockquote> <p>First off, if it's so easy to use a proxy to trick the system, why haven't you used one? I could list half a dozen sites that'll let you use a proxy for free, and I'm sure you'd find a lot more if you just typed "proxy" into google. It sounds like you have solved your own problem, but refuse to use it and instead expect McMasters to bend over backwards to impliment all these suggestions you've been offering.</p> <p>Second, it's not impossible to identify who's behind a proxy anyway. The IP address may show a different computer, but it's not outrageously difficult to find the computer behind it. Also, I wouldn't be surprised if McM had a list of proxy IPs somewhere. Certainly not all, but at least commonly used ones. If someone was doing some obvious cheating using a proxy it would be caught (and it has, in the past. If I'm not mistaken, some players tried to proxy cheat themselves to Mysterious Power bloodline and got busted.)</p> <blockquote> <p>just have an item record in his poxy little database the ip's which it was held in and make it impossible to be taken by another ip thats the same.</p> </blockquote> <p>Imagine the following scenario:</p> <p>I have two Stealth Suits, and I want to trade one to Jadian for his spare Codec. We make the trade, now Jadian's Stealth Suit is marked with my IP and my Codec with his.</p> <p>I run out of ryo and am forced to sell my Stealth Suit in order to pay for something I really want.</p> <p>Later, I acquire a second K-Dog's Headband, and Jadian acquires another Stealth Suit. We agree to trade again.</p> <p>I drop my K-Dog's headband in the storehouse and he takes it, at the same time, dropping his Stealth Suit in.</p> <p>I try to take the Stealth Suit and BAM! "You cannot take this item because your IP has already owned it!"</p> <p>WTF? It was a legitimate trade. I didn't do anything unusual or suspcious or unfair; I just tried to make a trade.</p> <p>It could become even more annoying if, after 5 or so trades, Jadian's Codec ends up in the hands of his alt, entirely by coincidence… well almost ends up in his alt's hands.</p> <p>Lesson: Just because it worked in one game doesn't mean it will work in another.</p> <p>—-</p> <p>What I don't think you realize is that McMasters doesn't have to prove that you're the same person because you're right; same IP doesn't mean same person, but it is highly suspicious. It's not unreasonable for him to assume it's the same person and treat the two characters as if they had the same owner. In the internet world, there is no such thing as "Innocent until proven guilty." If you do something to raise suspicion of cheating, you'll be watched. If McM doesn't like what he sees, you'll be banned. Simple as that. It's not unfair and it's not unreasonable. In fact, it's necessary to make things fair. It's your responsibility to make sure that there's no reason he'd suspect you of cheating. He's told you what not to do, and you insist on doing it anyway, and you're going to suffer for it. Sorry.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220272</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220272</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 19:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><em>I'd like to apologize in advance for the discourteous tone throughout most of my message.</em></p> <p>Your ego is showing.</p> <p>By thinking so highly of yourself and so lowly of McMasters, you're telling me that, in essence, you think you could run this game better than the person currently in charge. Not every suggestion is a bad suggestion, but with how I've heard that they still get a lot of bug reports and suggestions practically saying "LOL stamina plz" I can see them considering good suggestions as a minority.</p> <blockquote> <p>Theiving from honest people is not a way to play a game, its a way to be an ass.</p> </blockquote> <p>Find a rule on the BvS site that says that it is not allowed. Hence mods don't deal with deadbeating, and furthermore players take dealing with deadbeats into their own hands—as a community effort. If you can find that rule in there somewhere, then bring it up to McMasters, and you'll get something changed for sure.</p> <blockquote> <p>the ip wont be changed because there is nothing i can do about it barring using a proxy.</p> </blockquote> <p>Nothing will change if you don't try. I see you've ignored where I suggested asking your ISP for suggestions regarding that aspect, not even saying as much as "I don't want to try that" or "I've already tried that and Customer Service was no help."</p> <blockquote> <p>If you want a suggestion just have an item record in his poxy little database the ip's which it was held in and make it impossible to be taken by another ip thats the same. trust me, i have seen that system work.</p> </blockquote> <blockquote> <p>really finding nifty little ideas like that is my speciality and dont say i dont understand how the game works.</p> </blockquote> <p>I'll be responding to both these points at the same time, starting by shaking my head in distaste.</p> <p>It's easy to understand the fundamentals on which the game is based, they aren't difficult in the least. If you want to say you understand how the game works, then try telling us how the databases are stored. You might be able to guess, but I wouldn't expect 100% accuracy from you, in all honesty. After all, I can see your suggestion right there telling me that you don't. I'll excuse it by saying that you were getting caught up in the heat of the argument, but I think only perm items could have that applied to them, even then it'd require going through a lot of trouble to implement, and lastly it wouldn't stop people from abusing multiple characters.</p> <blockquote> <p>For kaiju, how about reducing the damage done by a %age, such as one alt in village 50% damage reduction, 2 alts 33%. and such.</p> </blockquote> <p>Look at your suggestion here again too. How is it determined how Kaiju drops get awarded again? Tickets that characters get for attacking, not how much damage they do? Whether you planned on reduced damage or tickets for allowing people on the same IP to attack the kaiju, it'd still be broken: one way would give more tickets for the same amount of damage, while the other would lessen the number of tickets that would have been distributed to other people in the village, and thus still raises the person's chance of getting the drop unfairly. Both would have to be implemented at the same time, in addition to modifications to the way several items work, just to avoid Lear's suggestion of alternating Kaiju.</p> <blockquote> <p>so im just gonna quit.</p> </blockquote> <p>Well, if that's how you really feel, and not just you getting caught up in the heat of the moment, then I'm sorry. I'm sure your village will miss you ( and your girlfriend if she decides to leave with you ), and hope that the two of you continue to have good times together. I would just like to ask that you let your village know if that's really going to be the case.</p> <p>Edit: Fixed some spelling, and feel like an idiot for having to.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220214</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220214</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 18:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>one thing that amuses me is that everyone instantly assumes every suggestion is a bad suggestion.<br /> one thing i suggested was to make it a rule against theiving from a village and put in this safeguard "Make an option that allows a leader to REPORT a theft of items, and a mod look through the facts and make a judgement based on village logs".<br /> His reply to that suggestion "Its the leaders fault for allowing a member the right to take items".<br /> Taking items for starters is the basis for the storehouse. Even allowing just 3 items a day they could take the best and leave. My suggestion was simply to make it possible for someone to report the theft and for it to be recified. is that a good or bad suggestion.<br /> Theiving from honest people is not a way to play a game, its a way to be an ass.</p> <p>Being in the same village is what we enjoyed about the game. we put up with his anti-cheating laws until now but hes going too far. whats next? the party house? the storehouse?. its just going to continue until there is nothing left to do. so im just gonna quit. the ip wont be changed because there is nothing i can do about it barring using a proxy.</p> <p>yes thats right, a proxy. asnyone who legitimatly wanted to cheat the system would use one. so putting these stupid things in place would change nothing.</p> <p>If you want a suggestion just have an item record in his poxy little database the ip's which it was held in and make it impossible to be taken by another ip thats the same. trust me, i have seen that system work.<br /> as for partoling and crap make them half as effective. simple no? to get the benifit of ONE person all parts would need to patrol.<br /> For kaiju, how about reducing the damage done by a %age, such as one alt in village 50% damage reduction, 2 alts 33%. and such.</p> <p>really finding nifty little ideas like that is my speciality and dont say i dont understand how the game works. I got distinctions this year in computers systems, web development and software programming. it runs off a databases using languages such as java and such. not really too complicated at all.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220189</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220189</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 17:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Several hundred suggestions are only going to annoy him, not make him change everything. I'd suggest you stop that. And considering that you really don't know much about the system that the game runs on (no one does but McM), they're probably mostly wrong.</p> <p>And he does have something to track theives, but it's very hard to determine whether there are actually two distinct players, or 1 player playing two characters. If you ever dumped something in the storehouse and your girlfriend's character picked it up, how would he be able to know that was two players and not merely one player switching an item between his alts? It's too difficult, and so to avoid that, he's discouraged people from playing in the same village as someone with their same IP.</p> <p>He's not trying to make the game MORE fair, not less. If he allowed players to have characters of the same IP in the same village with no penalty whatsoever, cheating would be rampant. He'd be able to catch flagrant cheating, like using one character as an obvious mule/farmer, but there would be a ton of subtle things that would go unnoticed. The system can't catch everything, and he can't monitor everyone's activities 24/7. The few who cheat would have a huge advantage on players like me, who've played entirely according to the rules.</p> <p>He's limiting people's freedom slightly so that everyone has a fair chance at the game. It's not that he's being entirely unflexable; you're just not seeing how flexible he is. He could very well say, "One character per IP, and that's final," but he doesn't. Quite frankly, running the game would probably be a lot easier if he did that. He wouldn't have to code all these safeguards to make sure no one creates a mule character or that there's too much collaboration between alts, but he did. He wants to allow people the most freedom they can have in the game, but there are inevitably some rules that he has to put in place, else anarchy would rule.</p> <p>Also, the rule that duplicate IPs should be in different villages helps protect you. If you're in the same village, you could get caught for cheating that's not really cheating. He doesn't want to accidentally ban people who are just trying to play the game fairly, and so he's told you what you should do to protect yourself.</p> <p>He has given you plenty of room as far as duplicate IPs go. If you're in different villages, then there'll be no problem. If you choose to be in the same village, then you're going to have to deal with all the anti-cheating rules he's put in place. That's just the way it is.</p> <p>And remember, all (or at least most) of these rules are because someone has abused something in the past. He's merely making sure that it doesn't happen again. Writing a code to stop ALL cheating, while at the same time NEVER catching someone who isn't cheating AND allowing duplicate IPs in the same village would be infinitely meticulous and probably just not possible. Also, considering that he's still adding content to the game, I don't think he wants to spend several hours working on some issue that he's already solved.</p> <p>So, you really have three options:</p> <p>1.) One of you move to a new village. Slightly inconvenient, but not a horrible sacrifice.</p> <p>2.) One of you start playing from a different IP. It's really not too hard. Ren Po Ken offered several solutions to that problem.</p> <p>3.) Deal with the restrictions. Alternate monster attacks. You attack one monster, then she attacks the next monster, and so on. Alternate ingredient collection days and buy a trial mix every other day to make up for it. Stay out of the storehouse and don't trade items between each other.</p> <p>Edit: Ninja'd, not once, but twice.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220170</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220170</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>I have 3 different compuetrs with 3 different mac addresses but they are connected to the net though a wireless LAN router. yes i know computers better than most people.</p> </blockquote> <p>I'd be more surprised if they had the same mac address, since I'm pretty sure that's ROM on the NIC after all…but then again, that's why I was thinking you could call your ISP to try and find out what you could do for that. They would know how to help you there better than I do.</p> <p>I'd also like to note that not all suggestions are good ones, even if you happen to think they are. After all, McMasters is the one doing the coding for this, and he knows how he wants various aspects of the game to turn out. People hate deadbeats, but he hasn't put in a countermeasure to that with a simple and honest reason: It isn't against the rules, and it's a way to play the game. Because of this, while there are still thieves from time to time, they tend to not be allowed in major villages due to the stuff they pull…and people who might be legitly pulling a number of items out are also able to without worrying about an anti-thieving mechanism.</p> <p>Another reason he's against multiple IPs is so that you can't use the actions of one character to just support another character or a village ( yours or someone else's, doesn't matter ). Some people still don't get the lesson though, and you'll occasionally run into some asking you to let his friends into the village while the 3-4 of them ( 2-3 applying and the one already in ) all are recognized by the system as having the same IP. Might just be that they all played from one computer one day, but if that was the case, they need to be told to try avoiding that from then on.</p> <p>I'll agree that you won't meet him halfway, for one statement of yours:</p> <blockquote> <p>he has been battling the wrong things to enhance the game</p> </blockquote> <p>Remember: if all else fails, you could just have your ninja in different villages….after all, it's not like you need to be in the same village to make getting in touch with each other easier. Please try to keep things like these in mind.</p> <p>@Ren Po Ken-It seems same to say that he means "In the same village" at this point.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220167</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220167</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 17:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually, there's a place called Random Forums where he posts regularly. He is a very reasonable person. However, I don't see a way to prevent people having multiple characters and using them to mule or easily boost village pop without disallowing people with multiple IPs in one village to contribute much. If you see a viable alternative then please inform, but I don't.</p> <p>AS far as you not liking the things he has added(which I don't see how you can't, but meh), then it's your prerogative to leave.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220142</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220142</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>ok i understand now the terri thing but that doesnt change my stance on the duplicate IP.</p> <p>we DO use different computers the problem wherein lies within the network IP. I have 3 different compuetrs with 3 different mac addresses but they are connected to the net though a wireless LAN router. yes i know computers better than most people.</p> <p>you say i havent tried to meet him halfway but have you even talked to him at all? i must have sent several hundred suggestions by now pointing out things that could be done to enhance the system the game runs on. such as implimenting something to track theives in villages and what not. my point is, he has been battling the wrong things to enhance the game and i'm thinking of quitting it because of it.<br /> before you say anything, i know im not overracting on this issue, if he sees breaking alts away as a core fundamental issue i will leave, simple as. i do not find enjoyment playing a game which will ruin my ability to play with friends.</p> <p>as far as meeting him halfway, i have tried. he is like an oak tree, he doesnt gtive way until he breaks apart. and at which point its too late.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220074</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220074</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 15:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>With the recent release of terri lvl3's ability to hoarde monster drops and the recent same ip's cant attack the same kaiju anymore do you feel that these changes are fair?</p> </blockquote> <p>Wait what? This is new to me! Are you saying that if I have two characters, in two different villages, and they both get attacked by Magical Girls or Evil Taxi or whatnot, I can only attack one? Seeing as that actually happened less than a week ago, I'd say that's a very recent change.</p> <p>Or do you mean that two characters in the same village from the same IP can't attack the kaiju? The last one just makes sense, as McMasters has a long record of encouraging each villagers in a village to have a unique IP.</p> <p>This isn't heckling (that comes later), I'm genuinely curious which you meant.</p> <blockquote> <p>How it could be seen as fair<br /> I can see some reasoning behind this, to stop the same person making alts to help kill a kaiju and hoarde drops for them and their "Many" alts of three max. And rewarding of high level people for an almost garanteed item drop.</p> </blockquote> <blockquote> <p>How it could be seen as unfair<br /> Same IP doesnt mean its the same person. I preseonally play the game with my girlfriend and we are in the same village. it was bad enough not being able to collect ingrediants on the same day but this has actually made the game less pleasing to play. We like to do things together and be in the same village. So the fact we cant; patrol/collect, ingrediant hunt, fight kaiju or vote on topweb games at the same time really is bad for us. The terri lvl3 thing i personally see as a completle load. It is unfair to lower leveled people and new people to the game. I found it fair that the people who put a lot of effort into taking the kaiju down were rewarded with a greater chance of getting the item, but image this, a high level person comes to the village knowing he is likly to be the only person with terri lvl3… see wherre thats going. He takes all the odds away and gets the item.</p> <p>So im making this survey as i want to know what YOU think. Please leave feedback on this and state your mind.</p> </blockquote> <p>Okay, so you're really dealing with two separate, but related issues. The first one is duplicate IP nerfing and the other is Terri 3's Counting Coup ability. The first is done to prevent muleing, where Char1 ingredient hunts and dumps them in the storehouse for Char2. How McMasters is handling it is not ideal, but it is better than anything else I've heard suggested. That horse is dead, please stop beating it. This is one of McMaster's core design philosophies, and you're not going to change his mind on it.</p> <p>On the other hand, it doesn't sound like you or your girl friend are even trying to meet him half way. There are dozens if not hundreds of ways for you to get around this problem. Go to your cyber cafe/local library/college or high school campus/place of employment/free wireless hotspot/friend's house and do BvS there. My library has a strict no games policy when using their internet terminals. It's so strict, that I've never seen it enforced. I live in a place that aspires one day to qualify as 'The Boonies' and this is still an option for me, so I know it is for you.</p> <p>Now for Terri 3. I think you have a fundamental misconception of how her ability works. Essentially, there are now 3 potential drops from kaiju (except for Spirit of the Sand/Nine Tailed Fox. Not sure it it's one or two for them now), the normal one, the Kage one, and the counting coup one. A high level player coming in and kicking EvilTaxi once in the tires and getting the counting coup drop in no way affects the likelihood of another player getting the normal drop. If anything, it enhances it since that powerful player is only likely to attack once. Is it fair to lower leveled players? Yes. That person with Terri 3 paid his dues (also known as Season 1) and leveled her. Every MMORPG works on a seniority system, except if you work hard, you may eventually surpass someone who's played the game longer. If you still think that's not fair, then you must also think that themes, loopable items, and season 2+ exclusive content are also unfair.</p> <p>Now I'm going to tell you something. I know you've heard it before, but I'm going to tell you again because it's important. The Kaiju Drop is irrelevant. You fight Kaiju because <em>it's your job</em>. You are ninja. You're getting some nice stamina bonuses, the Ingredient Hunt Special Mission is available to you, and let's not forget about The Party House, all thanks to your village. It's sweet, but it ain't free.</p> <p>When a Kaiju attacks you are the first and only line of defense. It's your job. I've personally sunk 63 hits and probably close to 200&nbsp;000 Ryo worth of stuff on a single kaiju with no chance of getting the drop. Part of being a ninja is protecting your village from the rampages of prepubescent girls armed with magic wands on a sugar high. It's all part of the cost of keeping your party house intact.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220071</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220071</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 15:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jediwaldo</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>104443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Terri lvl. 3 is a god send to a lot of people with horrible luck with the RNGgod. He has smoted me many times with kaiju drops. I don't like the whole 2 accounts from the same ip and and 2 different is kind unfair. But seriously it is in place to stop people from having 3 alts in one village and getting all three of them to get the like 23-28 attacks worth of tickets and pretty guaranteeing them the drop. What should be done? Well that is a hard one. Technically McMasters should prolly change the rule on a situational basis. If my lover would play the game and we both wanted to be in the same village and cant that would be really hard to pull off. But as I remember from Travian you set up on your preferences to say who the "1" player who might be known to play off your same ip either all the time or some of the time.</p> <p>So yeah. Terri 3 drops basically are allowing those who have like no luck at getting Kaiju drops to finally get that drop they really badly want. And eventually there will be enough people with Terri 3 to make it a contest. Currently, its just a few people and that is ever expanding. I like because it a great way to get the elusive 1 monster drop that you need to complete the Monochrome mission line.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-220070</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-220070</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 15:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It isn't a major change, only an addition. The old system is still there, however, now there is an extra monster drop in the mix. It is actually MORE fair to new players since older players who have perm items to help monster mashing will probably get the drop due to Terry 3 damage rather then number of attacks.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-219954</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-219954</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 12:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Please explain "It is unfair to lower leveled people and new people to the game" for me, if you still think so after reading my post.</p> <p>Terri 3 doesn't not affect the normal system of monster drops in ANY way. At the end of the list of ninja who attacked the Kaiju, it will say that So-and-So Ninja recieved a trophy item for doing XXXX damage to the kaiju, because Terri3 keeps track of the damage the ninja dealt of Terri in their party and awards a drop to the ninja who did the most damage in that way…that someone who was Season 3+ to begin with used Terri to get an extra drop out of the kaiju over what it normally gives shouldn't bother you so much.</p> <p>I mean, seriously now, how bothered were you when Tsukiball came out? That was Season 3+ people only as well. Perhaps this is part of the reason that it wasn't annouced, but just implemented, to begin with: people who've been playing longer get more content and bonuses, and people who haven't get annoyed by it ( admittedly, I didn't notice that it wasn't mentioned in the news, though the page for Terri3 got added a little over half a month ago ). Any further and I'd just be ranting, so I'll stop here.</p> <p>I can't really say much about the IP issue, though you and your girlfriend could try using seperate computers and seeing if the two of you could have seperate IP addresses on the WAN side, if that'd be feasible. On the other hand, I'm not sure if that might be difficult to get done…never tried finding out about something like that.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-219940</guid>
				<title>Re: Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-219940</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Additional</p> <p>i quote mcmasters on this "Now, if you are are the only one that has Terri 3, you just kick the tires of a kaiju, and bam, free shiny."</p> <p>Is that fair? And is it fair not not give warning of a MAJOR change?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267#post-219939</guid>
				<title>Impartial survey</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74267/impartial-survey#post-219939</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 11:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>With the recent release of terri lvl3's ability to hoarde monster drops and the recent same ip's cant attack the same kaiju anymore do you feel that these changes are fair?</p> <p>How it could be seen as fair<br /> I can see some reasoning behind this, to stop the same person making alts to help kill a kaiju and hoarde drops for them and their "Many" alts of three max. And rewarding of high level people for an almost garanteed item drop.</p> <p>How it could be seen as unfair<br /> Same IP doesnt mean its the same person. I preseonally play the game with my girlfriend and we are in the same village. it was bad enough not being able to collect ingrediants on the same day but this has actually made the game less pleasing to play. We like to do things together and be in the same village. So the fact we cant; patrol/collect, ingrediant hunt, fight kaiju or vote on topweb games at the same time really is bad for us. The terri lvl3 thing i personally see as a completle load. It is unfair to lower leveled people and new people to the game. I found it fair that the people who put a lot of effort into taking the kaiju down were rewarded with a greater chance of getting the item, but image this, a high level person comes to the village knowing he is likly to be the only person with terri lvl3… see wherre thats going. He takes all the odds away and gets the item.</p> <p>So im making this survey as i want to know what YOU think. Please leave feedback on this and state your mind.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>