<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Some Questions</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Some Questions&quot; - Questions about B rank and higher missions</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:54:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-259252</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-259252</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 10:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thanks, I am somewhat sure I have the right allies and their respective levels for either of these teams. I have the allies at the required levels for either Never Say Yaoi and Crazy Love Triangle. I am using CLT atm, get back 2 stamina per mission - 1 from Stalkergirl and 1 from Pinky, which helps out a bit when doing my daily runs. Not that I have the necessary potions and items needed to do my Sannin mission, not that I am worried about getting to Sannin in Season 1.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-257545</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-257545</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2008 21:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Or a solid team is never say yaoi or however you spell it. That team got me through A ranks at season 1.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-256264</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-256264</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2008 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>ok thanks, will work on getting Crazy Love Triangle team together and do some gen reaper missions with stripeypants</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-255584</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-255584</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 13:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd rather use Crazy Love Triangle, you're really not in the best shape for range. There are also some very useful items in the store … consider farm Gen Reaper missions with MC Stripeypants in your team for the 2000 ryo drops in some B-ranks.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-255527</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-255527</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 09:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Would the Ro-Sham-Bo Redux (current team) be a good team to use on A rank missions or should I use a different team.</p> <p>Current stats are:<br /> <img src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v163/Simes/Simes-2.jpg" alt="Simes-2.jpg" class="image" /></p> <p>permanent items are:<br /> <img src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v163/Simes/SimesPermanentItems.jpg" alt="SimesPermanentItems.jpg" class="image" /></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-231182</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-231182</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2008 07:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Got my other items needed and have done some reaper missions, cruise through them without a hassle. Also I finally got Ro-Sham-Bo Redux and did a couple of B-Rank missions and passed them all like they were D-Rank missions</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-225759</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-225759</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 06:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I picked up a heck butterfly from my village's storehouse and learnt EDUT yesterday, so will go do the c and d rank missions, then complete the special mission.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-225362</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-225362</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 17:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>No, there is not.</p> <p>However, there are 3 Reaper items you can get on normal Missions. <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/jutsu:epic-dog-urination-technique">EDUT</a> really helps.</p> <p>The Heck Butterfly and Swallowtail Butterflies from D-Rank missions, and the Soul Glove from C-Rank missions.</p> <p>So, while the Blue Flower Hairpin is certainly nice to have, you don't strictly need it to become a Reaper.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-225050</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-225050</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 06:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I am also working on getting 3 otherworld items to complete the special mission: The Path of The Reaper. Is there any other way besides the Party House to get Hairpin Pieces?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-221327</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-221327</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 06:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Don't wait to buy a couple NWW items at once. You might as well take the benefit that one item gives as soon as possible since you won't gain anything extra by saving the points.</p> <p>And leveling allies usually takes multiple times of passing the mission. Getting Billy to level was one of the biggest pains I had during season 1; it took me 10+ times.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-221316</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-221316</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 05:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok thanks, I nearly have enough points to get one of the first items from NWW. I think I might hold off until I have enough to get 2 or 3 in one go. I think I had billy in the team when I did his lvl up mission, but it is a small chance to lvl them right? With the exception of allies who lvl by giving them items such as ro. Well I will work on getting more allies, learning justu's and increasing my range and strength in all of my areas.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220708</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220708</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 10:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Unless you have something giving you range to pass B-ranks, you probably won't be able to get Billy, Pinky, and Stalkergirl to lvl 2 very easily. All three of them require that you take them along on their B-rank level up mission several times before they'll level. The only one you can probably level up right now is Billy, as he levels on a Genjutsu mission, while Pinky and Stalkergirl level up on Tai and Nin missions respectively. Ro-Sham-Bo Redux is the way to go until you have the range to be able to get Crazy Love Triangle.</p> <p>Also, all of the items that you can purchase with NWW points will be useful to you, though right now I would probably suggest getting the Medals ( +1 Strength in that stat ) first.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220702</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220702</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 09:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Got Lil Bo, now just to get him and lil shammy to lvl 2 for the redux bonus or I could get billy, pinky and stalkergirl to lvl 2 as well since I have them as well.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220612</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220612</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 04:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The Ro-Sham-Bo Redux is probably the ideal team for a Season 1 Sp. Jonin, at least until you have Crazy Love Triangle (Billy Lvl.2, Pinky Lvl.2, Stalkergirl Lvl.2).</p> <p>I should also point out that Sp. Jonin is probably the ideal time to start the Reaper Missions: <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:reaper">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:reaper</a></p> <p>You ought to be strong enough that you can use Epic Dog Urination Technique (which you WILL need) on the missions to get the Heck Butterfly, Swallowtail Butterfly, and Soul Glove and you should be strong enough for most (not all, but most) missions you'll encounter as a Sp. Jonin. You'll need to be Jonin to finish the Reaper missions, but Sp. Jonin's not a bad place to start.</p> <p>Also, just because B ranks are available to you now doesn't mean you have to take them. You can still run C ranks while farming for ryo to buy items or farming for item drops. There's nothing wrong with that either.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220605</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220605</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 04:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok will buy some Chakra Armor when the village I am in get's that upgrade, win a K-Dog Headband and use Ro-Sham-Bo Redux Bonus. I have Lil Ro lvl 2 already, just need to get lil bo and then I can get him and shammy to lvl 2 for the redux bonus. Also would it be helpful to get items from partcipating in the NWW like:</p> <p>Badge of Wisdom<br /> (+1 Gen Lvl) - 200&nbsp;N - Would help me with B Rank missions</p> <p>Medal of Wisdom<br /> (+1 Gen Str) - 500&nbsp;N - Same as Badge of Wisdom</p> <p>or</p> <p>Aura of Experience<br /> (+10% XP/AP) - 800&nbsp;N - Which will allow me to lvl a bit faster, leaning towards this as one can never get enough xp/ap on missions ^_^</p> <p>Perhaps it is more beneficial to me to stick with C Rank missions which I know I can pass and work on getting the other ally needed for Ro-Sham-Bo and the items that were mentioned before I bother with another B Rank mission/s</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220592</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220592</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 03:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>One reason why you're failing missions is you're range. Many B-rank missions have a difficultly of greater then 10, which is as high as you can go in Gen and Nin. Buy Chakra Armor and try to win a K-Dog Headband to increase your range. To increase the chances of passing right away use jutsu that increase range, such as Kido's taught by Shorty(which also give you successes), or Lil' Bo's Welcome to Good Burger. You should also try to get as much strength as possible. And as Uzuki said, Ro-Sham-Bo Redux is probably the best team you can use that doesn't require already being able to beat B-ranks(such as Crazy Love Triangle).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220575</guid>
				<title>Re: Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220575</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 03:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Most new players will tend to use <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/team:ro-sham-bo-redux-bonus">Ro-Sham-Bo Redux Bonus</a> for B-Ranks.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448#post-220574</guid>
				<title>Some Questions</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74448/some-questions#post-220574</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2008 03:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Simes</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>164162</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have just gained access to doing B Rank missions and have only got a success in 1 thanks to billy and his auto win otherwise I fail them. I tried when I was doing the exam to become a Sp Jonin with timmy in the team but he really shafted me and I failed them all. So what is an ideal team to use so I can pass B rank missions? I use billy, pinky and emosuke for original trio bonus and have used them for quite awhile now. Besides all that I would like to get all the allies I have to lvl 2 and get more xp/ap ^_^</p> <p>I am a Sp Jonin (Genjutsu) lvl 32 with the follwing stats:</p> <p>Genjutsu: 11 (+3)<br /> Strength:+1 Range: 1-12<br /> (37822/40000 AP)</p> <p>Ninjutsu: 10 (+3)<br /> Range: 1-10<br /> (25392/26000 AP)</p> <p>Taijutsu: 11 (+3)<br /> Range: 1-10<br /> (4321/40000 AP)</p> <p>Thanks for any tips and advice in advance</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>