<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Hello newbie here!</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Hello newbie here!&quot; - neeed some questions answered!</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:53:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-290989</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-290989</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 15:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sorry, it's <em><strong>I</strong></em> just answered.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-290988</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-290988</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 15:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>boredom struck so yeah… There was a trailing question about alt which U just answered</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-290928</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-290928</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2008 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You do realize that the thread you just answered is made 3 months ago?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-289665</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-289665</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 12:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BloodyANBU</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>128570</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>mynykr: You can have up to 3 alts, up to 2 in the same village. More than 3 alts are not allowed, unless you are making an alt for Evil Taxi's challenge, which allows you to enter a 4th alt if you already had 3 alts. Hope this helped~</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-222072</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-222072</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 10:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mynykr</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I see…<br /> okay thanks ^-^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221966</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221966</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 04:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>What it means is, you can get Redeye, Whiteeye and Legacy, and use whichever one you like.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221927</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221927</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 03:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You can only get 1 of each Arena Bloodline (WhiteEye has 2 uses).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221896</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221896</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 02:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You don't keep any jutsu experience or NWW points. And I don't know if you can get two of the same arena bloodline abilities. I don't think so, since then someone could get their redeye bloodline three times and autowin pretty much any match. I'm pretty sure you can only get 1 of each bloodline.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221892</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221892</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 01:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mynykr</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I see…<br /> when you loop, do you get to keep your jutsu xp?<br /> for that matter, do you get to keep your reputation points or nww points loop? (because the nww items loop, i did research :D)</p> <p>one last question…for today…<br /> it says if i win 10 times in the arena, i get a special prize, and i looked it up but it says i get a blood line trait. it loops AND stacks, does that mean if i win 10 times in 2 seasons i can use white eye 4 times?!?! that would be like insane o_O</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221889</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221889</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 01:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>After one stat(Gen, Nin, Tia) reaches level 18 you will be able to loop. A special mission will pop up called 'into the loop' and it will give you all the info on it. Once one stat reaches 20, a timer will start and if you don't loop after so many days a lot of your bonuses will start getting taken away.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221795</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221795</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 21:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mynykr</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>1.okay i will<br /> 2.technically failed 2 because no forums, my village doesn't have ANYTHING cept the world war and party house…<br /> 3.technically failed #3 because i don't even know how to make potions…and stuff<br /> 4.I PASS WOOT<br /> 5. alts? are you talking about multi accounting? isn't it against the rules? i do have a friend that made his char. on my comp…but that shouldn't be a problem. and i have friends that play on my comp…but they didn't make it on mine so..<br /> 6. will do<br /> 7. special mission sounds good ^_^<br /> 8. am doing<br /> 9. whatever that is<br /> 10. will steal from ware house</p> <p>now my question!! WHAHAHHAHA<br /> when does the season change? when i reach a level or at a certain time?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221750</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221750</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 20:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <ol> <li>Don't blow all your cash at the party house. Save some for jutsu reagents and those buyable permanent items.</li> <li>If your village has a forum, then create a login and try to read the threads at least once a week.</li> <li>Before you try to make like Edward Elric and brew potions, make sure that you a) Know the recipe for what you're trying to make, otherwise it will go kablooie in your face b) fulfill any special requirements the recipe may require (many potions require you to have Bankai to make, something you can't get until Jonin), and c) have the necessary ingredients</li> <li>read the front page when you log in. If McMaster's says don't bug report something, then don't.</li> <li>If you make alts, send them to different villages. Likewise, if you have a spouse, sibling, parent, or child in the same household, make sure their characters are all in different villages.</li> <li>Read the How to Play section</li> <li>Try to get the NWW items as quickly as possible. In season 1 that is mostly going to be due to luck, but just don't forget to do your daily battles. Collecting them all unlocks a very nice special mission.</li> <li>Read the Wiki.</li> <li>Don't eat any wooden nickles.</li> <li>Start saving smokebombs now. You'll thank me when you try for Sanin.</li> </ol> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221664</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221664</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 17:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mynykr</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>okay thanks. any tips for this newbie xD?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221661</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221661</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 17:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Check the items in the wiki to see specifically if they loop, but for sure Party House Super Rares and Monster Drops loop; and most other permanent items loop, too.</p> <p>Also, benefits to being in a village besides Party House and NWW - access to Kaiju, which drop very rare and powerful items; stamina bonuses from upgrades, 70+ if they've all been bought or earned from defeated kaiju; strength bonuses; use trainers to learn jutsu from allies you don't have; storehouse items; brew potions; lower jutsu chakra costs; and probably other stuff I'm not thinking of.</p> <p>You need to be in a large village with lots of upgrades to get these bonuses, so join one of the more established villages unless you want to help a smaller one get to the top. And you don't lose any NWW points or items by switching villages. The only drawback to leaving one village for another is that you have to wait 2 days to join a new village after leaving your old.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221642</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221642</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 17:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mynykr</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I guess…<br /> i still want a bigger benefit though xD<br /> so we do get to keep most of our items? like i have one that you get from winning the wheel (super rare) prize.<br /> also can someone reccoment me a good active village? i've been on everyday since i started the game (except when i had to go on vacation), and i can collect resourcese everyday too!<br /> P.s- if i switch villages, do i lose all the stuff i got from winning battles in the ninja world war?, i usually get lucky and win :D I am saving up for the 800 thing.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221631</guid>
				<title>Re: Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221631</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 17:10:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>1.) Sort of. You keep the same character, but you are reverted back to a level 6 Genin. You get to keep most of your items and you get some cool new stuff, but other than that, you start over. It's really not as bad as it sounds though. It'll take you a while to get there, so you'll learn a lot more before you need to do that.</p> <p>2.) The Ninja World War and Party House are DEFINITELY worth paying the taxes and collecting recourses. And those are just two benefits. Eventually, you'll get upgrades to your village that give you more stamina and a bunch of other cool stuff.</p> <p>And by the way, you need to be in a village to become anything higher than a Chunin, so I suggest you get into one soon.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739#post-221625</guid>
				<title>Hello newbie here!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-74739/hello-newbie-here#post-221625</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 16:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>mynykr</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>167532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>okay so umm i have a few questions.<br /> 1.I've heard of "seasons" in BvS, does that mean after every season, i have to create a new character and start over?<br /> 2. benefit of a village? i hopped into one but all they do is make me collect resources and make me pay taxes D:&lt; only benefit is the ninja world war and party house…:/</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>