<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>BvS Uzuki Alert</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-75697/bvs-uzuki-alert</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;BvS Uzuki Alert&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:55:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-75697#post-224488</guid>
				<title>Re: BvS Uzuki Alert</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-75697/bvs-uzuki-alert#post-224488</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 10:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>How simple do you need them to be? There are already guides for those reachable from the drop-down menu that appears when you hover the cursor over the "Guides" on the navigation bar at the top ( just below the "Search" function ). The Monochrome Guide is just missing the parts on getting a full moon in the Dark Hours of the Arena and completing the Tsukuyomi Ascendant special mission, and the Wasteland Guide doesn't list the order to mix ingredients for the gear you have to make, but other than that they are complete.</p> <p>Monochrome is only for Season 2+ ninja, so until you've finished the first Season, you won't be able to access that content.</p> <p>Also…Uzuki is not the only person to help you with this stuff, others of us can help out too. Even if you specify his name in the topic title, unless it's something only he can help you with, then other people are going to come along and answer your questions anyways. I would suggest making the topic title pertain more to the subject you're addressing in the topic, rather than asking for only a specific person's help. Something like "Newbie Guide for Reaper, etc.?" or even "Could I get a dummy's guide for these?" may have been more appropriate.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-75697#post-224478</guid>
				<title>BvS Uzuki Alert</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-75697/bvs-uzuki-alert#post-224478</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2008 10:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I need a complete newbie dummy guide to complete wasteland, monochrome and reaper bloodlines. The simpler the better coz i dont get the wiki and its too hard coz i only started 2 days ago and im a lvl28 chunin about to be special jounin.<br /> Cheers</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>