<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Speedlooping Guide&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Speedlooping Guide&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-1179677</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-1179677</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 15:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Apples</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Been using crazy love triangle for the extra crank over smith, it's been working for me. (took about 2-3 days not counting the post loop &quot;half day&quot;) 43 on Saturday so I should be done with this loopiness.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-1024496</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-1024496</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 01:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Nyrin</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>SuperChunin gives 11% AP, not 10%</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-985122</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-985122</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 12:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RikaCovena</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>368815</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You don't have to drop that much crank. I run at 22 crank from D through AA and it works just fine. I might need to smoke the field Key and errant bit missions if I just use my stalker/pinky/timmy team, but if I use some of my tons of team changes and put on say billy/stalker/pinky then I can get past them with a very high probability, switching back afterwards.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-984940</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-984940</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 06:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>chaz017</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As for reaching Sannin in speedlooping, I run at 25 crank while speedlooping and I would have to drop by quite a lot to efficiently beat AA missions. I can't help but wonder if the loss in crank is really covered by the gain in AP from AA rank missions.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-891954</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-891954</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 15:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yukimi</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I was wondering if someone would actualise it to proficiently speed-loop. There's a lot of people that have gotten to 111 or are about to get and I'm sure this list needs a few tweaks :P</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-857432</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-857432</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 14:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yukimi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>549005</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm going to speed-loop from season 20 to season 32 soon and I'm stocking stuff (2400 smokies and 360 TACOS sitting in my bucket) and I'm changing my awesome to get the maximum out of it when I finish getting my season collections and all the stuff befpre looping so I really am interested in the most effective way so I can loop EVEN in the same dayroll (if I can afford it) so my real question is that if you are going to loop in the same dayroll or the next one after that, is it really effective to get sannin just taking into account speed-looping and not ryo or anything else? For what you've said I guess the answer is yes but in case this chnages anything, I levae my question about getting sanin and the rest here.</p> <p>Also, any tricks that aren't mention in the general guidelines :D</p> <p>Thanks for everything.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-856457</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-856457</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 08:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Reasons to get Sannin rank:</p> <ul> <li>AA Tai stamina mission is found more often.</li> <li>AA missions give more AP. If crank is at a normal value (13-17), you'll get a +25% AP boost per mission. Less crank means the difference is even greater.</li> <li>AA missions give more ryo. +25% more, to be more exact.</li> <li>High stat level required to loop.</li> </ul> <p>Reasons not to get Sannin rank:</p> <ul> <li>It costs you 150 stamina: tracking, snakeman and big three.</li> <li>It costs you 250k ryo : 150k prize wheel, 100k party room.</li> <li>Missions might be too difficult if you don't have good stats.</li> <li>Low stat level required to loop.</li> </ul> <p>I can't remember the math I did in the past, but around level 31 required for loop it is totally worth it to get Sannin rank.<br /> Other benefits:</p> <ul> <li>Stamina cost to get sannin rank is basically recovered by the AP gain.</li> <li>Ryo cost is recovered by the ryo gain.</li> <li>Yuri (wheel ally) can be leveled in C-rank tai =&gt; less smokebombs used to level some of the C-rank gen level-ups =&gt; less ryo cost.</li> </ul> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-856085</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-856085</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 19:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well, you do get a few extra stamina/app for sannin, but I wouldn't say it's necessary.</p> <p>As for anonymous, if you can get the style points you need for the trade, by doing your one daily bingo for appetite, and making sure you do the village leader for that last part, I don't see why not…it's only 10 stamina lost per day, and you get a fairly good exp booster. Then again, if you're speedlooping, chances are you won't get enough style points in time, as you are only doing about 1-2 days per loop anyways.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-855800</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-855800</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 13:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yukimi</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Is it useful to go for Sannin if you are speedlooping? I don't really tink it necesary at all.</p> <p>And, is it worth the trouble to get annon and obsesive inside jutsu?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-833319</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-833319</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 21:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>sarf</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>423538</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've added which C-rank missions to look out for while speedlooping - included K.Y. in that list.</p> <p>I also reformatted C- and B-rank missions to make it a bit easier to see which to do and why (with regards to Jonin allies).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-822026</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-822026</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 08:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sue2 in day 2, maybe. But Kdog2 is already a stretch.<br /> Keep in mind that character battles aren't your average battle. Getting hit in the last round with a baiman, even while having Lightning Draw, isn't that pretty.<br /> If lucky enough, Sue2 can be gotten in the 1st day.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-821983</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-821983</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 04:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Let's not forget Sue2 and K-Dog 2 from Mahjong. Add in Tsukasa2, and you can get them as soon as you hit Chunin. And considering smoke prices, paying 36k for a couple of games (assuming you have the 10% discount from village upgrade) is not that unreasonable, by the time you start speedlooping.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-821265</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-821265</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 22:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I find it more smokebomb effective to do the following:<br /> Get Tsukasa. Level-up Tsukasa through quest (10 stamina cost).<br /> Get Yuri from partyhouse wheel. Level-up through C-Rank Tai.<br /> By the time you need to level-up the third ally, you should already have at least meatballs and terri. You might be lucky enough in D-ranks to also get Red Rover.<br /> This would reduce the smokebomb cost to an average of 50 instead of 100.</p> <p>So… as Genin:<br /> Tsukasa, Meatballs, Stalkergirl through quests.<br /> Arena fights for JXP to get Escape Jutsu. Not during Dark Hours.<br /> Flipper+Stalkergirl : reach level 12, while smokebombing for allies.<br /> Chunin Exam.</p> <p>As Chunin:<br /> Get Yuri, The Rack, J-Diddy, Lil' Rack*, TACOS*. (* = optional)<br /> C-rank Tai with Stalkergirl and Yuri in team.<br /> Level-up Yuri, get Terri*.<br /> Reach Tai 13. Start Special Jonin Exam.<br /> With Stalkergirl and Timmy in team, get the remaining stuff from D-ranks (Lil' Ro / Red-Eye Jutsu, Billy, Emosuke, Pinky, Red Rover*). Level-up the third ally, while smokebombing C-rank Gen OR, while doing C-rank Tai with Stalkergirl+Timmy+Red Rover, get Dog Treats and get Spot AND, after that, Level-up Spot.<br /> Finish Special Jonin Exam.</p> <p>As Special Jonin:<br /> Billy+Stalkergirl+Pinky team.<br /> Level-up Pinky. Level-up Stalkergirl. Level-up Billy. Get Mr Smith.<br /> Mr Smith + Stalkergirl2 + Pinky2 team.<br /> Get to level 41.<br /> Start Jonin Exam. You should already have waaay over 300,000 Ranking XP.</p> <p>As Jonin:<br /> Megamissions.<br /> Mr Smith + Stalkergirl2 + Pinky2 team.<br /> Get to level 60.^<br /> Get Snakeman.^<br /> Do Sannin Exam.^</p> <p>As Sannin:^ (^ = if you get to season 13, I think… can't remember the math on that)<br /> Get to Tai required for speedlooping.</p> <p>Worth mentioning: you could get the trade level 2 and, obviously, Anonymous (Obsessive Insight jutsu).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-813790</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-813790</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 12:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>blueddict</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>192543</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You could add K.Y. when Chuunin. Good for Jonin Exam. An alternative to Rover's Mom.<br /> [edut] Also, edit RedRover from Special Jonin exam. It's Red Rover.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-757002</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-757002</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2010 08:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>jimwormmaster</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>122250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>And you forgot to add Late-Night Snack. Having that, and the Sp. Jonin upgrade (academy?) will cut your exp needed for jonin by 3, so you'd need a measly 100k exp. Quite easy to do even with only a fair amount of stamina. So no real reason to get Mister Tea, for the ranking…And as it's been said, it takes a fair bit of stamina to get the captain's jacket, even with smokes, so I'd say to avoid the reaper area entirely, to be honest.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-720029</guid>
				<title>Reaper?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-720029</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 12:08:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Hokorippoi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>448532</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I still don't under stand why you would get Captain's Jacket.<br /> TO get Captain's Jacket, you need to put out at less 80 stem. 15 in "The Path Of The Reaper" (half of 30). 10 for Strawberry, and and 50 for "The Reaper Council". I have +188% AP without the Jacket, and I been looping every 3-5 days.</p> <p>With a little good luck It take 1 good day to go from Loop to Sp. Jonin. 1 day to get from Sp. Jonin to Jonin. And 1-3 days to get looped from Jonin.<br /> I got from S6 to S9 in 10 days.</p> <p>EDIT: looping to S10 has taking me 5 days</p> <p>So the Jacket would only be good at higher loops.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-677700</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-677700</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 02:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Guest</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I almost fell off my chair… *still tries to pick up jaw from the ground*</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-602108</guid>
				<title>Speedlooping Guide</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-602108</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 00:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yoshirou</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>138620</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Does anyone else believe that Out on Top should be taken out of this guide? It serves no purpose when speedlooping because you grind a single stat and dont care about the rest. While your stat you are grinding requires 120K AP to level up, one of the other two stats that you dont care about may only need 40K AP and you dont really care that the minor stat leveled up. Please respond.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-533831</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-533831</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Myndaen</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>180441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'd recommend during the D-rank section that people get lil' ro. You need either her or lil' shammy's jutsu for the jonin quests.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-517051</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-517051</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 03:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well, the whole idea of a Rack + Anon + LisaLisa party doesn't make any sort of sense to me.</p> <p>Put LisaLisa Lvl 2 in your party. If Stalkergirl, Pinky, or Emosuke is your 'Valentine' AND you have their S-Rank Drop, put them in the party too. Fill out the rest of your party with either LisaLisa if you don't have her Level 2 form, Pinky/Emosuke/Stalkergirl if you have their S-Rank drop but not their Valentine, or Mr Sandman if you have his Valentine.</p> <p>You can get up to 100 Stamina over dayroll this way.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-515643</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-515643</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2009 20:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Tony6785</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>"++Sannin<br /> There is no Reason to Go Sanin when Speed Looping, as it cost 150,000 ryo to get Sanin as you will need The Rack"</p> <p>This makes no sense, as just above it you tell people to have The Rack in their daily party.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-408606</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-408606</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 07:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Toss Flipper into your team. Do the quests to get Stalkergirl, Meatballs, and Shorty. Run Reaper until you get Robogirl and TicTac. Get your Soul Candy. Run missions with a team of them until you hit Level 12. Go Chunin. You should be able to do all this the first day you loop.</p> <p>As a Chunin, go for important allies you may have missed. These include Pinky, Billy, and Red Rover from Gen-specific D-Ranks. If you're a Red Eye (And why wouldn't you be if you're going for speed?) be on the lookout for the missions that teach Dragon Flame and Mind-Body Switch jutsus. otherwise, be on the lookout for Lil Ro and Emosuke. get Terri from the C-Rank Tai, and be on the lookout for Bruce Sr for future Jonin. Terri, meatballs, and Rover all level on Gen C-Ranks. Spot does too, if you get him along the way. Again, Red Eye and its village upgrade are immensly helpful here. Hopefully, Rover will drop some dog treats along the way. Get Spot if you can, his EDUT jutsu, and a couple of spare treats. Focus on Gen until it hits Level 13. This time, look for K.Y. along the way for future Jonin. Spec Jo time. Timmy Missions go fast with Timmy + Stalkergirl. Toss in Rover if you still need treats. You've levelled 3 allies? welcome to Spec Jo. With a few nice Stamina bonuses, you can do all this in the second day that you loop.</p> <p>Jonin grind takes a bit longer. First real step will be to level Billy, Pinky, and Stalkergirl. Work on Pinky's tai mission first to have 2 allies that give back stamina. Look for Rover's Mom if you still need Jonin allies. While searching for Billy's gen mission, keep an eye out for Annie's mission. If you still need Golden Shinies, you'll want her. She can level while searching for Stalkergirl's nin mission and also Smokey, again if you still need jonin allies. While on a levelling kick, stop by Reaper Tai to level up Timmy. Level 41 means Jonin time. A good day with stam bonuses makes 300K not that hard. Brute force what you can, specific jutsu what you can't. Hopefully, you still have a couple of team changes to complete the exam. This could take a couple of days, but you could be only on Day 3 by the time you make Jonin.</p> <p>Jonin now, yay, but that means griiiind. Take this time to get Trade, and work your way up to Note. Note Rushes are invaluable, as is Anon's jutsu. We need a couple of things from Reaper now, like Strawberry. Look for him in Reaper Tai. Use him to get the Captain's Jacket. Like Annie2 before him, Mister Tea is optional but very useful when going for Golden Shinies. But he can be tricky if you can't afford the allies and jutsu needed to auto-pass his mission, and can't successfully brute force it. Either way, it's the home stretch. Focus on whatever stat is higher, and do A-ranks specific to that stat. Timmy2 + Pinky2 + Stalkergirl2 is the way to go. Use Obsessive Insight on every single mission (some enhancing may be required) and grind, grind, grind that stat up until you can loop.</p> <p>What, you wanna go Sannin? Sannin is a sucker's bet for speed looping. Generally, by the time you just have even enough levels to go for it, you'll be ready or past ready to loop. Then there's the 150K you need to spend to get The Rack. Not worth it.</p> <p>OPTIONAL: Once you get to about Level 48 or so, you can start thinking about Golden Shinies. Most Jonin immediately go for Sannin once they think they can get it. But, with that 1 Million Ranking, you're basically a lock for Top 3 Jonin. When you decide to go for it, make a team of Annie2 + MIster Tea + either Pinky2 or Stalkergirl 2. Get a Note Rush, get the Arena Favorite if you can. Chug any Silver Elixirs you can. If you can get over 1 Mil, you're Top 3, and can go get your Shiny.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-407340</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-407340</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2009 18:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous Poster</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>you completely missed doing the reaper missions as a genin. tictac + robogirl = 2 stamina a mission, putting you up to 4 stamina per mission running c ranks as a chunin.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114#post-343929</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-76114/speedlooping-guide#post-343929</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 19:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>hchan1</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>229416</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Pretty nice guide. It's fairly close to what I do, although dead wrong in a few areas (such as, using Hottie Regen puts you back half a day in terms of speed, so using it is utterly idiotic).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>