<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>BINGO!</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;BINGO!&quot; - B-12,I-41,N-62,G-74,O-86</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828#post-238164</guid>
				<title>Re: BINGO!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo#post-238164</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 17:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Er, okay… thank you for the advice I suppose, but I didn't make this thread so I could get help. I was simply suggesting that a page be created about bingoing which would include everything you've elaborated upon already in this thread plus any tips or whatnot that may help.</p> <p>P.S. I tried what you said about the EDUT and it did work. Thank you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828#post-235367</guid>
				<title>Re: BINGO!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo#post-235367</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 17:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That's probably because you're supposed to use EDUT and the Note Page in the same round, not use EDUT first round and Note Page second round. The Style Point bonus is for when the jutsu is used on the last round of the battle; hence, choose EDUT as your jutsu, check the box for using the Note Page, and THEN click to continue to use both during the same round ( most likely the first ).</p> <p>In probably 8 or 9 out of 10 cases, needing to become a more difficult target means that either you've pissed someone off, or that you're Top 10 on the Season 2+ rankings ( as a Tote target ). I realize there are exemptions to that generalization, but they're the main cases, really. Also, it's a bit harder to avoid being bingo'd if, say, the person targeting you has several levels and some strength above you to begin with, or you don't have Note Page immunity, or if they're using jutsu made for bingoing…</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828#post-235353</guid>
				<title>Re: BINGO!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo#post-235353</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 17:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I have bingo'd two people to date, and am still a bit lost. The first time I did so without a note page because I completely forgot about it (and I did not know about the EDUT bonus at the time) and the second time I used the note page and EDUT but apparently I used EDUT incorrectly because I only got the 35 for the note page bingo (I didn't get any half style point penalty so neither person was bongo'd at the time). I had already read that section of the trade guide as I was bingoing to get the style points for hyuk, though it seems I did something wrong when trying it (I definitely used EDUT as I lost the chakra and a dog treat).</p> <p>And yeah, I meant how to make being bingo'd more difficult for people trying to bingo you. I was aware of most of those tactics but odds are there are people who aren't quite as familiare with those and the "stuff like that". I'm just posing the option of having a page set out to explain this as that's what this site is basically for. Sure, through exploration of the game and trial and error you can figure out the process and details on your own, but the same can be said for pretty much all material put on this wiki. So, a page explaining how to go about bingoing efficiently and making sure you're not an easy target doesn't seem to me to be uncalled for.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828#post-235205</guid>
				<title>Re: BINGO!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo#post-235205</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2008 12:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>@moodragonx: If there's something you don't understand about it, then go bingo someone. That and a little intuition covers most of the basics of bingoing. As far as avoiding it? Um…don't piss people off? It's hard to name a thing in particular that'll get you bingo'd less often.</p> <p>If you mean being harder to bingo? Have your team and Reaper blood set up to do damage or otherwise make bingoing hard for the opponent, use one of the Ending Themes for bingoing ( Seasons Don't Fear or My Name Is ), use the Tools of the Trade upgrade for the village to become immune to Note Pages…stuff like that.</p> <p>Regarding EDUT, a copy/paste of a section of The Trade Guide:</p> <blockquote> <p>If you want to speed things up, at the beginning of bingo combat, utilize a Note Page. <strong>Doing so will insta-kill your opponent and you automatically get 35 points instead of 5 or a little more if you try to kill him the old fashion way.</strong> If you don't have a Note Page, or you just don't want to use one, keep bingo'ing until you get to 200 style points. Another astuce is to <strong>finish the enemy off with Epic Dog Urination Technique, what will give more than 40 points and can be used in junction with a Note page.</strong></p> </blockquote> <p>@Zras: I'm not in a position to say anything about the rules, nor do I use that section much, so I don't really have much to say. If that's a regular problem for you though, maybe you should try using some apples to see whether the potential target is bingo'd or not?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828#post-233989</guid>
				<title>Re: BINGO!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo#post-233989</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 17:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zras</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>175511</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>And on the subject of Bingo.. sorry for the derail but it's kind of related.. Can we get some Bingo Rules for the Village Bingo Book forum? I'm tired of looking for Ninja who supposedly wants to be Bingo'd and try to Bingo them and come to find out that they have already been Bingo'd that day and get half of the style points. It cost me the time of looking them up to Bingo, My notepage and stamina. Rules that are set forth such as the one in Sparring Partners is awesome so that we know who has Bingo'd or whatnot and they can't bump unless its been at least 2 days and 10 spots down etc. Thanks in advance!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828#post-230925</guid>
				<title>BINGO!</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-77828/bingo#post-230925</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2008 23:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I just noticed there's no page explaining the mechanics, in detail, of bingoing. I've looked through pages about the trade and with things about bingo armor, and the like. But nothing that actually explains what it is how it works and how to do it/avoid it efficiently.</p> <p>Personally, I still don't know much on the matter. I've tried my hand at it a few times but what's up with the EDUT thing? In any case clueless people like me and those who just joined would likely appreciate a page elaborating on the subject. Not a guide, but just a page with (as I said) the mechanics of the process and any useful details about it.</p> <p>If I could get the green light I wouldn't mind starting something off (but I obviously don't know much).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>