<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Could use a bit of advice...</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463/could-use-a-bit-of-advice</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Could use a bit of advice...&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:54:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463#post-237853</guid>
				<title>Re: Could use a bit of advice...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463/could-use-a-bit-of-advice#post-237853</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 04:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You're positive you have Hermano? Because the message shouldn't show up after you get the ally. If you do then you might want to bug report this. I don't see any reason you shouldn't have the special mission open.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463#post-237815</guid>
				<title>Re: Could use a bit of advice...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463/could-use-a-bit-of-advice#post-237815</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 02:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>since i too could use a bit of advice<br /> i'll ask right here too<br /> i have hermano, but the mission "A-Level! Protect a Possessed Bird"<br /> always indicates there is hidden rewards in the mission. is this normal?</p> <p>also i think i have all the requirement for "Adventures in the Other Side" o_o<br /> but i cant find it in the special mission.<br /> Tats,Hermano,Fletch,<br /> Bloodline: Blood of the Reaper,Named Sword of the Reaper,<br /> o Kido:Slayer, o Kido:Iron Maiden, o Kido:Metalocalypse</p> <p>are they related?<br /> is it a bug?<br /> what should i do?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463#post-234835</guid>
				<title>Re: Could use a bit of advice...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463/could-use-a-bit-of-advice#post-234835</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 20:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If you're a Legacy, then winning 15 matces in the arena in one day will get you an item that gives you +1 Gen range.<br /> Red Eye and White Eye will give you +1 Nin and +1 Tai range, respectively, but that won't help your Gen range.</p> <p>However, the two range items that you can buy from the arena do really help. It takes a while to get them, but the +3 range is worth it.</p> <p>Chakra Armor and Counterfeit Permits are purchasable from the store as long as your village has a specific upgrade. The items are expensive, but if you save your ryo, you can get them pretty quickly.</p> <p>K-Dog's headband is also an obvious choice if you're lucky enough to win it.</p> <hr /> <p>However, my advice is to wait until you're a Jonin to do Revenge. That'll make it a lot easier.</p> <p>For bingoing, focus on Levels and Strength, not Range. The bingoing difficulty is never higher than 10, so there shouldn't be any problem. Besides, if you're trying to get Hyuk, Note Page + EDUT = WIN</p> <p>For B-rank missions, there's no reason you have to run Gen missions. Run Tai or Nin missions instead. Most of them are two stat, so you'll still get a good amount of Gen AP. CLT helps too. Once you're high enough leveled to get Jonin, do that and your Gen range shouldn't be so bad. (Assuming you've gotten the basic Range items.)</p> <hr /> <p>The good news: You only have to worry about Range in your first Season. By Season 2, you should have so much range that non-Monochrome missions are a piece of cake. (Dark Band + Awesome Pants + Moon = 2-4 Range)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463#post-234661</guid>
				<title>Re: Could use a bit of advice...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463/could-use-a-bit-of-advice#post-234661</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 17:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If your village has pass permits you can buy a counterfeit permit. It's +1 gen range.</p> <p>Besides that it's golden items, arena warrior item(if legacy), Hall Pass, or Storm's Path for gen specific range. None of those I would call easy for a spec jonin though. Besides that just find items to increase range in general.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463#post-234659</guid>
				<title>Could use a bit of advice...</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-79463/could-use-a-bit-of-advice#post-234659</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 17:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wartooth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>174414</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm trying to complete B-rank missions/revenge/bingoing etc, but my Gen range is…well…it's pathetic. What sorts of (not impossible to obtain) items can I find that'll raise that?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>