<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>I would like to write a bingo&#039;ing guide</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80671/i-would-like-to-write-a-bingo-ing-guide</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;I would like to write a bingo&#039;ing guide&quot; - I need permissions or how to do so</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:57:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80671#post-240595</guid>
				<title>Re: I would like to write a bingo&#039;ing guide</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80671/i-would-like-to-write-a-bingo-ing-guide#post-240595</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 18:46:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I was actually asking for the exact same thing in the suggestions area (except I'm much, much, much less knowledgeable about bingoing and it's intricacies). What you could do is go ahead and make a page and just title it Bingo Guide or whatever (in case you don't know how to create a page you just do this: go to <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/[name-of-page-here">http://bvs.wikidot.com/[name-of-page-here</a>] then you should find a blank page that says something like this:</p> <p>The page guide:bingo you want to access does not exist.</p> <p>* create page</p> <p>and you can just click the "create page" link. By doing so you just created the page and then you can just add in whatever content you want). Then you can plead to Uzuki or whoever to add it to the Guide drop down list. Plenty of guides are on the site but not on the drop little drop down thing (eg. <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:xp">Xp</a>). So if you just make a page under:</p> <p><a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:bingo">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:bingo</a><br /> or<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:bingoing">http://bvs.wikidot.com/guide:bingoing</a></p> <p>It should work quite well. And people could easily find it by searching.</p> <p>But to play it safe you may want to wait on a thumbs up to create a page. I'm not sure if it really matters because I would think all additional accurate and articulate content would be appreciated, but it doesn't hurt to play it safe.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80671#post-237445</guid>
				<title>I would like to write a bingo&#039;ing guide</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80671/i-would-like-to-write-a-bingo-ing-guide#post-237445</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 07:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Blah Nin</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>156677</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think I can write a guide fairly easily. I am intelligent, can spell well, and rarely miss things in edits. Praise Satan our Lord and Master. I know all about Bingo'ing, and have three characters who have all made the trade. Pretty much all the information is on the site, but it has yet to be organized in a coherent fashion. So, Uzuki, or someone else, can I get a bingo guide under the guides section and permission to edit it?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>