<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>A few probs with Fletch</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741/a-few-probs-with-fletch</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;A few probs with Fletch&quot; - Him actually dropping</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:57:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741#post-238239</guid>
				<title>Re: A few probs with Fletch</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741/a-few-probs-with-fletch#post-238239</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 19:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yeah, my mistake. Stand By Your Ninja, not All Together Now.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741#post-237810</guid>
				<title>Re: A few probs with Fletch</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741/a-few-probs-with-fletch#post-237810</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 02:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think you mean Stand By Your Ninja. All Together Now is for levelling up allies.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741#post-237638</guid>
				<title>Re: A few probs with Fletch</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741/a-few-probs-with-fletch#post-237638</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>First, this is in the wrong section. It should be in Bill Vs. SNAKEMAN / General, not Wiki / General, but anyway…</p> <p>Your first option is to use a Monochrome Pheromone. That'll give you a 100% ally get chance on your next reaper mission. Run missions until you get Sew Up a Plushie then go back to main and use the Monochrome Pheromone (before completing the mission). Go back to the mission, finish it, and you should have Fletch.</p> <p>If you can't get your hands on one, then you want to stack as many ally get bonuses that you can.</p> <p>MC Stripeypants + All Together Now + Ichi Ramen Special = 8x find chance.</p> <p>If you're WhiteEye, add in WhiteEye for a 16x find chance.</p> <p>If (and only if) you can manage to get through the beginning of Monochrome without Bankai, then you can try to make a rush for Miss Kitty and learn her Kido: I Can Haz a Cheezburger jutsu, which gives a x10 ally/item find chance. Stacked with Stripeypants, ATN, and Ichi Ramen, that's an 80x find chance, which should be an auto-get.</p> <p>If your level cap is getting too close for comfort, use potions for smoke bombs instead of stamina. Smoke bomb out of missions you don't want.</p> <p>Your last option is to just not complete Reaper this season. There's really no reason you need to get Bankai. It doesn't loop and there are no lasting benefits for it. Bankai is really just a step to help you complete other more difficult parts of the game (Monochrome and Wasteland). If you can complete them without Bankai/Shorty2/Mister Six, then I wouldn't bother with Bankai.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741#post-237626</guid>
				<title>A few probs with Fletch</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-80741/a-few-probs-with-fletch#post-237626</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 18:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ok well, I understand i'm probably just unlucky but I am unable to unlock Fletch. I understand he drops from the A rank mission sew up a plushie, I am currently season 2 and have the crank on level 1. I have been running Genjutsu reaper missions for so long I am getting horribly close to the cap. Any suggestions/feedback of what I should do greatly appreciated.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>