<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Super-Rare Grand Prize&quot; - Super reare grand prize in the party house.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:57:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-251493</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-251493</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Does that mean you can only Power of Greass it once a season?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-251124</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-251124</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 02:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>All of the Monument Missions are techinically the same mission, just with slightly different text. This has been proven by people using Sight Beyond Sight to repeat a Monument Mission, and getting different ones.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-250754</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-250754</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 18:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Pure speculation is that the the odds of getting a monument mission are not calculated with the missions being separate. So it's not 11/37 but 1/26 and then it randomly selects which mission is displayed. 1/26 = 3.846…% so it makes it much rarer, 30% really isn't rare, and correlates with what you've experienced.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-250748</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-250748</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 18:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kelumhi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>24443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>the more i run wasteland missions the more i think the Monument missions are rare. out of the 300 not-wasteland disease missions i have ran Ive only seen a monument mission 8 times or so, when the number of missions for them are 11/37.</p> <p>8/300=2.67%<br /> 11/37=29.7297297%</p> <p>which comes out to be a difference of 11.1486486486486… percent</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-250216</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-250216</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 07:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>argent</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99364</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Can you verify that each certain missions are rarer than others?</p> </blockquote> <p>Without access to the code or word from on high, verification is impossible.</p> <p>What I've done is mission tracking. Created a spreadsheet and started recording what missions showed up and how often. Running strictly general missions.</p> <p>When you track 200+ missions, and some show up a dozen times, while others only show up twice, you can make some guesses as to how rare a mission is. On the other hand, the sample size (under 1000) is rather small, so they're only guesses.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-250114</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-250114</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 02:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>chris1887</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>193039</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>4 kunai in a row,wow<br /> the only 2 super rare i got is stealth suit and the first hocage necklace</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-245197</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-245197</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 00:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kelumhi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>24443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>your correct in what i was thinking of, about using SBS on that mission, but ill take your word for it and just asumed that i read it incorrectly. thankyou for correcting me.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-243464</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-243464</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 10:50:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Oh, really? As much as I would ask to see proof of it, I'm fairly certain that what you're thinking of was from McM mentioning how low the drop rates of Runes were, and that you'd probably being using Sight Beyond Sight on them due to how low the drop rate is for them.</p> <p>Seriously, the only time that a mission will really seem rarer is when you're looking for it in particular, when it's spammable under a certain stat and you're running general missions, or when it can only be found running general missions and you're running under a specific stat.</p> <p>I fully agree with Lear on this subject. Some of you who don't yet might want to try running a couple missions at with 30 or so levels ( similar to the number of missions you run in a day, maybe less ) and your strength as close to 0 as possible. It should be the same RNG, just working in a different section, right? Just switch to Bankai, perhaps Wasteland jutsu or allies…the main point here is what Lear was saying: that you may see patterns in a random sample that really aren't patterns.</p> <p>It is difficult to simply say "From what I've seen running a relatively small number of missions, the RNG is completely biased ( in favor of/in opposition to ) this and/or that particular mission." Proving tendancies in a program that is meant to produce random results requires large samples of data.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-243422</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-243422</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 08:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>he had maid notions that Some missions were more rare, the runic ones in particular</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-242785</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-242785</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 04:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Can you verify that each certain missions are rarer than others? I've never seen McM make any statement about that, and anything else is just speculation.</p> <p>I did consider the possibility that all missions weren't equal chances, but for the purposes of my post, I assumed they were. It doesn't change any of my points, and if anything, would reinforce them. (If one mission is more likely to appear, you're more likely to get it twice in a row.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-242781</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-242781</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 04:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>argent</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99364</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Lear - You're assuming each mission has equal odds of appearing. That isn't the case. Some missions actually are rarer than others.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-242027</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-242027</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 23:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kelumhi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>24443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>mcmasters made his own code? thats awesome</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-241312</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-241312</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 16:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Ren Po Ken</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103468</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>There are hot streaks, cold streaks, and streaks of hot pictures of Terri. In any random system, streaks are inevitable. Also inevitable, streaks end. If you get a monkey to pound away on a keyboard long enough, you will eventually get the complete works of Konami. Long before that happens, you will get various Stephen King novels, The Davinci Code, reality TV shows in .avi format, the source code for the BvS SWATBU content, and a pissed off monkey. These are all steaks. A streak is simply the human mind (I apologize if you are not human) ascribing meaning to a slice of random values.</p> <p>I highly doubt, given the fact that there is an RNG built into every programming language, that McMasters went out and made his own. I find it even more unlikely that if he did, that it would be any less random than the ones that come with a language. The RNG is no more broken than any other RNG out there.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-241310</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-241310</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 16:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>2 cheating spins in a row were Hot Pictures of Terri.</p> <p>In total, of my 11 spins today, 4 of them were Terri Pics.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-241046</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-241046</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 20:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I don't think that it's that the RNG is broken. In fact, I don't really see how the RNG could be broken, unless of course, he's purposely written code to make it return the previous result more often than others.</p> <p>What I think is happening, is that your fooling yourself into thinking that it's broken. You're finding unlikely results (or results that appear unlikely) and isolating them, rather than weighting them appropriately by their likelyhood.</p> <p>For example, let's say there are 4 possible outcomes for a randomly determined event, all equally likely. We'll call them A, B, C, and D.</p> <p>Now, which is more likely, getting two of the same in a row, or getting all 4 in a row (any order) without any duplicates?</p> <p>Getting two As in a row, and by a fairly significant margin.<br /> Two in a row = 1/4 chance<br /> All 4, no duplicates = 6/64 chance</p> <p>Now, which would you notice more, two of the same in a row or getting all 4 without duplicates?</p> <p>Getting two of the same kind in a row, and you'd think of it as being unusual. That's not really fair, though. You're ignoring all of the other equally unlikely or even more unlikely results.</p> <p>Now, which is more likely, getting A,A,A,A or getting A, B, D, A?</p> <p>They're equally unlikely. Both have a 1/256 chance of occuring. But would you really stop to think, "Wow, ABDA, that's surprising. I can't believe that happened."? Of course not, and you shouldn't think that. You shouldn't think that about AAAA either, but it's inevitable that you're going to.</p> <hr /> <p>The same works on a scale similar to the game's. Let's say that you're trying to level Annie. Her level mission, Teach a Class, is a Nin B-rank, so you just run Nin missions to increase her chances of leveling.</p> <p>Now, the first mission, you end up getting Defend the WhiteEye Princess, and you think, "Damn! I should have brought Stalkergirl too!" Or maybe you've already leveled her and think, "Damn! Took forever to get her mission when I was trying to level her, and now I get it when I no longer want it!" Well, so you complete (or smokebomb the mission) and the next mission you get is Defend the WhiteEye Princess again. By now you're probably thinking that the RNG is hating you, and you might be right, but it's just random, not due to any bias it has. The odds are 1/11 that you'd get that mission again, no less likely than getting say, Row a Gondola, or Teach a Class, both of which you'd have probably been happy with.</p> <p>Now, let's say you've run 20 missions, and that mission you need still hasn't shown up. You think that it's been mean to you, but what are the actual odds of it not coming up in 20 missions? About 15%, not horribly unlikely.</p> <p>The prize wheel could be worse, and it's really not possible to assess because we don't know the exact odds of each prize. Now, have I gotten two Super-rares in a row before? Yes. Has that happened to me after that? No. Have I had plenty of days where the most valuable thing I won was a shuriken? Yup. It goes both ways, and everything in between.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-240837</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-240837</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 07:46:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lokumun</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112075</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think the RNG is a little broken. My theory is that the RNG has a great tendency to pick similar picks to earlier ones. Meaning that you'll either get abysmal luck, or insanely awesome luck.</p> <p>I'm planning on eventually testing the RNG through missions, and maybe getting enough proof to convince McM to change it. Having the RNGod stripped of it's cruel, tortuous, awful powers would be absolutely wonderful.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-240129</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-240129</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 19:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KazeNR</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>87475</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yeah, me too, in the first try in both of my accounts. And still can't get the codec, so far, I have nearly all super rares but the codec and love paradise, oh, and 2 extra necklaces.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-238861</guid>
				<title>Re: Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-238861</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MRUhlir</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>145588</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Probabilities are fickle. I've done 10+ spins on the wheel and gotten nothing better then a kunia, other times I roll 5 times and get two +50 stam, +100 stam, giant fan and yuri. Be happy, remember - the RNG will make it up to you later, so don't ask why you get the same mission 5 times in a row when you're looking for a different one.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034#post-238511</guid>
				<title>Super-Rare Grand Prize</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81034/super-rare-grand-prize#post-238511</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 07:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Noukon</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>163625</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I was wondering if there was something wrong with the odds or something for today.</p> <p>i won the super-rare grand prize twice, and the rare 3 times.. and i only played 7 times in total…</p> <p>Wierd.</p> <p>(yes, i understand some of my vocabulary, and grammar may be a little disastrous… i just type fast, and Clearly make mistakes)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>