<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Ryo makes the world go round.</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Ryo makes the world go round.&quot; - It&#039;s true.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:32:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727#post-1127924</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round#post-1127924</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 21:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wydra</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>currently the easiest way to obtain ryo for anyone who is newer to the game but has their stats at a resoneable lvl is to check the front page for any new content that requires easily obtainable items such as ash covered's to get permanents. Top ranked players seem to feel these missions above them and or have a very effective way of making ryo, so they will dish out big bucks to obtain these items. The market place is your friend use it see the fluctuation in the bvs worlds prices and you can sell your unwanted items for a substantial amount of ryo.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727#post-242109</guid>
				<title>Re: Ryo makes the world go round.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round#post-242109</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay the page was updated. If anyone has anything to add, please say/do so :).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727#post-240600</guid>
				<title>Re: Ryo makes the world go round.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round#post-240600</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Oh right I should have caught that about I Can Has Cheezburger, but MC Stripey says that he has double the chance of "finding things". I assumed that wording meant that he found events as well, but I suppose it just means he find items and ninja easier like all the other allies that do that :| Oh well. I could include to bring strawberry and shorty as well so you can get dozens of silver petals that sell low, but are very common drops.</p> <p>The A-ranks idea is good as well, but I think the item prices you posted are a bit high (I'm not sure though). Regardless A-ranks, AA-ranks, and S-ranks, all give more base ryo than reaper missions (B-ranks give less) but I'm not sure where it would balance out as Gen reaper missions have the the chance of giving you 2000 ryo. I could try doing some spading myself as I'm looking to farm ryo for my upcoming sannin run anyway. But I don't have any of those season 2+ allies you mentioned :(.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727#post-240495</guid>
				<title>Re: Ryo makes the world go round.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round#post-240495</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 15:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>rash92</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>136343</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>get stalkergirl 2, and pinky 2 and cato and run A-ranks/ AA-ranks is a good way of farming ryo, or get tictac and robogirl (for the +2 stamina per mission bonus) and run general reaper missions. those are the two most efficient ways. A-ranks give more, but they may be wuite hard for some people and are only available for jonin/ sannin. reaper missions give more if you don't think you can pass ALL A-ranks or if your not jonin yet.</p> <p>alternatively, get emo 2 and any other ally that gives drops worth a lot of money (like billy 3, buckets), and also have olmek, and run A-ranks, so you get the normal money+ whatever from the drops. (blades = 750, pic = 250 and cd's = 500 last time i checked)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727#post-240485</guid>
				<title>Re: Ryo makes the world go round.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round#post-240485</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 15:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Feel free to add it. However, I Can Has Cheezburger has no affect on getting the 2k ryos from Gen Reapers, nor does MC Stripeypants. It's considered an event, and not an item or ally, so only WhiteEye can boost the chances to get it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727#post-240311</guid>
				<title>Ryo makes the world go round.</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81727/ryo-makes-the-world-go-round#post-240311</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 06:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/ryo">ryo</a> page is sadly very blank. As most of the information concerning ryo is scattered around the wiki to where it's applicable (missions pages, item/store pages, party house, Xp Guide, etc….) this page can still be put to some use. First of all, basic info concerning where it can be obtained, how to put it to use, how to spend it efficiently, etc, can be provided. I can (and am about to) handle all of that myself (though i'm bound to miss alot so help is appreciated). I was just wondering if there were any particular tactics to be used for farming ryo. One I've heard of is this:</p> <p>Take MC stripeypants along with 2 other reaper allies and run genjutsu missions. There are 2 (both B-ranks) out of only 7 or 8 gen missions that have a hidden 2k ryo in them. MC double the chance of finding them. If you have <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/allies:miss-kitty">Miss Kitty</a>'s <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/jutsu:kido:i-can-has-cheezburger">Kido: I Can Has Cheezburger</a> you can use it to boost that to a 20x chance of finding it (though it has a high chakra cost).</p> <p>Also you can list all sources of extra ryo like the ever obvious aura of ryo/letter of marquee and the fact that taking a general mission has a ryo bonus. And that with every additional season (or crank level) yo get additional ryo as well.</p> <p>Um.. I can't think of anything else at the moment and it's getting quite late so, I'm actually going to postpone updating that page till tommorow. Unless someone else want to tackle it tonight, or before I can manage to. I have no problem with it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>