<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Juice Bar</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Juice Bar&quot; - A few questions.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:38:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-346250</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-346250</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 04:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Congratulations. Nice to know it all went well for you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-346234</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-346234</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 03:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's been a while but as an update I'd like to inform anyone reading that I did make #1 the day after my sannin run with <strong>over 3.6 mil XP</strong> (as a sannin since the sannin special mission was re-ordered to stop exactly what I was trying to do). <strong>SO I got <span style="text-decoration: underline;">out on top</span>, <span style="text-decoration: underline;">2&nbsp;B A Master</span>, and <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Sannin</span> in one day, plus I managed to <span style="text-decoration: underline;">hang out with 4 friends</span> on my sannin run day so the next day when I looped I got <span style="text-decoration: underline;">Nadeshiko</span>.</strong> All the peices just seemed to fall together that day.</p> <p>Yes. I am that amazing.</p> <p>Incidentally I'm trying for my S2 Sannin run and was just checking this thread for reference and noticed I never mentioned what became of me. In any case I don't need any help this time around just thought I'd say yippee for old times sake.</p> <p>HUGE thanks to everyone who bothered to read that mess and respond so quickly, thoroughly, and diligently. I probably could have done it without you, but your help was appreciated anyway (Just Kidding).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-260862</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-260862</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 02:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Now that's if everything goes according to plan. Which it won't…</p> </blockquote> <p>It's like I could see into the future. It's kind of scary actually.</p> <p>Me in my brilliance decided it'd be fun to take an extra week to prepare all the nitty gritty details. Like making sure I have enough friend points to hang out with both anonymous and shorty, while trying to get a few thousand more ryo for an extra party. While doing so I chose to ignore that fact that my loop timer was menacingly coming closer. day 14. I'm on day 14 and my procrastination means I am 2 days away from traveling to another village without a tele-village potion and my appetite is at 80… out of the 100 necessary to chug one. Really all this means is I lose out on the note rush. The 20% boost would have been amazing and been the factor that would have pushed me over 2 mil and gave me a decent shot at geting a golden yummy. Oh well. I'll still have like 1.4 mil without it, enough to get me sannin, but not much better.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242895</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242895</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 12:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well…the loop timer blocks you out from Bingoing, getting tickets toward monster drops, etc. at day 15, which would block you from getting the Note Rush for the extra XP, but your stamina isn't capped to like 72 until day 31 of the timer.</p> <p>FP totals for hanging out are checked at dayroll. This gives you the whole of the day to earn FP for the hangouts, and the whole of the next day to do the mission, should you be hanging out with them.</p> <p>Should your village get the upgrades for you to buy ramen, the options would be 15k for Chakra or Appetite, I think 30k for +3 levels on missions, 90k for +30 stamina, 100k for 2x find chance ( doesn't affect ally drops though ), 400k for +100 stamina, and 1 mil for +10 arena fights. The suggestion to not purchase ramen was just for the sake of making sure you have the jXP you need sooner.</p> <p>Of course, this is going to be your plan. If you want to avoid the higher-ranked missions so that you can run more missions and get more ryo before your run, that's certainly an option for you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242872</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242872</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 10:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Zeekee</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>176256</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Question: As I've never "hung out" with an ally before, I don't know, so does hanging out status update upon dayroll, or is it an immediate affect?</p> </blockquote> <p>The hanging out bonus occurs the day after. And there will be a message in your "Daily Report" Box ie I got this today "Friendship Bonus 8/20 (Wed):You are hanging out with Hyuk today! Your Friend Points with them are set to zero, but you get special bonuses! Mood Ring Bonus! +30 Stamina for hanging out with at least one Ally today!</p> <p>And as for the 1&nbsp;000&nbsp;000 XP "Theme "Teacher's Pet" don't worry… you will get a lot of XP doing your Sanin run! So feel free to use it as you please beforehand for Ano and Right's jutsus…</p> <p>And one more thing I just thought of… Since you are Legacy you can by buying +30 Appetite from the Juice Bar for 18000 Ryo and (I hope you have Hollow leg) end up with 250 Appetite. That would be 5 Silver Elixirs or 500&nbsp;000 XP! Then spend the last 6 drinks on +30 Stamina for another 9000 Ryo!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242779</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242779</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 04:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well I have 1,200,000 some JXP as of right now. I want to buy both of right and Anon's Jutsu while hanging out with them to reduce costs and do indeed need to enhace anon's. But beyond that I want to loop with 1 mil JXP for the theme.</p> <p>I've got 5 apples and 5 note pages. I'll only need 2 of the apples to pull off all the bingo's, so I'm pretty sure I'm set there.</p> <p>I forgot to mention I still need to farm a ton of petals for my silver elixirs, but I was planning on doing that while running reaper gen missions.</p> <p>I do have both billy and emo at lvl 2 as of right now. I completely forgot about the razor blades necessary, so thanks for reminding me. So I'll be running never say yaoi in A-ranks for the sake of the billy buckets and blades. I've heard the level rate for billy 3 is very aggravating so I expect this to be fun.</p> <p>Instead of running B-ranks, could I run D-ranks for the ally drops instead? B-ranks do have decent ryo, but I'm hoping to cut down on AP, and D-ranks have a better Ryo:AP ratio, and there's no less chance of ally drops.</p> <p>I should probably go ahead and get J-diddy the cheap way, though. So I'll do General B-ranks at some point either for ally drops or friend points.</p> <p>If possible I'd like to also avoid tai missions due to this accursed carapace armor. I almost (just almost) wish I hadn't won the kaiju lottery with this one :\. So for the friend points I guess I'll try my luck with the A-ranked ninjutsu missions.</p> <p>I don't have the option to even buy ramen yet -.-. Though I'm not sure if it will be completely horrible once my village gets the upgrade as…<br /> Dark Consolidation costs 300k JXP thus 150k JXP while hanging out.<br /> Obssesive insight is the same.<br /> Then you pay 600k XP to enhance OI once, though I'm not sure if the village I'm borrowing with have ancient tomes to drop jutsu enhancement by 10%.<br /> regardless, that's alltogether only 900,000 JXP. I have 200k JXP saved up that I can spare (keeping 1 million in reserve for the theme), thus I think I could spare the daily 10 or 20,000 for some ramen? Maybe not. I'll just have to pace myself and see.</p> <p>Question: As I've never "hung out" with an ally before, I don't know, so does hanging out status update upon dayroll, or is it an immediate affect?</p> <p>And also, the loop timer givers you 30 days? I thought it was 2 weeks (if it is 30 days, then the looping guide needs to be updated).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242697</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242697</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 00:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Assuming you have Emosuke lvl 2 to begin with, run the Never Say Yaoi team ( Billy 2 and Emo 2 ) through General A-rank missions looking for Withstand the Eyepatch of the Soul, and use Flying Thunder God Technique to auto-pass. Hopefully Billy will level on the first try. If not, keep running, and either let the mission sit through dayroll the next time you get it or use something strong like Kido: Nightfall, or the Bone Daddy summon with something like Pinky Style: Pervert Destroying Punch.</p> <p>After Billy has leveled, if you already have the Razor Blades you need, see if you can borrow a Billy Bucket from your village. If you can't or need Razor Blades, switch to running General B-rank missions ( for the ryo ) with Billy, Emo, and another ally with drops you need, or otherwise Pinky lvl 2. If you only have a few apples, stock up on more with Hyuk for getting Note 2. Pages? Use Right. Need more petals? Shorty or Strawberry. Don't need any of those? Pinky2 for the extra stamina as well as Exploding Tag drops.</p> <p>Once you've got Emosuke lvl 3 mission started, so long as you make sure to stop before they hit Hangout levels, start doing General B-ranks with Anon, Right, and Tic Tac. Oh, now that I think of it—doing General B-ranks brings up the Have a Shexy Party mission, which drops J-Diddy, a potential bonus for you at this point: more FP per mission. If one of them is requiring more FP than the other, give him a little boost to FP without the other in the party, but keeping them both in safe levels. Then, either run a day of Tai C-rank missions with Anon/Right/(Tic Tac or J-Diddy), or a day of Nin A-rank missions with Anon/Right/Emo3. The goal there is more FP through mission bonuses: 200 FP per mission with a potential +1500 from Sabotage Armor in Tai C-ranks, or 50 FP per mission potential +4000 from Impersonate A Village Leader in Nin A-ranks. It's your choice, depends on your luck and available stamina either way.</p> <p>Don't buy ramen, since you need so much jXP prior to your run, especially if you haven't learnt OI and DC yet or enhanced OI.</p> <p>Remember, if push comes to shove, you've still got 30 days from when a stat of yours hits 20 to do everything. You'll probably be done with most of that a few days into your loop timer to begin with.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242650</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242650</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 21:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay then. This strayed far from the topic the title may have suggested, but since my sannin run is being discussed here, I might as well post here as well.</p> <p>In my preperations for sannin I seemed to have run into… a problem.</p> <p>I have both right and anonymous, and now I'm charged with the task of hanging out with both of them on the same day (in order to get note lvl 2 and note rush). The friend rankings say that I need 70k+ friend points to manage something like that.</p> <p>I have about 1,000 arena rep and am saving up to get "arena favorite". Now if I were to try and get 2 pheromones I'd need 6,500 arena points for the whole thing (or 5,200 if I hop into a village with pilot training).</p> <p>I could take the route of throwing a bunch of parties, but I have virtually no ryo and am saving up once again to throw all out bashes during my sannin run.</p> <p>Currently have<br /> Lvl 18 Gen (97373/300000 AP)<br /> Lvl 17 Nin (257453/300000 AP)<br /> Lvl 18 Tai (34150/300000 AP)</p> <p>+10% AP from captains jacket<br /> +10% AP from Letter of Marque<br /> +10% Tai AP from carapace armor</p> <p>I also have to get billy to lvl 3, then emosuke to lvl 3, complete another 90 spars, then get just over 2.2million Jutsu exp, all before I reach my sannin run day.</p> <p>I don't have Jarai yet, but I do have Love Love paradise.</p> <p>Any suggestions?</p> <p>I'd rather not have to skip out on any portion of my plan but I may need to drop something like the note rush, or arena favorite, or possibly my all out bashes the day of. If anything the partying would have to go considering it's only be an extra 20 or 30k XP at best.</p> <p>I know I said I was pretty ready but I underestimated what it took to get note lvl 2.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242428</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242428</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 16:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You would get a message on your main screen that would tell you that you were the top in your rank. You get it for top 3 as well, if I remember correctly. At least that's how it used to be. It could have been changed.</p> <p>Regardless, it's somewhat pointless to try that a second Season if it doesn't work this Season. In Season 2, you'll be able to get Sannin earlier, and you'll want to hold out on looping until later. In Season 1, you don't get to spend much time as Sannin, but with a loop cap of 23 and permanent items that make running A-ranks a piece of cake, you'll be able to get Sannin almost as soon as you get Jonin, if you chose to do that. The Season 2+ top ranked looks high, but the Season 2 bonuses, plus being able to run AA-ranks makes getting that much XP a lot easier.</p> <p>Short version: It doesn't make that much sense to try an out on top run as Jonin in Season 2. It's more beneficial to do it as a Sannin.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242107</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242107</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 03:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Er, not sure at all how, but I suddenly have 16 nin range O.o. Not counting allies or anything. Still four strength, and 1 free success. I'm going to do the math with my items because I don't remember changing anything recently except for finally getting the trade.</p> <p>Update: I also got letter of marquee. That's an additional one range… oh and I got a k-Dog's headband as well. Okay then that makes sense.</p> <p>In any case even if that helps my chances by like 6%, I'm not going for wastelands this season. I'm way in the beginning and I don't have the luck to rush through it :\. I'll be able to redo it as a legacy in season 4 :).</p> <p>Anyway, thanks for all the help everyone. I'm (mentally) ready for the sannin insanity. On a fun note: today's top 3 (s1) players were all jonin at dayroll. this means I'm probably not the only one trying to pull something like this. Thus, unless I get over 2 mil (today's top person was a little over 2 million XP) on my run, I'm going to have to wait for the out on top theme.</p> <p>Even though I'm basically ready and everything, I do have a question. How do you know the individual rank standings for season 2+? For example if I tried pulling something identical to this in S2, how would I know I was the number one ranked jonin, separate from all ranked sannin?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242081</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242081</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2008 02:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Based on my stats Spinal Tap is the best (though it's the difference between a 98% and a 97%). I suppose I was wrong to assume that it would be the same to him, but I wasn't really thinking too in depth. Regardless, the point is that his chances are low. Anything lower than a 30%, and I wouldn't bother with it.</p> <p>I didn't include any items other than the Glasses because a.) cowls, boots, cloaks, and guns don't help and b.) I forgot you'd need at least a silver scythe to get to EotS. I was assuming he'd have the worst (as it'd be a pretty quick rush), and I was too lazy to look up what it gave, so I just didn't include it. Again, point is, the odds are low, which is what I figured when I saw 14 Nin range.</p> <blockquote> <p>Yeah, now that you mention it, pretty sure J-Diddy is needed for the mission, but that ( and with the bloodline requirements ) are things people forget about during the planning—they aren't the hard part, so they're easier to overlook.</p> </blockquote> <p>Okay, yeah, you caught me there. Add 1 to the "What kind of idiot are you?" moments for me.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-242028</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-242028</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 23:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Why does everyone assume Spinal Tap is the way to go for Eye of the Storm's Nin 25d 25s check? For those stats, you could get 12% using the +5 Nin success jutsu that Sticky2 teaches, as well as…I think it was about +3% for each level gain and +5% for each range gained prior to actually taking the mission. Also, does the scythe work for the Eye of the Storm stat check?</p> <p>Yeah, now that you mention it, pretty sure J-Diddy is needed for the mission, but that ( and with the bloodline requirements ) are things people forget about during the planning—they aren't the hard part, so they're easier to overlook.</p> <p>Anything else I might try to say, Lear has already covered, though. Good luck with whatever you choose.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241839</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241839</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 16:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Alrighty then, I'm postponing 500k in the party house for later,. My reasoning behind getting J-diddy was that I was hoping to get sannin :P</p> <p>Unless he's not needed for the sannin special mission anymore? I thought he was one of the three allies you needed. In any case, whether I need him or not, he's coming with me.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241835</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241835</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 16:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>J-Diddy doesn't loop, nor does he give any theme or other looping effect. There's no reason you need to get him. He's useful to have (because of the 4x friend points), but if you're not going to use him, I wouldn't worry about it.</p> <p>Of course, if you'd get him just by doing what you'd do anyway, then great, but I wouldn't worry about it.</p> <p>Spending 500k in the party house is tough as Season 1, but it makes farming ryo a lot easier.</p> <p>Of course, getting and spending 500k ryo is a lot easier in Season 2 because you have more ryo bonuses. You get the Sannin's premium (+15% ryo), Cato (+25% ryo), and Rich Man's World (+15% ryo) (though Right's jutsu is better for ryo). Money for Nothing gives an additional +25% ryo, but if you can get that in Season 3, that's pretty good.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241598</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241598</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 07:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well that takes a huge load off. Now instead of shooting for number one I can succumb to mediocrity and shoot for #3. Plus that equated to only one XP run to worry about.</p> <p>Everything you mentioned I either have or am on the verge of having besides Nadeshiko (waiting for the floating on air theme), sevens trophy, and -sadly- 500k in party house. I have spent 150,000 on the prize wheel, and am saving up to spend at least 120,000 on the party room (need 100k for J-Diddy and feel like doing all of that on the day of my sannin run for maximum daily XP). That leaves me at 270,000 at best there. And that's if I can save up that 120,000 in time. I might end up just running general B-ranks to get J-diddy that way if it doesn't look plausible. Unless I can find a magical way to make ryo in S1, I'll have to look forward to that theme later.</p> <p>Oh well. This all helped a lot.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241448</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241448</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 23:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Okay, you're a legacy. (Sorry, never picked up what bloodline you had.)</p> <p>Whether you should complete it during this season hinges on one important question:</p> <p>Do you think you can beat a Nin 25d25s mission using with a MAX of +6 strength (if you're using Rock On:Spinal Tap)?</p> <p>You said that you have 14 Nin range, right?<br /> 14 Range + 6 (Sticky2) + 8 (Palmface) + 5 (Venus) + 2 (Spinal Tap) = 35 Range<br /> Assuming 17 levels + 3 (Sticky2) + 8 (Palmface) + 5 (Bankai) + 2 (Sword) + 1 (Monster Mask) + 1 (Soul Glove) + 1 (Letter of Marque) = 38 Levels<br /> 1 Success (Letter of Marque)<br /> And 6 strength (1 (Not Wasteland Disease) + 1 (Cote) + 1 (Desert Shades) + 1 (Venus) + 2 (Spinal Tap))</p> <p>BvS Calculator says: 5.0483% chance of success.</p> <p>So I guess, no. You shouldn't worry about completing Wasteland this Season. You can get the item by doing it as a Legacy in Season 4.</p> <p>By the way, the reward would be the Eye of the Storm Bloodline and Storms Path (+2 gen range).</p> <hr /> <p>Anyway, things you want to have in Season 1 before you loop and what they'll get you:</p> <p>True Blood of the Reaper (gives Seasons Don't Fear theme- +100% HP on bingos)<br /> Sannin (gives Sannin's Premium and Sannin theme)<br /> Emosuke Lvl. 3 and Billy Lvl. 3 (gives Battle Champions theme- Double Friend Points on missions)<br /> Bruce Lvl. 2 (gives Drunken Fist theme- Double XP while sparring, activate 'juice' bonuses)<br /> Nadeshiko (gives Road to Womanhood theme- Girl Power team bonus is +2 strength, +2 range)<br /> 1,000,000 XP (gives Teacher's Pet theme- Double JXP in regular missions)<br /> Letter of Marque (unlocks Season 2 NWW items and gives Warstruck theme- Double NWW points)<br /> 46 or more allies (gives All Together theme- Double Chances of leveling allies)<br /> Over 500,000 ryo spent in the party house (gives Money for Nothing theme- +25% ryo on regular missions)<br /> Sevens Trophy (gives Lucky Sevens theme- Automatically find allies)<br /> Stuff you've already said you have.</p> <p>Bruce Lvl. 2 and Nadeshiko really aren't that great, though. I haven't ever actually used either of the themes, nor did I use the characters when I had them. They're not hard to get either, and you can get them next Season anyway. The Letter of Marque, getting 46 allies, True Blood of the Reaper, and spending 500,000 ryo should all be a priority as they all give useful themes. The Sevens Trophy gives the best of all those, but is very difficult to get. If you don't already have it, don't worry about it.</p> <p>Okay, let's say that you make your Sannin run on day 1. You start the mission, but don't finish it. On day 2, it turns out that you made #1 Jonin and #3 Season 1. You finish the mission on day 2, then do 2&nbsp;B A Master and Cashing In on that day as well. Then you loop, still on Day 2.</p> <p>When you loop, you'll get the Sannin theme, the Out on Top theme, and you'll still have the golden item you got from Cashing In. The game considers you as being the rank you are at the beginning of the day for Out on Top. Since you were top Jonin, and you started the day at Jonin, then you'll get Out on Top.</p> <p>It used to be real common for people to make a Sannin run and then loop the next day, since there was actually a time where Sannin required you to be the top player in your rank. They'd get Sannin and then loop, getting both the Sannin and Out on Top theme.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241415</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241415</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 22:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>As far as getting out on top and sannin at the same time was a concern of mine. The theme page says that you have too lop the day you are number one in your rank (I think it means the day after since the rankings are updated nightly). So if I completed the sannin special mission before looping it would mean I'd have to be the number one sannin when I looped, which would most likely be difficult if I was doing the XP run as a jonin (which I am). Unless of course I'm missing something. But then again that was my initial plan. TO get close to 2 million XP</p> <p>I did the 15 arena wins in a day and got my <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:warrior-of-wisdom">warrior-of-wisdom</a> and my <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:jazz-hands">jazz-hands</a>.<br /> I have yet to beat wasteland. I stopped after getting 3 out of the 4 sounds from outskirts and turned my sights towards my "sannin run" instead. Should I really go back and try to finish it, and still have the time the time to prepare for two sannin runs this season? I can always go back and loop as a legacy in my 4th season. So essentially, what rewards would be best to go ahead and get now?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241362</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241362</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 19:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You know, now that I think about it, I think you're right.</p> <p>It used to be that you would have to get top 3 Jonin and then you could get Sannin the next day. That way, the top Jonin was always completing a Sannin run, and most of the time, 2nd and 3rd were as well. However, with the change, you might be right. The top Jonin probably DIDNT get Sannin, and as such, probably has less than 1,000,000 ranking.</p> <p>So I suppose that if you got to 1,000,000 XP, started the mission, but didn't finish it, and then ran some more missions until you were out of stamina, you'd have a good chance of making top Jonin. The next day, you could finish the mission and loop, getting you Sannin and Out on Top, but you probably WONT get a golden item. You might, but I wouldn't count on it. You'll need AT LEAST 1,500,000 to have much of a chance and about 2,000,000 to make it a safe bet. That's pretty high for a Season 1 Jonin. (Good news, the Arena Favorite WILL count for this.) If you can get that much on a Jonin run, then I say go for it. If not, then you'll probably be better off doing a top 3 run as a Sannin using a Timmy2, Pinky2, Emosuke3 set up. Emosuke3 makes running any rank mission a piece of cake. If you don't have him, get him. Emosuke3+Billy3 gives a very good theme.</p> <p>To further clarify, your priorities should be: Sannin &gt; Top 3 &gt; Out on Top.</p> <p>By the way, if you HAVEN'T completed Wasteland yet or if you haven't won at least 15 arena matches in 1 day so far this Season, you should probably do that before looping. They both give you a very good item that is different for each Bloodline (meaning, unless you want to loop as the same bloodline as you have now, you won't be able to get it next Season). Season 1 Wasteland is tough, but it is doable. Winning 10 arena matches in 1 day also gives an item that is practically a must-have if you want to do well in the arena next Season.</p> <p>Looping as a genin = Fail. Don't do it. It'll take forever (you'd have to hit level 20+3/Season as a Genin), and there are a lot more important bonuses to get each Season. The way the game is currently set up, it takes until at least Season 4 to get everything, and that's with extreme luck. (You'd need to win the golden items from the lotto.)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241352</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241352</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 19:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Huh. My train of thought was that as a jonin I'd have a better shot at the out on top theme as I thought most people would get sannin as soon as hitting their 1 million +. Thus the next day when their rankings showed up it would be as a sannin rather thank as a jonin. Thus the top ranked jonins would just be regular people who just happened to do better on missions than others or had their top web/7day bonus or something. But I guess I can push the out on top theme back a few seasons (if push comes to shove I"ll just loop as a genin).</p> <p>Assuming I tried another XP run after becoming sannin, what would I change in my plan? Just running AA's rather than A-ranks? I'm not sure I'm completely confidant I'll be able to do AA-ranks missions that well either. Any further tips?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-241047</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-241047</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 20:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>That's fine that you want it, but what I'm trying to say is that Out on Top is MUCH easier as a Sannin. You hardly have to prepare. In fact, I got Out on Top as a Season 1 Sannin by accident. I was running AA-rank Mission with OI and Timmy2 (purely for AP) and managed to beat out everyone else. I had a few bonuses to stamina but not many. No sparring, no Blue Flower Hairpin, no Hottie Regeneration.</p> <p>Besides, the top 3 reward is actually useful, and you can very easily get that as a Sannin. Being Sannin is useful too because of the +15% ryo item (that does loop, so it's a permanent increase). Out on Top isn't. You can try for it (as I was planning to do before I hit it by accident), but get the stuff that'll actually be useful before getting the useless stuff solely for collection purposes.</p> <p>By the way, I got roughly 400,000 XP today by running ~30 missions with only the bonuses that are always active. In short: You can get a LOT more XP as a Sannin than as a Jonin.</p> <p>Out on Top runs as Sannin generally take very little preparation. During your Sannin run, find out what stamina bonuses you need and just don't use the ones you don't need. By this I mean, Blue Flower Hairpin, Sparring, Hottie Regen, etc. If you can avoid those, then you'll still have 3 hairpin pieces, 49/99/149/199 spars, etc for another run. If you can avoid them all, then it's just essentially waiting another week to do a second run. If you can enhance your Obsessive Insight with the XP you get from your run, that'll help for a second run as well. Boots (from wasteland) also make it easier.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240854</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240854</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 09:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's probably not hard at all as a S1 Sannin….That was when I got Out On Top, though that was before Sannin was considerably easier to get, as well…</p> <p>After being looplocked ( meaning I started the day at ~72 stamina as opposed to base stamina + bonuses ), I managed around 900k just running AA-rank missions with an XP team and OI—pretty sure I didn't use any silver elixirs at all for that…or maybe I used only one. Lear has a good point: perhaps for now, rather than using your elixirs for an Out on Top run, you might want to just do Sannin for now, and wait for Out on Top until later?</p> <p>Although, if you have everything you wanted to do in Season 1 complete already, then that probably would be the way to go for you.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240842</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240842</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 08:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Huh, I really should have noticed Mister Tea was season 2. Okay then. I'll end up with less than the calculations, but I'd really rather have out on top out of the way now (purely for the sake of it, to tell you the truth). To do so as a sannin would mean I'd have to wait till next season (being at lvl 52 does mean I do have ample time to prepare, but I doubt I could prepare for something like this twice in a row before I'm forced to loop).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240629</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240629</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 19:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>First off, Mister Tea is Season 2 only, which is why I thought you were Season 2, for a Season 1 run, this is what you should have:</p> <p>Captains Jacket - +10%<br /> Letter of Marque - +10%<br /> Ancient Teachings - +10%<br /> Note Rush - +20%<br /> Timmy Lvl. 2 - +20%<br /> Stalkergirl Lvl. 2 - +1 stamina/mission (essentially +10%)<br /> Pinky Lvl. 2 - +1 stamina/mission (essentially +10%)<br /> Sand Monument - +1 stamina/mission (essentiially +10%)<br /> Obsessive Insight - +50% minus chakra charge cost</p> <p>If you need more range, swap Stalkergirl Lvl. 2 out for Emosuke Lvl. 3.</p> <p>Assuming the 4,750 XP/mission is correct (it sounds a little high to me, but if you're smokebombing out of single stat missions, I suppose that's fairly close), then you should be able to get: 4,750 x 1.1 x 1.1 x 1.1 x 1.2 x 1.2 x 1.5 = 13,656 XP/mission on average</p> <p>Assuming a Pinky2, Stalkergirl2, Timmy2 team, then you should be running missions at 7 stamina per mission.</p> <p>1,000,000/13,656 = (rounded up) 74 missions at 7 stamina/mission = 518 stamina plus chakra charging costs</p> <p>So you should be able to get Sannin very easily. Remember to save 30 stamina to start the mission and another 30 to change teams if you want to complete it on the same day as your run (assuming you've already changed teams).</p> <p>The Arena Favorite wasn't included because it doesn't help a Sannin run. It only helps a top 3 run or an Out on Top run. That's because the Arena Favorite adds 15% to your *end of day* ranking, meaning that it doesn't add it in until it calculates the rankings that show up on the top daily players. If you're going for Out on Top or top 3, then take the XP ranking you have after your run and multiply it by 1.15. That'll give you your total ranking for tomorrow.</p> <p>As a side note, the 2&nbsp;B A Master mission was intended to be completed by Sannin players for the most part. That is, Jonin's generally won't be able to get enough XP to make top 3. It's possible that Season 1 Jonin could get lucky and end up as a top 3 player every now and then, but don't expect it to happen often.</p> <p>Also, the Out on Top theme sucks. It really does. I've only used it twice, now, and even then it was only because I had nothing better to turn on. It really should buffed, but the way it is now, it's really not worth trying to get. The only reason you'd want it is for the sake of having it. And even still, it'd be easier to make an Out on Top run as a Sannin than it would to do so as a Jonin. There's less competition.</p> <p>In short, BvS playerlookup says you're only level 51 right now. So don't fret about getting top 3 and Out on Top at the moment. Just focus on your Sannin run. You can get the other two later, and it's much easier to do them as a Sannin than as a Jonin.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240591</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240591</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 18:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Er… I'm in season one. The only reason I'm stressing this sannin run so much is because I'm not actually shooting for sannin. I want to get the "out on top" (or whatever it is) theme. Doing so requires that i loop as number one in my rank. If possible I'd like to do it as a sannin but if I don't have enough daily XP after it's all said and done, I'm going to loop as a jonin (which I should be #1 as). Season 2+ seems much more difficult to pull off (even with all the extra bonuses) so I want to get this done while in S1. Also, if my ranking meets the cut, I'd like to complete the "2&nbsp;B A MASTER" special mission as well. Ultimately I'd like to get sannin, beat 2&nbsp;b a master, and loop as #1 to get the theme all in one day, but that might be too ambitious. Not sure.</p> <p>What I plan on doing is smoke bombing out of most, if not all, single stat ninjutsu missions and only completing the double stat ones. Thus I gain more XP per mission (the XP ranking rewards range from 4600 - 5100, but I found a safe average at 4750). If I play everything out right I should have just over 1000 stamina like you suggested as well.</p> <p>As far as multipliers, starting off at a base 4750 I get:<br /> X 10% for Captain's Jacket = 5225<br /> X 10% for Letter of Marque = 5747.5<br /> X 10% for Ancient Teachings (I'm going to hopefully be adopted by an epic village with this upgrade) = 6322.25<br /> X 15% for Arena Favorite (you forgot to count this?) = 7270.5875<br /> X 20% for Note Rush = 8724.705<br /> X 20% for Timmy Lvl. 2 = 10469.646<br /> X 50% for Mister Tea = 15704.469<br /> X 50% for Obsessive Insight = 23556.7035<br /> X about 90 (charging chakra every 10 missions) = 2,120,103.315<br /> + around 15,000 daily ranking XP from Party room = 2135103.315<br /> + 500,000 for 5 silver elixers = A grand Total of 2,635,103.315 Daily Ranking XP (give or take a thousand as I'm not sure how it works as far as decimals)</p> <p>Now that's if everything goes according to plan. Which it won't. But my charge every 10 missions comes from the fact that I plan on hanging out with anonymous. Now that not only means I get half chakra cost of Obsessive Insight (50) it also means I get an additional 30 stamina that I didn't and won't consider.<br /> Then, the village I plan on borrowing for my run has spartan battleground, which which cut the cost in half once again to 25 chakra per use. Then I finally plan on enhancing the jutsu once which will result in the jutsu costing 22-23 each (not that big of a deal but oh well). I'm not going to be able to hang out with shorty in time so I won't be able to benefit from that, but oh well.</p> <p>Now I've seen people hit #1 with less than 1.6 million, then other days I see people with over 2.8 million (darn red eyes). Thus, I just hope I get lucky and land on a day when everyone else is being lazy.</p> <p>So even if all else fails I can definitely still hit at least 1 million XP and get to sannin. But I might skip sannin altogether and just go for the "out on top" theme.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240329</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240329</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 07:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lear</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>91991</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You'll never make 2,000,000 XP without Mister Tea. Well, you can, but it'll be a LOT harder. Getting 2,000,000 XP without Tea is like getting 3,000,000 XP with him.</p> <p>Also, if you're running A-ranks on crank 0, then you should get an average of about 3,700 XP per mission before mulitpliers. At least that's what I calculated it to be. Given, I didn't run a ton of missions to get an average, but that shouldn't be too far off.</p> <p>With multipliers*, you should be able to get around 20k-25k XP per mission. (This is off the top of my head, no calculations.) If you need to charge chakra, on average, ever 4th mission, then you should be able to get about 200,000 XP per 100 stamina. Meaning you'll need 1,000 stamina if you don't plan on using Silver Elixers. I actually did it on around 900 stamina.</p> <p>Also, if you can manage to complete an S-rank mission, do so, even if you have to use a jutsu other than Obsessive Inisight. The S-rank mission I ran (with Obsessive Inisght) gave me a little over 80,000 XP. And that's just one mission.</p> <p>*Multipliers you should have (ie. ones I had):<br /> Captains Jacket - +10%<br /> Flip Out Theme - +10%<br /> Letter of Marque - +10%<br /> Ancient Teachings - +10%<br /> Note Rush - +20%<br /> Timmy Lvl. 2 - +20%<br /> Annie Lvl. 2 - +30%<br /> Mister Tea - +50%<br /> Obsessive Insight - +50% minus chakra charge cost</p> <p>The only one that there's an excuse for not having is the Ancient Teachings, since it's a village upgrade, not an item. The others, if you don't have them, I suggest you postpone your Sannin run until you do have them.</p> <p>If you can't run missions with an Annie2, Timmy2, Tea setup and still have a &gt;95% success rate on missions, then I suggest swapping out Timmy for Emosuke3. I wouldn't bother with Stalkergirl2. The stamina return is nice, but the strength isn't going to help you enough that it makes sense to use her in place of Emosuke3.</p> <p>But 2,000,000 is easily doable with the setup I showed. My Season 2 Sannin run was about 3,400,000 XP, and this Season I got 2,000,000 with stamina left over and very little planning (no sparring bonus, no Shorty hangout bonus, no anyone hangout bonus, no Anonymous hangout, no jutsu enhancement, no Blue Flower Hairpin, no arena stamina, no juice bar stamina). You've just got to make sure you have the multipliers and around 1,000 stamina.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240317</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240317</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 06:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>I was wondering why your numbers were so low, since I didn't have Note Rush to help out. Figures that you were forgeting something :P Although you may be counting it too high, if you're taking XP values from when you complete the missions and aren't removing the XP bonuses applied due to your items.</p> </blockquote> <p>Wait… why would I remove the xp bonuses applied due to items? I'm not sure what you meant exactly (I'm just really wanting to make sure my math isn't screwy as I want to know what I'm getting into before I jump in).</p> <p>And as for team placement, I've been considering substituting stalkergirl for mistertea. Or is that extra strength bonus really that significant?</p> <p>I've got 4 nin str bonus and 14 nin range at the moment (plus one str due to the jonin training school thingy). Which should bring my total up to<br /> Nin 19(+4)<br /> Nin str +10 (without stalkergirl, +11 with her)<br /> Nin Range 1-17(highest ninjutsu difficulty in double stat A-ranks is 17).</p> <p>So, I'm not entirely sure, but I seem well enough in that field without stalkergirl. But I'm not sure at all. Maybe I'd be biting off more than could chew without her.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240316</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240316</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 06:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>FaintIce</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>142801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You need to use Obsessive Insight jutsu taught by Anonymous. When I went for Sannin, I was RedEye, didn't have Arena Favorite, had about 80 smokebombs, my team consisted of Emo2, Timmy2, and Pinky2, I had 2 silver elixirs, 1000stam, and spammed OI as much as possible. The end result was I had almost 1.5mil RXP (though I didnt get Sannin cause I had bad luck and came in 4th that day). But anyway, the good A-rank missions I ran gave me at least 11k RXP, usually 12k. After the smokebombs ran out, the missions gave me 6-9k RXP, though I had good luck and still came across many of the double req missions.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240285</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240285</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Since you can get either a +5 Stamina or a +5 Appetite drink, the max stamina you could juice up is 60, while you could juice up 30 appetite/30 stamina and go with Teriyaki Ramen instead ( assuming you're legacy ).</p> <p>I was wondering why your numbers were so low, since I didn't have Note Rush to help out. Figures that you were forgeting something :P Although you may be counting it too high, if you're taking XP values from when you complete the missions and aren't removing the XP bonuses applied due to your items.</p> <p>As far as beating the missions, that's why you'll probably use Emo3/Stalker2/Timmy2 along with Shikai to max out your strength? That's +7 strength/+3 range/+1 success on top of (since you mentioned using nin for your run) Ninja Dog, Giant Fan, and other items that boost your stats. You'll be good for most missions.</p> <p>The downtime penalty is stamina, and -levels for the day if the penalty is quite large.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240225</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240225</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 23:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I was planning on doing just that, but I wasn't sure how much the penalty would be. Glad to see I can keep track of it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240217</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240217</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 23:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Has you drink more drink it will tell you what the penalty is the next day. The 10 appetite bonus was if you were not a legacy. Since you are drink 6 of the drinks to use another silver elixir. Keep in mind the 6 will cost you 14400 ryo.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240154</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240154</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 21:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well I did indeed look at the XP guide (seeing as I posted in the discussion page), but I did the math with what bonuses I'd have available and I got numbers similar to yours (just above 8k) which was clearly different than 13k. But I also noticed some of the information there was outdated so I asked here what bonuses deelle was taking into acocunt that I wasn't, and If I had the ability to get them in time. That's also the reason why I doubted the whole +100 stamina being better than the -40 stamins as I saw that without redeye I'd be getting around 85k with it and I could manage another 100k. I actually had considered note rush in it.</p> <p>As for the Juice replacing the +40 apatite ramen, it wouldn't be all that beneficial due to the recent apatite bonus to legacies.<br /> 220 starting daily apatite<br /> -50 * 4 silver elixers<br /> leaving you with 20 apatite left. and additional 10 from juice would increase it to 30 apatite which wouldn't help. And additional 40, however, would leave me with the ability to take a fifth silver elixer and 10 apatite left over.</p> <p>But since there might be something I'm overlooking I don't know. But till then I'm seeing on average, about 86k xp with 100 stamina. (My village doesn't have the ancient teachings upgrade)<br /> Well don't I feel silly. I completely ignored obsessive insight in the whole thing. That'll boost me over 100k in 90 stamina (The -10 stamina for the chakra charge cost). I'm not entirely sure if I can beat all of them with just obsessive insight though…</p> <p>In any case…<br /> Does anyone know if there are any problems with drinking juice that affects you the same day as you consumed it?<br /> Also, the "downtime" the next day… it's just a major stamina deficiency right? So, is it possible to completely wipe out your stamina (because I'll need to keep at least 60 stamina for the next day)?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240131</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240131</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 19:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Jadian</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103367</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Moodragonx, you should have been to the XP Guide here. You even posted on the discussion page for it. Why not just use that if you want to know "what bonuses I should be considering"?</p> <p>I think that S1, I was only getting 7k-8k (closer to 8k-9k, if you count Arena Favorite, which isn't added to each mission's ranking XP yielded) on the dual-stat missions, though that was as a WE without Note Rush.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-240109</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-240109</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 19:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>But I don't think I'll be running into double req A-ranks the whole time. I have it set up so I should have just over 1000 (or 1100 with the ramen) stamina for the day and I doubt that all 110 (using stalkergirl for return stamina) missions I can run with that will be double req. To pull that off I'd need tons of smokebombs…</p> <p>If I ran just ninjutsu (which have the highest ratio of double requs to total; 7:19) A-Ranks I'd need roughly 189 smokebombs to get out of all the single rquirement missions unscathed.</p> <p>And the double reqs gave 4600~5000 each, how does that jump to 13k (not asking because I'm skeptical, just asking so I know what bonuses I should be considering). I don't have any monster drops that'll help so that might be a problem.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-239775</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-239775</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 03:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>deelle</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>103382</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <blockquote> <p>Also on the topic of the sannin run (and I know this was discussed on the XP GUide) should I go for the +100 stamina ramen or -40 apetite ramen? Because with that extra forty apetite I could take another silver elixir and get another 100k daily xp. I doubt I could gain 100k in 100 stamina.</p> </blockquote> <p>You should go for the +100 stamina ramen. +10 appetite can be gotten from Juice Bar, so you can still take both. If you don't have access to Juice Bar, +100 stamina still. I think average xp get is 13k for double requirement A-rank mission.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-239753</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-239753</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 02:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>naito</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95487</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Limit i believe is constant. It is 12 for both a season 1 and a season 2 character of mine. The downtime does ocur the next day. If you really want that extra elixir just drink two of the +5 appetite drinks from the juice bar.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-239746</guid>
				<title>Re: Juice Bar</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-239746</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 02:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>FaintIce</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>142801</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Well different things lead to the factors that tell you the number of juices you can consume (like rank, season, items, etc.), i.e., your Limit and Tolerance. Your limit is the total number of Juices you can consume, while the Tolerance is how many you can take before the penalties start. With my S1 Jonin chara, I have a limit of 12 and a tolerance of 2. And from what I understand, the penalties don't take affect until the next day, but I don't know for sure as I haven't gone over my Tolerance. As of this moment, I think the only item that affects the the negative effects is the Hollow Leg (again, I'm not 100% on that).</p> <p>As for the Sannin run, I take the +100stam Ramen. I can get 100k rxp easy just running A-ranks with smokebombs. And especially now with NinjaBurger, the +40app Ramen isn't really necessary, well imo it isn't.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465#post-239729</guid>
				<title>XP looks like it&#039;s a smiley</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81465/juice-bar#post-239729</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 01:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>moodragonx</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>161593</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I was wondering, what's the actual limit to how much juice you can consume (barring need of ryo) in one day. I know you have downtime the next day but for that specific day that your actually drinking the juice, is there any actual limit? Or any defect at all on the same day? Like I''m not sure but it said that you have penalties on missions and stuff, but is that the same day that you're drinking or the next? Are there any known factors (besides hollow leg) that affect the negative effects of juice (if there are any at all).</p> <p>I'm asking all of this to prepare for my sannin run and I want to know how much I'll be able to consume safely.</p> <p>Also on the topic of the sannin run (and I know this was discussed on the XP GUide) should I go for the +100 stamina ramen or -40 apetite ramen? Because with that extra forty apetite I could take another silver elixir and get another 100k daily xp. I doubt I could gain 100k in 100 stamina.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>