<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Kage-ship</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81367/kage-ship</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Kage-ship&quot; - 7-day retake kage position rule</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:54:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81367#post-240307</guid>
				<title>Re: Kage-ship</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81367/kage-ship#post-240307</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 06:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>argent</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>99364</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>From what I can tell, you have to log in at least once every seven days and burn through all of your stamina (or most, I think Stamina &lt;= 9 is what you want). Running missions is the preferred way, but as far as I know anything that burns through your stamina will do it.</p> <p>If you are allowed to retake your village, scroll to the bottom of the village area and there should be a section there. Retaking your village bingos you (something about being tired out or some such).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81367#post-239424</guid>
				<title>Kage-ship</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-81367/kage-ship#post-239424</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 17:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i lost kageship due to being "inactive" for 7 days.i wasnt really inactive as i logged on several times each day,i apparently just didnt do anything that counts as action,didnt patrol cause we have 50+ peace time bonus and didnt do any missions as i had little time this week.well anyway my question is about the 7 day retake kageship rule:can somebody explain to me how does this rule work,what you have to do to take it back and when(before 7 days or after 7 days-on the 8-th) and if this is possible if you loose the title due to inactivity or only if you name a new kage yourself,and if this is the case is there any other way to get it back?<br /> thank you very much for any info,as you can imagine i am pretty down and would appreciate any help.<br /> tnx</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>