<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Hunters Village</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-83329/hunters-village</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Hunters Village&quot; - A great experiment</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:56:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-83329#post-244524</guid>
				<title>Hunters Village</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-83329/hunters-village#post-244524</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2008 03:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Azareth</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>188187</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>With the new Item Shipping option, I wanted to see if people would be interested in forming a Mercenary Village.</p> <p>Rather than the standard method of operation, the village would sell its services to other villages for a nominal fee. Depending on the actions requested, the fee could range from a few items, donated contracts, monster drops, or even a free invasion against the client.</p> <p>Possible Services:<br /> -Raids<br /> -Invasions<br /> -Intelligence<br /> -Bingos<br /> -Bingo Locks</p> <p>While this probably wouldn't drastically affect the gameplay, I think it could prove to be an interesting addition, especially when contracted by small, solo villages for assistance against their rivals.</p> <p>Assuming enouh people would be interested in founding/running this village, we could even create 2, one for NRF, one for Non-NRF, enabling a large number of clients.</p> <p>This is an experimental Village, but at this point, we're struggling to get enough members to enter the NWW. If this village catches your interest, please join up so that we can all start making money.</p> <p>If you have any questions about this, you can ask here on the thread, or visit the Village's Site, at: <a href="http://z10.invisionfree.com/Mercenary_Village/index.php?&amp;act=idx">http://z10.invisionfree.com/Mercenary_Village/index.php?&amp;act=idx</a></p> <p>Hope to see you soon!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>