<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?&quot; - Looking for the Best Team make-up to do the big Wasteland Missions</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:57:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739#post-252372</guid>
				<title>Re: Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions#post-252372</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2008 13:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gogolu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>95693</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>For me best team in the Inner Wastelands is: Palmface + Threads + Haus.</p> <p>Why? Because of those finds:</p> <p>Rubber Bits(Nin mission)<br /> Furry Swatch Distill into 2 x Fur Square(Nin mission)<br /> Wampus Pelt Distill into 3 x Fur Square(Gen mission)</p> <p>Fanboy Shirt Distill only into 1 x Fur Square(Tai mission)</p> <p>So you only have problem with Tai missions and you should use smoke bombs when they come.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739#post-252180</guid>
				<title>Re: Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions#post-252180</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2008 03:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Buretsu</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>112381</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Early Outskirts:<br /> Flutie2, Sticky2, Haus. In Season 1, without access to the Stand By Theme, improving drop rates is a must. 4x Rate from Ichi Ramen + Haus is almost an auto-drop on most missions, and Tai missions are relatively rare, so Tubby isn't a must. Once you do get Stand By going, you can swap Tubby2 back in.</p> <p>Advanced Outskirts, Early Wastelands:<br /> Bones2, Haus, Good Boy. Good all around Range and free Successes, with increased Drop Rate. This will serve you well until you can unlock Advanced Wastelands. Plus, on Crank 0, with this setup and with Letter of Marque, Sword Call Jutsu is an auto-pass on the missions get the initial 3 Wastelands allies.</p> <p>Advanced Wastelands:<br /> If you're in need of range, go with The Paper, Venus, Jaws. A solid 5 Range and 1 added Strength. It's at this point you'll really want to consider Diagnosis to help with getting drops. Otherwise, you can continue on with the Bones2, Haus, Good Boy setup.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739#post-251815</guid>
				<title>Re: Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions#post-251815</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 19:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Honestly, there is no single "best team" for the biggest Wasteland Missions: you're going to have to tailor your team to beat them.</p> <p>What CAN be useful, though, is having LisaLisa, Hyuk, and Right. You can't use them directly in the Wasteland, but you can use them to farm Note Pages. These are needed for LisaLisa's jutsu 'Turn the Page', which will let you switch teams without using Stamina. This makes switching teams in and out much easier.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739#post-251813</guid>
				<title>Re: Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions#post-251813</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 19:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>kelumhi</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>24443</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i have to disagree. Sticky Lvl2 + Flutey Lvl2 + Tubby Lvl2 might be a very good outskirts team, but i think that the best starting wasteland team is Good Boy+Bones Lvl. 2+Haus. with goodboy you need a lot less successes, bones gives you the needed range, and haus secures the item drop (which is really what everyone wants). then in inner inner wastelands, IMO the best team is Jaws+The Paper+Venus which is +5range, +1 wasteland strength. of course i personally prefer The Paper+Venus+haus for the increase chance of getting a Hide Piece.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739#post-251775</guid>
				<title>Re: Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions#post-251775</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Sticky Lvl2 + Flutey Lvl2 + Tubby Lvl2 make for the best team for general wasteland missions.</p> <p>For the Special Missions, tailoring your party shouldn't be too difficult.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739#post-251728</guid>
				<title>Best Team for Doing Wasteland Missions?</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85739/best-team-for-doing-wasteland-missions#post-251728</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 18:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Looking for the Best Team make-up to do the big Wasteland Missions.</p> <p>Any opinions?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>