<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Kaiju Point Standings</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Kaiju Point Standings&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 04:44:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-302234</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-302234</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 00:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Anyone can join for any amount of time, but only if we have room at the time (which we often do not).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-302092</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-302092</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 20:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Cambdoranononononono</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>153250</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Is this offer specifically for long-term members of the village, or would it be at all acceptable to join the village for the purpose of earning an item?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-281022</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-281022</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 18:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Keep in mind that damage doesn't matter for anything except for Terri 3. Terri 3 only matters if you're in Season 3 or higher. Everything else is determined by number of attacks (where higher attacks gives you a greater probability of getting the item, even if you're hitting for next to nothing).</p> <p>Cybuster has only received about 3 drops out of our past ~30 kaiju that weren't from Terri 3. She's also doing about 40-50% of <em>all</em> the damage to the kaiju. And she's lost some Terri 3 drops too (though not many).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-281004</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-281004</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 17:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RupertGriffin</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>219105</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>… Does that mean we might actually stand a chance at getting some of these items ourselves?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-280972</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-280972</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 16:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Cybuster is a Sannin with Hard Corps, and since she hit her loop timer, she's been juicing to full every day. This means her damage is multiplied by 1.5x, 2x, and then 1.6x, for a total of 4.8x normal damage. To do 150 damage per hit, she only needs ~32 successes. She also gets between 11 and 12 successes automatically each hit (Poisoned Daggers, Bring the House Down, Letter of Marque, and Plug Suit/Power Over 9000), meaning she only needs 20-21 successes from the dice.</p> <p>She's also using Terri 3 (+5 kaiju damage), and potentially wasteland allies that give +8 and +6 levels respectively, so there's 14 levels right there, and 5 more damage. Considering she's at her loop timer with a Knightmare frame in S3, her base levels are ~29-33 in all stats. Keep in mind that she's won pretty much every monster drop we've had so far (with a couple of exceptions). That's just made her ability to do damage grow.</p> <p>Having said all that, she's going to be forced to loop in about a week and a half.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-280876</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-280876</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 11:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Grimmjow6</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>124669</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>He could buy more Kaiju Dmg from the Juice Bar!?! ^^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-280796</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-280796</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2008 06:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>RupertGriffin</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>219105</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>wait… how is cy doing more than 150 damage to kaiju, on average? wtf? As a matter of fact… against one of them, he got 335 average damage per hit! 2/3 of that (for the +50%)… is 223. Assuming he got 5 successes for bringing down the house… That doesn't even almost sound like a reasonable number of levels to have. I have to be missing something.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-261880</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-261880</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2008 08:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>fayemyzteriouz</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>143714</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yay, I got my first 10 points :D Uzuki-chan, I'd be attacking the kaiju five times a day and would spy once I hit Sp. Jonin (maybe) :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-261627</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-261627</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 23:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>To clarify, the current standings are updated to the day roll that started that day. (So if it says 9/15, it includes everything that happened before the day roll that started the day of 9/15).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-261154</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-261154</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 14:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Grimmjow6</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>124669</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The 118 on me can't be true..</p> <p>48+48 = 98</p> <p>I had 61 points before i did those 2 spying days, and today i should get +30 more.</p> <p>So it should be, 158+30 = /</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-259085</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-259085</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 23:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm generally not going to check, since it takes too much time. However, it's better for the village if they're in NRF villages.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-259074</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-259074</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2008 23:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>fayemyzteriouz</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>143714</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Uzuki, can we put spies on non-NRF villages?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-249768</guid>
				<title>Re: Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-249768</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 15:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong><em>The following points are included in the standings</em></strong></p> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:07): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into MoonLight Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:06): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Tuesday Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:04): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into UNIT Force Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:04): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Valhalla Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:03): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Volcano Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:03): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Uraha Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:03): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Seraphim Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:03): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into TFF Rant Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:03): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Suzaku Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:03): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Moon Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:02): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Strata Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 13:02): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Red Dawn Village!</li> </ol> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 11:37): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Tiger Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 11:35): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Threatdown Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 11:35): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Underworld Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 11:35): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Toxic Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 11:34): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into TFF II Village!</li> </ol> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 18:58): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into UFC Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 18:58): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into Toukon Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 18:58): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into Tardis Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/26 (Sun - 18:57): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into MoonLight Village!</li> </ol> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 4:01): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Obvious Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 4:00): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Norse Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:59): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into NerdFury Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:58): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Neo Blazon Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:58): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into NapalmLuck Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:57): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Mugiwara Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:56): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into MoonLight Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:56): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Moon Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:55): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Kamkatana Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:55): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Jedi Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:55): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Hinamizawa Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:54): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Gold Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:53): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Dotaportal Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 3:53): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Anansi Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:42): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Volcano Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:42): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Tsubasa Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:41): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Spaghetti Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:41): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Relentless Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:41): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Rasta Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:40): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Oniwaban Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:40): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into One Piece Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 5:40): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Champions Village!</li> </ol> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:29): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into ElDorado Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:29): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Sith Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:28): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Dark Moon Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:28): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into The Cake Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:28): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into WhyNot Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:28): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into TFF Zero Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:27): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Family Guy Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:27): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Gilead Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 8:26): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Bird Village!</li> </ol> <p>Demon of the Sand is defeated! 10/27 (Mon): The Demon of the Sand has been defeated! Uzuki received Spirit of the Demon of the Sand! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - Uzuki- 53. godofall- 25. DeMy- 22. ranvier- 18. Darkshard- 18. KingMe- 16. Tsubani- 15. Arwed- 13. Ainn- 12. Stone245- 9. MiniTaurus- 8. Dasende- 7. Thoma- 6. red dragon- 5. Rupert- 2. ukagore- 1. WolfX- 1. dragonmark- 1. Ananvil- 1.</p> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 15:16): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Tanstaafl Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 15:14): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Maelstrom Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/27 (Mon - 15:14): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into TFF II Village!</li> </ol> <p>Cardcatchers is defeated! 10/27 (Mon): The Cardcatchers has been defeated! Uzuki and Darkshard received Claw Card! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - Angelg- 14. Niroque- 10. IzzyPuff- 7. Darkshard- 6. Dasende- 5. SonixChao- 3. Tsubani- 2. Uzuki- 2. Rupert- 1. godofall- 1. Angelg won a Trophy Item, for doing a total of 4147 Damage!</p> <p>Zodiac Girlyboys Fight! 10/28 (Tue): You have 6 days left to defeat Zodiac Girlyboys! Total number of successfull attacks from each Ninja — godofall- 13. Angelg- 12. KingMe- 8. Rupert- 1.</p> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:57): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Dream Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:56): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Yume Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:55): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Watermelon Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:55): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Volcano Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:54): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Tiger Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:54): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into The Kaskus Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:53): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Star5 HQ Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:53): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Spaghetti Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:52): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Sarcasm Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:52): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Rekidaishi Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:51): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into One Piece Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:50): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into NerdFury Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:49): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Mugiwara Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:48): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Incendium Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:47): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Generic Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:46): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Dotaportal Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/28 (Tue - 3:46): Ainn has infiltrated a spy into Dark Flame Village!</li> </ol> <p>Zodiac Girlyboys is defeated! 10/28 (Tue): The Zodiac Girlyboys has been defeated! Uzuki and godofall received Fruits Basket! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - godofall- 19. Angelg- 12. KingMe- 8. Uzuki- 2. Rupert- 1. Angelg won a Trophy Item, for doing a total of 4035 Damage!</p> <p>Pro Wrestlers is defeated! 10/28 (Tue): The Pro Wrestlers has been defeated! Uzuki and Niroque received Shiny Belt! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - Grimmjow6- 18. Angelg- 11. Niroque- 9. Darkshard- 7. Tsubani- 5. WolfX- 1. Uzuki- 1. Angelg won a Trophy Item, for doing a total of 3595 Damage!</p> <p>Dakralai is defeated! 10/29 (Wed): The Dakralai has been defeated! Uzuki and DeMy received Hacksaw! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - godofall- 16. Ainn- 13. Angelg- 11. ranvier- 9. KingMe- 7. Darkshard- 5. Tsubani- 5. Dasende- 5. DeMy- 5. Arwed- 4. Uzuki- 4. Grimmjow6- 3. SonixChao- 2. Rupert- 2. WolfX- 2. Ananvil- 1. Ainn won a Trophy Item, for doing a total of 3930 Damage!</p> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 12:32): WolfX has infiltrated a spy into Ero Village!</li> </ol> <p>Celeste is defeated! 10/29 (Wed): The Celeste has been defeated! Uzuki and Grimmjow6 received Poisoned Daggers! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - Fenix01- 27. Grimmjow6- 18. godofall- 14. Angelg- 14. Niroque- 10. Pandafish- 8. ranvier- 8. Thoma- 8. Terjeal- 8. Tsubani- 7. Ruby Moon- 6. Dasende- 6. Ananvil- 4. BlackMage2- 4. MiniTaurus- 3. Ainn- 3. Umbra- 2. Uzuki- 2. Rupert- 1. Hitomi B- 1. Angelg won a Trophy Item, for doing a total of 4693 Damage!</p> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 19:18): Ananvil has infiltrated a spy into Dark Village!</li> </ol> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 20:38): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into Malicious Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 20:38): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into Imperial Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 20:36): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into Fantasy Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 20:36): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into 3rd Eye Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/29 (Wed - 20:36): Darkshard has infiltrated a spy into Button Village!</li> </ol> <p>Robot Monkeys is defeated! 10/30 (Thu): The Robot Monkeys has been defeated! Uzuki and Darkshard received Monkey Cymbals! Total amount of fights each Ninja did - Angelg- 9. Darkshard- 8. godofall- 6. Grimmjow6- 4. Ananvil- 3. Rupert- 2. BlackMage2- 2. Uzuki- 2. cyborg009- 1. Angelg won a Trophy Item, for doing a total of 3051 Damage!</p> <ol> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:21): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Mirage Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:18): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Tsubasa Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:17): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Incendium Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:17): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Bear Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:17): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Eulers Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:16): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Blazzed Village!</li> <li>Spy Success 10/30 (Thu - 14:16): Thoma has infiltrated a spy into Scarlet Village!</li> </ol> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157#post-249766</guid>
				<title>Kaiju Point Standings</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-85157/kaiju-point-standings#post-249766</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BvS-Uzuki</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>78144</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>These points are used for purchasing kaiju drops, when they become available. You can obtain points in the following ways:</p> <p>Attacking a kaiju: +1&nbsp;pt. per attack (top 10% of attackers on a kaiju get double points)<br /> Spying on another village: +3&nbsp;pt. per spy placed</p> <p>For duplicate kaiju drops (all but 5 of them), the system will work like this. Base cost will be kaiju's health divided by 25. In the event that more than one person has enough points to buy the item, people should send me 1 message saying how much they're willing to spend on it. The item will go to the person who bid the most, but they will only have to pay the amount the second place bidder bid + 1 point (minimum of the item's cost). If that's a tie, it goes to whoever has more points then. If no one wants to buy an item with points, it goes in the claw machine.</p> <p>You can still bid on items that are in the claw machine, assuming no one has won them yet. If someone bids the minimum bid for the item when it's in the claw machine, I take it out of the claw machine and send it to them. Otherwise, you're welcome to try and spend ryo to win it.</p> <p>Bidding is open for the following items:<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:big-mouth">Big Mouth</a> - 600 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:book-of-spoilers">Book of Spoilers</a> - 240 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:carapace-armor">Carapace Armor</a> - 160 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:claw-card">Claw Card</a> - 280 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:go-piece">Go Piece</a> - 320 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:granola-camouflage">Granola Camouflage</a> - 360 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:groupies">Groupies</a> - 280 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:kaiju-memento">Kaiju Memento</a> - 400 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:lab-coat">Lab Coat</a> - 800 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:late-night-snack">Late-Night Snack</a> - 200 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:magical-wand">Magical Wand</a> - 240 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:monkey-cymbals">Monkey Cymbals</a> - 280 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:perfect-hair">Perfect Hair</a> - 200 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:persocom">Persocom</a> - 280 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:plug-suit">Plug Suit</a> - 280 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:power-over-9000">Power Over 9000</a> - 200 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:regalia">Regalia</a> - 800 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:shiny-belt">Shiny Belt</a> - 240 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:spirit-of-the-demon-of-the-sand">Spirit of the Demon of the Sand</a> - 1,400 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:spirit-of-the-nine-tailed-fox">Spirit of the Nine Tailed Fox</a> - 1200 pts.<br /> <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:troll-account">Troll Account</a> - 360 pts.</p> <p><em>10/26 Current Standings</em>:<br /> Aarroniero : 3<br /> Ainn : 247<br /> Ananvil : 417<br /> Arcteris : 53<br /> Arekanderu : 42<br /> Arwed : 107<br /> BlackMage2 : 209<br /> Blah Nin : 47<br /> Bleach261 : 161<br /> Captain : 47<br /> cyborg009 : 137<br /> Cybuster : 788<br /> Darkshard : 255<br /> Dasende : 197<br /> DeMy : 46<br /> DesertJ : 99<br /> dragonmark : 43<br /> Fenix01 : 116<br /> GodMe : 30<br /> godofall : 449<br /> GogoluG : 45<br /> Grimmjow6 : 86<br /> Harisu : 5<br /> Hitomi B : 95<br /> IzzyPuff : 31<br /> Kensen : 19<br /> KingMe : 123<br /> Kohikki : 3<br /> Kyousuke : 170<br /> Lasalista : 74<br /> levacy : 47<br /> loathedkid : 60<br /> MeXoC : 154<br /> MiniTarus : 76<br /> Mokujin : 49<br /> Myusha : 33<br /> NarutoRame : 14<br /> Nei Tomoe : 54<br /> Niroque : 174<br /> Oathsend : 19<br /> ranvier : 152<br /> red dragon : 487<br /> redhiar : 175<br /> redice : 318<br /> Ruby Moon : 212<br /> Rupert : 117<br /> Simon7 : 16<br /> Snake eyes : 27<br /> SonixChao : 35<br /> Stone245 : 111<br /> Suigintou : 25<br /> Swann : 124<br /> Tatze : 10<br /> Terjeal : 273<br /> the master : 13<br /> Thoma : 57<br /> Tsubani : 277<br /> ukagore : 2<br /> Umbra : 81<br /> WolfX : 181<br /> Xavxy : 185</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>