<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Comments for page &quot;Pinchy Claw&quot;</title>
		<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Pinchy Claw&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 03:47:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-1531958</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-1531958</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 04:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>stratzvyda</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It's still ridiculous sushi this goes far beyond reasonable differentiation. Take yukumi and my current situation of spending over 3M till we finally got it, that's over 333 tries. The probability of not getting a pinchy claw from that(assuming that the drop rate is actually 5%) is 3.8*10^-8, less than one in 25 million, a dubious scenario. Interestingly, if the drop rate is actually .5% all the time and not just when you already have one, that falls to just under 20%, not even a statistically significant outlier. My guess is there was a coding typo some point along the line which causes the check to return that you always have it. Either that or it's 5% per won item, which would still make us outliers(p=.015), but nowhere near the absurdity of a one in 25 million shot occurring twice.</p> <p>For those curious as to how i got those numbers, you take the probability of failure(.95, then .995, then .9875(.05/4=.0125)) and raise it to the power of the number of attempts. Typically if it drops below .05 it's an outlier, if it drops below 1 in a million it's almost definitely not correct.</p> <p>This happening once is worse 1 in 25 million odds if 5% is the true probability, .5% is far more likely. As it happened at least twice and the player base is (ridiculously generous estimate in lieu of no data) 100,000, the probability of this occurring twice is 1 in 62,500, and i doubt we are the only ones.</p> <p>TLDR; The number isn't 5%, it's most likely .5% and the trigger is just wonky, could possibly be 5% chance per won item, but that is unlikely. MATH!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-1426655</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-1426655</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 03:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>SushiMasta</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Actually it is pretty normal when you're dealing with probability. You have to remember that it is a 5% chance EACH TIME you attempt for the claw. Just because you've lost several games in a row doesn't raise the chances of you actually winning: if you're flipping coins you're just as likely to get H H H H H H H H H H H as you are H T H T H T H T H T H. In the case of a 95:5% rate you're much more likely to lose a hundred times than win. That win within 20 games thing only applies when you theoretically involve an infinite amount of players attempting to obtain it, and the amount of players who have tried it and failed is nowhere close to that. If you arn't OK with that, I suggest just give up on this perm now.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-1300196</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-1300196</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 06:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Dracos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1197540</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm feeling fairly confident the formula is what was said&#8230;</p> <p>But only if you win. Getting it on the 4th win fits pretty reasonably with 1/20 odds. Getting it on the 100th or so try in general is not.</p> <p>Super Easy is definitely the way to go though. If I'm right its vastly better, if I'm wrong it's no worse than the others.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-1294818</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-1294818</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 20:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>MIKOLA</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>658680</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I used to got it in 5-25 rolls (do not sure 'cuz it was some monthes/few years ago) but it was super easy difficulty roll with cost 9001 ryo, SO I confirm the way. Allways hard to discuss veeeery rng-related stuff :) (even not looking at the fact that BvS mostly RnG based xD)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-1293507</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-1293507</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 17:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Dracos</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>1197540</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm seeing just far too many folks making ridiculous level of attempt claims to really believe that it is a 5 percent drop. The guy above here claims he's done it 300+ times. I've done it close to a 100 without a drop. Both of these are pretty horribly unlikely. It's more likely that either the quoted claim is out-dated or that it does require something else (1 in 20 on a successful winning crane grab? 1 in 20, if you have the Mark of the RNG? 1 in 20, requires Kona first). Maybe on success (BUt folks claim otherwise).</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-845862</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-845862</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 19:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yukimi</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>FINALLY I GOT IT!!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-843472</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-843472</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2010 00:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yukimi</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've spent around 3million ryo playing a 9001 ryo crane game (concretely hard, not that it matters). I don't have the pinchy claw, I already have kona-chan. Is there any reason why I haven't got the pinchy claw that any of you can think off? I sent a Bug Report to 11 after the first 1'5 mill ryo which was unanswered and every time I play it gets more ridicule taking into account it should be one in twenty at the worst case scenario I think. I've won the price (exploding tags in my village) a lot of times (I know it's not related) what should be a bit more difficult than winning the pinchy claw… I'm etting desperate and exhasperated… HELP.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-739341</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-739341</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 16:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Agent Inari</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>392886</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Confirmed: according to the <em>BillyClub Q&amp;A</em>, the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:pinchy-claw">Claw</a> and <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:shovel">Shovel</a> make two separate rolls of 10% and 20% respectively.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-732438</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-732438</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 19:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>zeroshadowragnarok</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>96760</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>i think it's a separate activation.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-732426</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-732426</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 19:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Agent Inari</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>392886</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Does it stack with the <a href="http://bvs.wikidot.com/items:shovel">Shovel</a>? If so, is the result a 30% chance, or two separate chances of activating?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-716592</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-716592</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 19:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>zeroshadowragnarok</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>96760</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>well the chance to win it is the same on all difficulties, however easy has the greatest chance of winning an item. (you have a chance of getting it if you win something) so our leader does 9001 (easy), 250 (normal), 500 (hard, 100 (super hard) the super hard is due to kona-chan and yes i did get her at that cost. (kona-chan is the same as in you have to win an item to have a chance of getting her)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-716571</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-716571</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 19:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Yukimi</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Is it normal to play over 150 games to a 9001 hard crane game without having the pinchy claw and not win it? T_T It just that if theorically you win it once every 20 times… more than 150 plays and not winning it… it just sucks.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-279882</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-279882</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 21:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Izuna</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>94909</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The claw game breaks with all the money you stuffed into it, and the claw drops through the hole! (They fix the game right away)</p> <p>You got Pinchy Claw!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-266684</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-266684</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 03:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Basically you can get it even on a failed attempt. It seems to be an event similar to a mission drop. I managed to get it after 4 tries over 5k ryo.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-265822</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-265822</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2008 01:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>could someone who has gotten this item please respond? shelling out thousands of ryo when i have no idea what to do isn't exactly fun.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526#post-264300</guid>
				<title>(no title)</title>
				<link>http://bvs.wikidot.com/forum/t-90526/pinchy-claw#post-264300</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2008 07:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Anonymous</wikidot:authorName>								<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>when you're playing, does it say you're going to get the claw, or do you just have to play and hope for the best?<br /> to clarify, will the slot with &gt;5000 cost say "whatever leader has shoved in machine here" or will it say "pinchy claw" while you play?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>